Hey.
Oye.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Listen, uh...
Mira, eh...
You think I have a chance with Janine?
¿Crees que tengo alguna oportunidad con Janine?
Ugh, we've been through this.
Uf, ya pasamos por esto.
Don't do this to yourself.
No te hagas esto a ti mismo.
She made it clear it isn't going to happen.
Ella dejó claro que no va a pasar.
All right, then. I guess I shouldn't get too excited about the fact...
Está bien, entonces. Supongo que no debería emocionarme demasiado por el hecho...
...that I just kissed her!
...¡de que acabo de besarla!
- Are you serious? - That's great!
- ¿Hablas en serio? - ¡Eso es genial!
Yeah, well, we'll see.
Sí, bueno, ya veremos.
You kissed her?
¿La besaste?
Oh, we kissed it up real nice.
Oh, nos besamos muy bien.
So you kissed. Then what happened?
Entonces se besaron. ¿Y luego qué pasó?
I came over here to tell you guys.
Vine aquí a contárselos.
So she's waiting over there for you?
¿Entonces ella te está esperando allí?
Yeah.
Sí.
- I gotta go. - Okay.
- Tengo que irme. - De acuerdo.
I'm gonna be late for dance class.
Voy a llegar tarde a la clase de baile.
Okay.
- Okay, now I'm really leaving. - All right.
- Bueno, ahora sí que me voy. - Está bien.
But can you just...
Pero, ¿puedes solo...
...just leave your lips?
...dejar tus labios?
- Bye. - Bye.
- Adiós. - Adiós.
Have you kissed her yet?
¿La has besado ya?
It's awesome!
¡Es increíble!
I could do it forever.
Podría hacerlo para siempre.
You know what? She kisses better than my mom cooks.
¿Sabes qué? Ella besa mejor que mi mamá cocina.
- I'm so glad you said "cooks." - Right?
- Me alegro mucho de que dijeras "cocina". - ¿Verdad?
Rachel, you've got to tell the post office that you've moved.
Rachel, tienes que decirle a la oficina de correos que te mudaste.
We still get your bills and stuff.
Todavía recibimos tus facturas y esas cosas.
Oh! Oh! Pottery Barn! You can throw the rest away.
¡Oh! ¡Oh! ¡Pottery Barn! Puedes tirar el resto.
I'm not your garbage man.
No soy tu basurero.
I'm your mailman.
Soy tu cartero.
Monica, look.
Mónica, mira.
Here is that table that I ordered. Ah!
Aquí está esa mesa que pedí. ¡Ah!
- You got it from Pottery Barn? - Yeah. It's an apothecary table.
- ¿La compraste en Pottery Barn? - Sí. Es una mesa de boticario.
Does anyone even know what an apothecary is?
¿Alguien sabe siquiera qué es un boticario?
A pharmacist.
Un farmacéutico.
Phoebe hates Pottery Barn.
Phoebe odia Pottery Barn.
I hate Pottery Barn too.
Yo también odio Pottery Barn.
They kicked me out just because I sat on a bed.
Me echaron solo porque me senté en una cama.
You took off your pants and got under the sheets.
Te quitaste los pantalones y te metiste debajo de las sábanas.
I was tired.
Estaba cansada.
Phoebe hates Pottery Barn?
¿Phoebe odia Pottery Barn?
She hates mass-produced stuff.
Ella odia las cosas producidas en masa.
She thinks her furniture should have a story behind it.
Ella piensa que sus muebles deben tener una historia detrás.
This has a story behind it.
Esto tiene una historia detrás.
They had to ship it all the way from the White Plains store.
Tuvieron que enviarlo desde la tienda de White Plains.
It's got to be one-of-a-kind.
Tiene que ser algo único.
Like that God-awful ceramic fruit bowl she has on her counter?
¿Como ese horrible frutero de cerámica que tiene en la encimera?
Hey! I made that for her.
¡Oye! Yo se lo hice.
- You made pottery? - Yeah.
- ¿Hiciste cerámica? - Sí.
I made it out of a fruit bowl I found in the garbage.
Lo hice a partir de un frutero que encontré en la basura.
If you put that in her apartment, you'll never hear the end of it.
Si pones eso en su apartamento, nunca dejarás de oírlo.
I'll tell her that it's an antique.
Le diré que es una antigüedad.
She doesn't have to know where it came from.
Ella no tiene por qué saber de dónde vino.
Ah, I love these little drawers.
Ah, me encantan estos cajoncitos.
Oh, look! It says that it holds 300 CDs.
Oh, ¡mira! Dice que le caben 300 CDs.
Ah, just like the apothecary tables of yore.
Ah, igual que las mesas de boticario de antaño.
So the farmer says:
Entonces el granjero dice:
"That's not a cow, and you're not milking."
"Eso no es una vaca, y tú no estás ordeñando."
I'm so glad you're together.
Me alegro mucho de que estén juntos.
We wanted a couple to go out with and now we have one.
Queríamos una pareja para salir y ahora tenemos una.
We're a couple of couples.
Somos un par de parejas.
I had so much fun tonight. What a great restaurant!
Me divertí mucho esta noche. ¡Qué buen restaurante!
And Chandler, I can't believe I let you pay for this one.
Y Chandler, no puedo creer que te dejara pagar por esta.
Thanks again, man.
Gracias de nuevo, amigo.
If you come over tomorrow, I'll make pasta.
Si vienes mañana, haré pasta.
- That'd be great! - Okay.
- ¡Sería genial! - Vale.
But at least let us bring the wine.
Pero al menos déjanos traer el vino.
- You don't have to. - Ah, I insist.
- No hace falta. - Ah, insisto.
- You'll get the wine, right? - Yeah.
- Tú traerás el vino, ¿verdad? - Sí.
- Okay, good night. - See you tomorrow.
- Vale, buenas noches. - Hasta mañana.
Can't wait.
No puedo esperar.
How are we going to get out of that one?
¿Cómo saldremos de esa?
- What? - I can't handle two nights in a row...
- ¿Qué? - No aguanto dos noches seguidas...
...with them.
...con ellos.
What's wrong with them?
¿Qué les pasa?
They're just a little...
Son solo un poco...
...blah!
...¡aburridos!
Blah?
¿Aburridos?
Well, you know, he's blah. She's just...
Bueno, ya sabes, él es aburrido. Ella es solo...
She's very loud for such a small person.
Es muy ruidosa para ser tan pequeña.
Uh, they're my best friends.
Uh, son mis mejores amigos.
Are you saying we can't go out? 'Cause that'd be a problem.
¿Estás diciendo que no podemos salir? Porque eso sería un problema.
Of course we can still hang out with them.
Por supuesto que podemos seguir saliendo con ellos.
Just not two nights in a row.
Solo que no dos noches seguidas.
- Okay? - I guess.
- ¿Vale? - Supongo.
Thank you.
Gracias.
I'll sell my friends and use the money to buy you presents.
Venderé a mis amigos y usaré el dinero para comprarte regalos.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Ooh! What a great table! Where did you get it?
¡Ooh! ¡Qué mesa tan genial! ¿Dónde la conseguiste?
Guess.
Adivina.
Um, a flea market?
¿Um, en un mercadillo?
Ha, I knew you would get it on the first guess.
Ja, sabía que lo adivinarías a la primera.
Isn't it cool? It's an apothecary table.
¿No es genial? Es una mesa de boticario.
Ah, wow.
Ah, guau.
You can just imagine that this is where...
Puedes imaginar que aquí es donde...
...they kept all their stuff to make potions.
...guardaban todas sus cosas para hacer pociones.
- You know? - Ooh, yes.
- ¿Sabes? - ¡Ay, sí!
Ooh, you can almost smell the opium.
Uy, casi se huele el opio.
Almost.
Casi.
Oh, how much was it?
Oh, ¿cuánto costó?
Just only 500 bucks.
Solo 500 dólares.
500 bucks at a flea market?
¿500 dólares en un mercadillo?
I thought you meant how much was it...
Pensé que te referías a cuánto costó...
...when it was new, back then.
...cuando era nuevo, en ese entonces.
- Oh, no. - Yeah, no.
- Oh, no. - Sí, no.
It was at a flea market, so it was like a dollar.
Era en un mercadillo, así que costó como un dólar.
- A dollar? - And fifty?
- ¿Un dólar? - ¿Y cincuenta?
So it was like one and fifty dollars.
Así que costó como uno y cincuenta dólares.
- They gave you the old-time pricing. - Yeah.
- Te dieron el precio de antes. - Sí.
Well, what period is it from?
Bueno, ¿de qué época es?
Uh, it's from yore.
Uh, es de antaño.
Like, the "days of yore," you know?
Como, de "tiempos remotos", ¿sabes?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Sí. Sí, lo sé.
- It's just perfect. - Oh, good.
- Es simplemente perfecto. - Oh, bien.
I bet it has a great story too.
Apuesto a que también tiene una gran historia.
Did they tell you where it's from or...
¿Te dijeron de dónde es o...?
Yes, that I know. This is from, uh, White Plains.
Sí, eso sí lo sé. Esto es de, eh, White Plains.
- White Plains. - Mm-hm.
Ooh, it sounds like such a magical place.
Uy, suena como un lugar tan mágico.
- I'm here. - Hi!
- Estoy aquí. - ¡Hola!
Oh, my God!
¡Oh, Dios mío!
- You like it? - Oh, my God!
- ¿Te gusta? - ¡Dios mío!
It's my new apothecary table!
¡Es mi nueva mesa de boticario!
Phoebe'll be here any second. She can't see this.
Phoebe llegará en cualquier segundo. No puede ver esto.
Why not? She'll love it. It's the real thing.
¿Por qué no? Le encantará. Es lo auténtico.
I got it at Pottery Barn.
La compré en Pottery Barn.
I know. I bought the same one.
Lo sé. Yo compré la misma.
And if she sees your table, she'll know I lied.
Y si ve tu mesa, sabrá que mentí.
- I said ours was an original. - Why?
- Dije que la nuestra era original. - ¿Por qué?
Because she hates Pottery Barn.
Porque odia Pottery Barn.
She hates Pottery Barn?
¿Odia Pottery Barn?
She says it's all mass-produced...
Dice que todo está producido en masa...
...nothing is authentic, and everyone winds up having the same stuff.
...nada es auténtico, y al final todos tienen lo mismo.
So come on! Can we cover this up, please?
Entonces, ¡vamos! ¿Podemos tapar esto, por favor?
What? No, no.
¿Qué? No, no.
I am not gonna hide it from Phoebe.
No voy a ocultárselo a Phoebe.
Although I did get some great Pottery Barn sheets.
Aunque sí compré unas sábanas geniales de Pottery Barn.
Ooh, I forgot they made sheets!
¡Uy, olvidé que hacían sábanas!
Heh, yeah.
Je, sí.
I still can't believe she hates Pottery Barn.
Todavía no puedo creer que odie Pottery Barn.
It's not like she hates you.
No es como si te odiara a ti.
Yeah, but Pottery Barn?
Sí, ¿pero Pottery Barn?
You know what I think? She's just weird.
¿Sabes qué creo? Que es rara.
It's because she's a twin. Twins are weird.
Es porque es gemela. Los gemelos son raros.
She's not weird. She likes her stuff to be one-of-a-kind.
Ella no es rara. Le gusta que sus cosas sean únicas.
Huh. You know what's not one-of-a-kind? A twin!
Vaya. ¿Sabes qué no es único? ¡Un gemelo!
Let's turn out the lights and watch the movie.
Apaguemos las luces y veamos la película.
- Hey, ooh, cool sheet! - You like it?
- ¡Oye, oh, qué sábana tan genial! - ¿Te gusta?
- You want to know where I got it? - Sure.
- ¿Quieres saber dónde la conseguí? - Claro.
At a flea market.
En un mercadillo.
You buy your sheets at a flea market?
¿Compras tus sábanas en un mercadillo?
Come on, you gotta loosen the purse strings a little.
Vamos, tienes que aflojar un poco la cartera.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Dinner will be ready in 20 minutes.
La cena estará lista en 20 minutos.
Here is the wine to bring over tonight.
Aquí está el vino para traer esta noche.
You were also gonna buy Monica flowers...
También ibas a comprarle flores a Monica...
...but you couldn't because you paid for dinner last night.
...pero no pudiste porque pagaste la cena anoche.
Thanks. But, uh, it's just gonna be me tonight.
Gracias. Pero, eh, solo seré yo esta noche.
- What happened to Janine? - She's, uh, really sick.
- ¿Qué le pasó a Janine? - Está, eh, muy enferma.
- That's too bad. - Yeah, she's been in there all day.
- Qué lástima. - Sí, ha estado ahí dentro todo el día.
Uh, high fever, nose problem. It's...
Uh, fiebre alta, problema de nariz. Es...
...phlegm, phlegm, phlegm, phlegm, phlegm.
...mucosidad, mucosidad, mucosidad, mucosidad, mucosidad.
Monica! Chandler!
¡Monica! ¡Chandler!
I'm sorry about tonight. I don't know if Joey told you...
Lamento lo de esta noche. No sé si Joey te dijo...
...but I couldn't get out of going to this play.
...pero no pude evitar ir a esta obra.
Have a great time, huh?
Pásalo genial, ¿eh?
That's funny, I saw no phlegm.
Qué gracioso, yo no vi mucosidad.
Oh, no, she really is sick.
Oh, no, de verdad está enferma.
Then why is she going to a play?
Entonces, ¿por qué va a ir a una obra?
Uh, well, you know, "Starve a fever...
Uh, bueno, ya sabes, "Ayunar con fiebre...
...go to a play for a cold."
...ir a una obra por un resfriado."
Why is Janine not coming over for dinner?
¿Por qué Janine no viene a cenar?
Uh, she didn't want to hang out with you guys two nights in a row.
Uh, no quería pasar dos noches seguidas con ustedes.
I'm so sorry.
Lo siento mucho.
Why doesn't she want to hang out with us?
¿Por qué no quiere pasar tiempo con nosotros?
Because she, uh, thinks that you are "blah."
Porque, eh, piensa que ustedes son "aburridos".
And that, uh, you, Monica, are too loud.
Y que, eh, tú, Monica, eres demasiado ruidosa.
What?!
¡¿Qué?!
What?
¿Qué?
So she just pretended to have a good time?
Entonces, ¿ella solo fingió que se lo estaba pasando bien?
She was lying to our faces?
¿Nos estuvo mintiendo a la cara?
I can't believe this.
No puedo creer esto.
Who is she to judge us?
¿Quién es ella para juzgarnos?
- We couldn't have been nicer to her. - And I am not "blah." I am a hoot!
- No pudimos haber sido más amables con ella. - ¡Y yo no soy "aburrido". ¡Soy muy divertido!
I know, I know.
Lo sé, lo sé.
Come on, please, you guys. Don't be mad.
Vamos, por favor, chicos. No se enojen.
I'm sure she said it...
Estoy segura de que lo dijo...
...because she was nervous 'cause you're my best friends.
...porque estaba nerviosa porque son mis mejores amigos.
And it was our first date.
Y era nuestra primera cita.
Plus, she's really sick.
Además, está muy enferma.
You said you made that up!
¡Dijiste que te lo habías inventado!
But isn't the "sick" thing better than the "play" thing?
Pero, ¿no es lo de "enferma" mejor que lo de "obra"?
They're both good. I generally just go with, "Monica's drunk again."
Ambas son buenas. Yo generalmente digo: "Monica está borracha otra vez."
Come on, please just give her another chance.
Vamos, por favor, denle otra oportunidad.
- She'll come around, I promise. - Of course we will.
- Ella cambiará de opinión, lo prometo. - Claro que lo haremos.
- Come on, we gotta make dinner. - Okay.
- Vamos, tenemos que hacer la cena. - Vale.
I do not like that woman!
¡Esa mujer no me gusta nada!
I can hear you!
¡Te oigo!
I am loud!
¡Soy ruidoso!
Aw.
Ay.
Isn't it good?
¿No está bien?
Can you please not put your feet up on my new...
¿Puedes, por favor, no poner los pies encima de mi nueva...
...old sheet.
...sábana vieja.
Oh, sure.
Oh, claro.
My apothecary table!
¡Mi mesa de boticario!
- What? - No!
- ¿Qué? - ¡No!
- Where did you get this? - At Pottery Barn, okay?
- ¿De dónde sacaste esto? - De Pottery Barn, ¿vale?
Oh, my God!
¡Oh, Dios mío!
Pottery Barn has ripped off the design of our antique!
¡Pottery Barn ha plagiado el diseño de nuestra antigüedad!
Wow. If they've ripped off our table...
Vaya. Si han plagiado nuestra mesa...
...ours must be worth much more than one and fifty dollars.
...la nuestra debe valer mucho más de ciento cincuenta dólares.
This doesn't even smell like opium.
Esto ni siquiera huele a opio.
It smells like wine, which you spilled.
Huele a vino, que tú derramaste.
And thanks for wrecking my sheet.
Y gracias por destrozar mi sábana.
Ross, calm down. I'll give you the 80 cents.
Ross, cálmate. Te doy los 80 centavos.
Okay, one more time.
Está bien, una vez más.
Would you like some orange juice?
¿Te gustaría un poco de jugo de naranja?
- Perfect decibel. - I know!
- Decibelio perfecto. - ¡Lo sé!
Hey.
Oye.
Uh, what are you guys doing?
Uh, ¿qué están haciendo ustedes?
Nothing. We're just talking. You know, blah-blah-blah.
Nada. Solo estamos hablando. Ya sabes, bla-bla-bla.
Come on, you said you were gonna try.
Vamos, dijiste que ibas a intentarlo.
I came over to invite you to a movie with me and Janine.
Vine a invitarte a una película conmigo y Janine.
- What do you say? - I'd like to...
- ¿Qué dices? - Me gustaría...
...but I'm not sure if we have the time.
...pero no estoy seguro de si tenemos tiempo.
Ha, very funny. I don't know what to do.
Ja, muy gracioso. No sé qué hacer.
I really want you to get along.
Realmente quiero que se lleven bien.
Please, come to the movie with us. You owe me.
Por favor, ven a la película con nosotros. Me debes una.
- We owe you? - That's right.
- ¿Te debemos? - Así es.
I helped you out in the start of your relationship.
Te ayudé al principio de su relación.
I helped you sneak around for six months.
Te ayudé a andar a escondidas durante seis meses.
I looked like an idiot.
Parecía un idiota.
And I was humiliated.
Y me humillaron.
And I only made $200.
Y solo gané 200 dólares.
We didn't give you any money.
No te dimos dinero.
You don't think I know that?
¿Tú crees que no lo sé?
I can't decide if it goes better by the new chair...
No decido si queda mejor junto a la silla nueva...
...the Sahara desk...
...el escritorio Sahara...
...or the Parker console table.
...o la mesa consola Parker.
I didn't know there was a Pottery Barn up here.
No sabía que había un Pottery Barn por aquí.
- I know, I went a little crazy. - A little?
- Lo sé, me volví un poco loca. - ¿Un poco?
Your place looks like page 72 of the catalog.
Tu lugar parece la página 72 del catálogo.
Look at that!
¡Mira eso!
- The ornamental birdcage! Large. - Ha, ha.
- ¡La pajarera ornamental! Grande. - Ja, ja.
Oh, Ross? Be careful. That is very old.
Oh, Ross, ten cuidado. Eso es muy antiguo.
Colonial bird merchants used to bring their birds to market in that.
[ERROR API]
Fascinating.
Another amazing find! Wow.
[ERROR API]
- I bet this has a great story too. - It does.
It is a room-separating apparatus from Colonial times.
[ERROR API]
Huh, a lot of this stuff is from the Colonial times.
What are some other time periods, Rachel?
[ERROR API]
Well, there's yore.
Ahem, and, uh, you know, yesteryear.
[ERROR API]
Rachel has such a good eye for this stuff.
Ross, if you ever decide to redecorate...
[ERROR API]
- and I think you should...
- you should ask Rachel to help.
[ERROR API]
Aw, he doesn't need my help.
I think he's ready to get rid of the... What'd you call it?
[ERROR API]
The, uh, "cheap knockoffs and dinosaur junk"?
Really?
¿En serio?
You know, since you have such a great sense of what I need...
[ERROR API]
Uh, here's 60 bucks.
Why don't you take Phoebe down to that Colonial, uh, flea market...
[ERROR API]
...and get me some stuff?
I don't think Phoebe wants to come.
[ERROR API]
- I do want to. - She does want to.
- She does want to. - Yeah!
[ERROR API]
I guess the flea market was just better last time.
Well, at least I got these sheets for Ross.
[ERROR API]
Ugh, look at this. Pottery Barn.
Ugh, yeah, you know what? Don't look at it.
[ERROR API]
- Seriously, don't look at it. - Look!
There's the table they stole from us.
[ERROR API]
Oh, those bastards! Let's go.
That fan kind of looks like ours, and the birdcage, and...
[ERROR API]
Wait a second, this is our exact living room!
No, it's not.
No, no lo es.
Come on, ours is totally different.
[ERROR API]
I mean, we don't have the... We don't have that lamp.
And that screen is on the other side.
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God. This is where you got all our stuff.
- Pottery Barn! Oh, my God! - No. No.
[ERROR API]
Okay, I did, all right? I'm sorry.
I wanted this stuff and I know how you feel about Pottery Barn.
[ERROR API]
- Come on, don't be mad. - No, but I am mad.
Because this stuff is what's wrong with the world...
[ERROR API]
...and it's in my living room...
...and all I can think about is how I don't have that lamp!
[ERROR API]
Well, then, honey, buy the lamp.
We have that 60 bucks from Ross.
[ERROR API]
I can't! I can't!
Unless...
[ERROR API]
Are you saying you'd move out if I didn't buy that lamp?
No, I'm not gonna move out!
¡No, no me voy a mudar!
But are you saying that you would move out if I didn't buy that lamp?
¿Pero dices que te mudarías si yo no comprara esa lámpara?
- Yes! I would so move out. - Then I don't have a choice.
- ¡Sí! Me mudaría. - Entonces no tengo opción.
- I have to buy that lamp! - That's right.
- ¡Tengo que comprar esa lámpara! - Así es.
But at least the apothecary table's real.
Pero al menos la mesa de boticario es real.
This was great. Didn't everybody have a great time?
Esto fue genial. ¿No se divirtieron todos?
I did. I really did. And I've got to say...
Yo sí. De verdad que sí. Y tengo que decir...
...I'm sorry if I was weird after the last time we went out.
...lamento si estuve rara la última vez que salimos.
I guess I was just nervous.
Supongo que estaba nerviosa.
- That's understandable. - Don't worry about it.
- Es comprensible. - No te preocupes.
So we can go out again?
¿Entonces podemos salir otra vez?
- Absolutely. - Well, good.
- Absolutamente. - Bueno, bien.
- Okay, well, good night. - Good night.
- Okay, bueno, buenas noches. - Buenas noches.
See, huh?
¿Ves, eh?
Wasn't that fun?
¿No fue divertido?
We have got to move.
Tenemos que mudarnos.
What?
¿Qué?
I knew it!
¡Lo sabía!
You're not so quiet yourself, missy!
¡Tú tampoco eres muy callada, señorita!
I'm blah? The only thing more boring than modern dance...
¿Yo aburrida? Lo único más aburrido que la danza moderna...
...is you talking about it.
...eres tú hablando de eso.
"Oh, Chandler...
...I just lost myself in the movement."
...me perdí en el movimiento."
You know, I know you're talking...
Sabes, sé que estás hablando...
...but all I hear is blah-blah-blah-blah-blah.
...pero todo lo que oigo es bla-bla-bla-bla-bla.
All right, you and me! Let's go, right now!
¡Muy bien, tú y yo! ¡Vamos, ahora mismo!
All right, enough!
¡Muy bien, ya basta!
Enough! You two, go home. I gotta talk to Janine.
¡Basta! Ustedes dos, váyanse a casa. Tengo que hablar con Janine.
I really think you could take her.
Realmente creo que podrías vencerla.
You better hope I don't see you in the hallway!
¡Será mejor que esperes no verte en el pasillo!
All right. Uh...
Muy bien. Uh...
Look, we got a little bit of a problem here.
Mira, tenemos un pequeño problema aquí.
You can't my treat my friends that way.
No puedes tratar a mis amigos de esa manera.
- They said stuff to me too. - I know, I'll talk to them about it.
- Ellos también me dijeron cosas. - Lo sé, hablaré con ellos.
They mean so much to me.
Significan mucho para mí.
They're like my family, you know?
Son como mi familia, ¿sabes?
If you guys are gonna be fighting all the time...
Si ustedes van a estar peleando todo el tiempo...
I don't think we can be together. It just can't work, okay?
No creo que podamos estar juntos. Simplemente no puede funcionar, ¿okay?
It can't.
No puede.
I'm very upset.
Estoy muy molesta.
Okay.
Would it help if I apologized?
¿Ayudaría si me disculpara?
Yeah.
Sí.
That'd be very helpful.
Eso sería de gran ayuda.
What did I tell you about the hall?
¿Qué te dije sobre el pasillo?
I was coming over to apologize for my behavior.
Iba a disculparme por mi comportamiento.
I'd really like it if we could be friends.
Realmente me gustaría que pudiéramos ser amigos.
Well, I know that would make Joey happy, so...
Bueno, sé que eso haría feliz a Joey, así que...
...I would like that too.
...me gustaría eso también.
- Great. - Now, come on.
- Genial. - Ahora, vamos.
- I'm glad we worked it out. - Me too.
- Me alegra que lo hayamos resuelto. - A mí también.
- I'll see you. - Bye.
- Te veo. - Adiós.
- Or I'll hear you. - That's it, big girl!
- O te oigo. - ¡Eso es, grandulona!
Wait!
¡Espera!
You'd better run!
¡Será mejor que corras!
Did you hear that?
¿Oíste eso?
- What am I gonna do? - I'm sorry, man.
- ¿Qué voy a hacer? - Lo siento, amigo.
- Want to go watch? - Yeah!
- ¿Quieres ir a ver? - ¡Sí!
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- How you doing? - So, uh, did she move out?
- ¿Cómo estás? - Entonces, eh, ¿se mudó?
Pretty much.
Prácticamente.
I can't believe you just broke up with her.
No puedo creer que acabas de terminar con ella.
When it's not right, you know it.
Cuando no es correcto, lo sabes.
- You okay? - I'll be all right.
- ¿Estás bien? - Estaré bien.
- You know what'd cheer you up? - What?
- ¿Sabes qué te animaría? - ¿Qué?
I'm giving this lecture on erosion theories tomorrow night.
Mañana por la noche daré esta conferencia sobre teorías de erosión.
I think you should come.
Creo que deberías venir.
You're right, that did cheer me up.
Tienes razón, eso sí me animó.