- Hey. - Hey, check it out. This is unbelievable.
[ERROR API]
Joey has been holding his breath for almost four minutes.
Are you trying to kill me?
[ERROR API]
- Pheebs, I wanna ask you something. - Uh-huh, what?
Um, well, since I'm moving out and you're so beautiful...
[ERROR API]
...how about I move in with you?
Well, that would be great, but then what do we do about Denise?
[ERROR API]
- Who's Denise? - My roommate.
- You have a roommate? - Yes, Denise. Denise.
[ERROR API]
Hey, what is with the secrecy, Phoebe? Huh?
And what about this Denise? She cute?
[ERROR API]
How can you have a roommate that none of us know about?
Maybe because you never listen to anything I say.
[ERROR API]
I talk about her all the time. Denise!
Rach, I was thinking, I'm gonna have an extra room over at my place.
[ERROR API]
- Oh, that's true. - Why don't you move in with me?
It'll be great. We can stay up late talking, watch movies.
[ERROR API]
And you know about naked Thursdays, right?
Yeah, yeah, I think I'm gonna find my own place.
[ERROR API]
Hey, hey. I thought naked Thursdays was just our thing, man.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
What did Rachel say when you told her you were still married to her?
[ERROR API]
Oh, that. Um, she took it really well.
- Oh. You didn't tell her, did you? - No.
[ERROR API]
- Because you're in love with her. - I am not in love with her.
She was very upset about having to move out.
[ERROR API]
So I didn't tell her we were still married, because she'd only get more upset.
I comforted her. As a friend.
[ERROR API]
- What do you mean, "comforted her"? - It was nothing. I gave her a hug.
Aha. A classic sign of love, the hug.
[ERROR API]
It's also a sign of friendship.
Yeah, not in your case, Lovey Loverson.
[ERROR API]
It was a hug.
Just tell me this, did you or did you not smell her hair?
[ERROR API]
Smell her hair? Well, what if I did?
Ninety percent of a woman's pheromones come out the top of her head.
[ERROR API]
That's why women are shorter.
So that men will fall in love when they hug them.
[ERROR API]
Come on, Ross, you're a scientist.
I was hugging her as a friend, okay?
[ERROR API]
It's not my fault her hair got in my face.
She's got a lot of it, and it smells all, uh...
[ERROR API]
...you know, coconutty.
What? Oh. It doesn't mean I have feelings for Rachel.
[ERROR API]
Maybe it means I have feelings for coconuts.
Okay, whatever you say. But just be careful. Rachel's not in the same place you are.
[ERROR API]
Okay, if the place you're referring to is being in love...
...then she is in the same place as me, because I am not in that place.
[ERROR API]
Okay, I didn't understand that.
But maybe that's because you were speaking the secret language of love.
[ERROR API]
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- Dude, some guy just called for you. - Who was it?
- Güey, te llamaron. - ¿Quién era?
I don't know.
No sé.
How about "Thanks for taking the message"? Jeez.
¿Qué tal "Gracias por tomar el mensaje"? Caray.
Hey, listen.
Oye, escucha.
When you move in, Rachel's room's gonna be empty.
Cuando te mudes, la habitación de Rachel va a quedar vacía.
You wanna talk about what we wanna do with it?
¿Quieres hablar de lo que vamos a hacer con ella?
- Sure. - Okay.
- Claro. - De acuerdo.
I think we should have a beautiful guest room...
Creo que deberíamos tener una hermosa habitación de invitados...
...with a mahogany sleigh bed and bedside tables with flowers on them.
...con una cama de caoba estilo trineo y mesitas de noche con flores.
Then we could have a rolltop desk with comment cards...
Luego podríamos tener un escritorio con tapa enrollable con tarjetas de comentarios...
...so people can tell us how much they love staying here.
...para que la gente nos diga cuánto le gusta quedarse aquí.
Whatever, you know, I really haven't thought about it that much.
Lo que sea, sabes, en realidad no lo he pensado mucho.
Well, I like that idea, obviously. Ha, ha.
Bueno, me gusta esa idea, obviamente. Ja, ja.
But I was thinking maybe it could be a game room, you know?
Pero estaba pensando que tal vez podría ser una sala de juegos, ¿sabes?
I mean, you can buy old arcade games...
O sea, puedes comprar máquinas de arcade viejas...
...like "Space Invaders" and "Asteroids" for $200.
...como "Space Invaders" y "Asteroids" por 200 dólares.
The real ones. The big, big, big ones.
Las de verdad. Las grandes, grandes, grandes.
No.
Okay, so you mean "no" as in, "Gee, Chandler, what an interesting idea.
Okay, entonces quieres decir "no" como en, "Ay, Chandler, qué idea tan interesante.
Let's discuss it before we reject it completely."
Vamos a discutirla antes de rechazarla por completo."
Oh. I'm sorry. Of course.
Oh. Lo siento. Por supuesto.
Yes. Interesting idea, um, talk about it, but no.
Sí. Idea interesante, eh, hablemos de ello, pero no.
So that's it?
¿Eso es todo?
Well, I just don't think that arcade games go in the beautiful guest room.
Bueno, es que no creo que las máquinas de arcade vayan en la hermosa habitación de invitados.
The guest room's gonna be filled with antiques.
La habitación de invitados va a estar llena de antigüedades.
Which is why "Asteroids" is perfect. It's the oldest game.
Por eso "Asteroids" es perfecto. Es el juego más antiguo.
What do you have against the guest room?
¿Qué tienes en contra de la habitación de invitados?
I don't have anything against the guest room.
No tengo nada en contra de la habitación de invitados.
Especially since everybody that we know lives about 30 seconds away.
Especialmente porque todos los que conocemos viven a unos 30 segundos.
Are you mocking me?
¿Te estoy tomando el pelo?
No, I'm not mocking you or your beautiful guest room.
No, no te estoy tomando el pelo ni a tu hermosa habitación de invitados.
What's up?
¿Qué pasa?
Nothing. Monica and I had a stupid fight.
Nada. Monica y yo tuvimos una pelea tonta.
But you're still moving in together, right? Because my ad came out today.
Pero todavía se van a mudar juntos, ¿verdad? Porque mi anuncio salió hoy.
"Wanted: Female roommate, nonsmoker, nonugly."
"Se busca: Compañera de piso, no fumadora, no fea."
- Nice. - Ah?
- Bien. - ¿Ah?
I figured after living with you...
Pensé que después de vivir contigo...
...it'd be an interesting change to have a female roommate.
...sería un cambio interesante tener una compañera de piso.
You know? Someone I could learn from. Someone who's different than me.
¿Sabes? Alguien de quien pudiera aprender. Alguien diferente a mí.
And what's more different than me, a guy who's not 19...
¿Y qué es más diferente que yo, un tipo que no tiene 19 años...
...than, say, a girl who is 19?
...que, digamos, una chica que tiene 19?
Ah? Ha, ha.
¿Ah? Ja, ja.
Not just a hat rack, my friend.
No solo un perchero, amigo mío.
- Pheebs, I have to ask you... - Shh. I'm swamped right now.
- Pheebs, tengo que preguntarte... - Shh. Estoy hasta arriba ahora mismo.
You're just staring into space.
Solo estás mirando al vacío.
Um, I'm trying to move that pencil.
Um, estoy intentando mover ese lápiz.
- This one? - It worked!
- ¿Este? - ¡Funcionó!
Pheebs, this whole apartment thing is a nightmare.
Pheebs, todo esto del apartamento es una pesadilla.
Every place that I can afford comes with a roommate who is a freak.
Cada lugar que puedo pagar viene con un compañero de piso que es un bicho raro.
Look at this.
Mira esto.
"Wanted: Female roommate, nonsmoker, nonugly."
"Se busca: Compañera de piso, no fumadora, no fea."
- It's just there's nothing. This city is full. - Wait, no, look at this.
- Es que no hay nada. Esta ciudad está llena. - Espera, no, mira esto.
"Two-bedroom, two-bath. Must be nonsmoker.
"Dos habitaciones, dos baños. No fumadores."
Satan worshipers okay."
Adoradores de Satán, vale."
Oh. Yeah, but it's on the ground floor.
Oh. Sí, pero está en la planta baja.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- Rach, are you still looking for a place? - Yeah, why?
- Rach, ¿sigues buscando piso? - Sí, ¿por qué?
Okay, there's this guy Warren from the museum...
Vale, hay un tal Warren del museo...
...and he's going on a dig for like two years.
...y se va de expedición como dos años.
And he's got this great place he needs to sublet.
Y tiene un piso genial que necesita subarrendar.
So you interested?
¿Te interesa?
That sounds great. I'd love to live at Warren's. I love Warren.
Suena genial. Me encantaría vivir en casa de Warren. Adoro a Warren.
- Thank you. - Oh, don't thank me.
- Gracias. - Oh, no me des las gracias.
You wanna thank someone, thank the volcano...
Si quieres dar las gracias a alguien, dáselas al volcán...
...that erupted thousands of years ago...
...que entró en erupción hace miles de años...
...killing but perfectly preserving an entire civilization.
...matando pero preservando perfectamente a toda una civilización.
Here's Warren's number.
Aquí tienes el número de Warren.
Oh, this is great. I am gonna call him right now.
Oh, esto es genial. Le voy a llamar ahora mismo.
- Oh, okay. Oh. - Thank you. Ha, ha.
- Oh, vale. Oh. - Gracias. Ja, ja.
Okay, you go call him.
Vale, tú llámale.
I saw it.
Lo vi.
I don't know what you're talking about.
No sé de qué hablas.
I'm talking about that which you already know but won't admit.
Hablo de eso que ya sabes pero no quieres admitir.
You know, that you love her again. You relove her.
Sabes, que la quieres otra vez. Que la quieres de nuevo.
Look, I do not relove her.
Mira, no la quiero de nuevo.
I can't believe you won't just admit it.
No puedo creer que no lo admitas.
Okay, just promise me that you won't do anything stupid.
Vale, solo prométeme que no harás nada estúpido.
Look, we're just friends now, okay? Why would I do anything stupid?
Mira, ahora solo somos amigos, ¿vale? ¿Por qué iba a hacer algo estúpido?
Ugh. Well, the apartment is already subletted.
Uf. Bueno, el piso ya está subarrendado.
I mean, this is just hopeless. I'm never gonna find anything.
Quiero decir, esto es desesperante. Nunca voy a encontrar nada.
You can live with me.
Puedes vivir conmigo.
- What? - What?
- ¿Qué? - ¿Qué?
What?
¿Qué?
- Oh, my God, are you serious? - Uh-huh.
- Dios mío, ¿hablas en serio? - Ajá.
I would love to live with you, Ross. That's great. Thank you.
Me encantaría vivir contigo, Ross. Es genial. Gracias.
I'm just glad I could, you know, help you out.
Solo me alegro de poder, ya sabes, ayudarte.
Wow, I'm so happy for you guys. This is so, so not stupid.
Vaya, me alegro tanto por vosotros. Esto es muy, muy poco estúpido.
Ross, Ross, you have no idea what this means to me.
Ross, Ross, no tienes ni idea de lo que esto significa para mí.
I mean, I was gonna be homeless. You've just saved me. You're my hero.
Quiero decir, iba a quedarme sin casa. Me has salvado. Eres mi héroe.
Hero? I don't know. Well, all right.
¿Héroe? No lo sé. Bueno, está bien.
Oh. I have to go tell Monica what a wonderful brother she has.
Oh. Tengo que ir a decirle a Monica qué hermano tan maravilloso tiene.
- Aw. Mwah. - Oh, please.
- Aw. Mwah. - Oh, por favor.
You're gonna say things now, aren't you?
Vas a decir cosas ahora, ¿verdad?
No. No, I won't.
No. No lo haré.
But I should tell you this.
Pero debería decirte esto.
This exact same thing happened to my roommate, Denise.
Exactamente lo mismo le pasó a mi compañera de piso, Denise.
She moved in with a guy...
Se mudó con un chico...
...who was secretly married to her and said he didn't love her but really did.
...que estaba secretamente casado con ella y dijo que no la quería pero en realidad sí.
It just blew up.
Todo explotó.
And that's how she ended up living with me.
Y así fue como terminó viviendo conmigo.
Okay, that's a lie.
Está bien, eso es mentira.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
Hi. Listen, I'm sorry about before. I don't need to have a game room.
Hola. Escucha, lamento lo de antes. No necesito tener una sala de juegos.
When I was a kid, I only played those games because I couldn't get girls.
Cuando era niño, solo jugaba a esos juegos porque no podía conseguir chicas.
Now I can get...
Ahora puedo conseguir...
Now I have you.
Ahora te tengo a ti.
No, not that I think that I have you...
No, no es que piense que te tengo...
...or think of you as property in any sort of way.
...o que te considere una propiedad de ninguna manera.
- I see women... - Stop it, Chandler.
- Veo mujeres... - Para, Chandler.
I'm sorry too.
Yo también lo siento.
- Really? - Yeah. Oh, yes.
- ¿En serio? - Sí. Oh, sí.
Oh.
Listen, we don't have to make that a guest room.
Mira, no tenemos que hacer de eso una habitación de invitados.
- We can think of something together. - That's a great idea.
- Podemos pensar en algo juntos. - Es una gran idea.
We can easily think of a way for us both to enjoy the room.
Podemos pensar fácilmente en una forma para que ambos disfrutemos de la habitación.
Totally.
Totalmente.
- We don't have to come up with this now. - Oh, good.
- No tenemos que decidir esto ahora. - Qué bien.
Why don't we think about changes that we can make in the living room?
¿Por qué no pensamos en cambios que podamos hacer en la sala de estar?
Changes?
¿Cambios?
Yeah, I mean, we're gonna have to move some furniture to make room for my chair.
Sí, quiero decir, tendremos que mover algunos muebles para hacer espacio para mi silla.
You're gonna bring the Barcalounger over here?
¿Vas a traer el Barcalounger aquí?
- Is that a problem? - Well...
- ¿Es un problema? - Bueno...
It's just that they're a set and they should probably stay together.
Es solo que son un juego y probablemente deberían quedarse juntos.
Oh, that's cool. Then I'll just bring them both over.
Oh, eso está bien. Entonces los traeré ambos.
See, now you're taking them away from their home.
Ves, ahora te los llevas de su hogar.
Okay, I get it. So I get nothing. Nothing here is mine. Everything is yours.
Está bien, lo entiendo. Entonces no obtengo nada. Nada de esto es mío. Todo es tuyo.
I'll get up in the morning, put on your clothes, and head off to work.
Me levantaré por la mañana, me pondré tu ropa y me iré a trabajar.
Yeah. Yeah, you know what? That's it. That's it.
Sí. Sí, ¿sabes qué? Eso es todo. Eso es todo.
Everything will be mine. Nothing will be yours.
Todo será mío. Nada será tuyo.
Oh, come on. I'm talking about the Barcalounger.
Oh, vamos. Estoy hablando del Barcalounger.
It doesn't match. Where is it gonna go?
No combina. ¿Dónde va a ir?
In the game room.
En la sala de juegos.
Look, it is not my fault that your chairs are incredibly ugly.
Mira, no es mi culpa que tus sillas sean increíblemente feas.
That's fine. I won't bring over the chairs. I won't bring anything over.
Está bien. No traeré las sillas. No traeré nada.
I wouldn't wanna ruin the ambiance over here at Grandma's place!
¡No querría arruinar el ambiente aquí en casa de la abuela!
Everything on your application looks really good.
Todo en tu solicitud se ve muy bien.
Oh, just one last question.
Oh, solo una última pregunta.
Are you and your friends gonna be over here all the time partying?
¿Tú y tus amigos van a estar aquí todo el tiempo de fiesta?
Oh, don't worry. I'm not really a party girl.
Oh, no te preocupes. Realmente no soy una chica de fiestas.
Whoa.
Now, don't just be blurting stuff out.
Ahora, no digas cosas a la ligera.
I want you to really think about your answers.
Quiero que pienses bien tus respuestas.
You can call off the roommate search. Hi. I'll be living here.
Puedes cancelar la búsqueda de compañero de piso. Hola. Yo viviré aquí.
Oh, don't listen to him.
Oh, no le hagas caso.
He's just some guy who wants the apartment.
Él es solo un tipo que quiere el apartamento.
But I don't think he's gonna get it.
Pero no creo que lo consiga.
Why did you take the shower curtain down?
¿Por qué bajaste la cortina de la ducha?
That thing was a hazard.
Esa cosa era un peligro.
I'm very safety-conscious.
Soy muy consciente de la seguridad.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Oh, I was just clearing some space for your stuff.
[ERROR API]
Oh, thanks.
Oh, gracias.
But listen, I was just at Monica's...
[ERROR API]
...and she and Chandler had a big fight and they're not moving in.
What do you mean, not moving in? They're still moving in, right?
[ERROR API]
No, no, they just had a big blowout over what to do with my room.
What? Over a stupid room?
[ERROR API]
I feel kind of bad for them...
...but I'm also psyched because I don't have to move in here.
[ERROR API]
Oh, no. Yeah. No, that part's great.
What's all this about you guys fighting?
[ERROR API]
Is this really over a room?
I mean, that is so silly.
[ERROR API]
- Ross, we can handle this. - Well, apparently not.
And I can't just stand by and watch two people I care about so much...
[ERROR API]
...be hurt by something that is so silly.
- I mean, enough of the silliness. - Why don't you tell her to stop being silly?
[ERROR API]
Okay, okay.
Está bien, está bien.
Two very good points.
[ERROR API]
Look, I've known you both a long time.
And I've never seen either of you one-millionth as happy...
[ERROR API]
...as you've been since you got together.
Do you really wanna throw that all away over a room?
[ERROR API]
That is so silly.
What's more important, love...
[ERROR API]
...or silliness?
Well, we are fond of the silliness.
[ERROR API]
But we also have a soft spot for the love.
- Love is the best medicine. - That's laughter.
[ERROR API]
- Why do you do it? - I don't know.
Now, Chandler, you wanna live with Monica, right?
[ERROR API]
Yeah, I do.
Sí, quiero.
And, Mon, you wanna live with Chandler, don't you?
[ERROR API]
Yes.
Sí.
Good. A verbal contract is binding in the state of New York.
[ERROR API]
So I understand you're looking for a place?
- No, no, I'm staying put. - Oh.
[ERROR API]
I was going to offer you my apartment.
Why? Where are you going?
[ERROR API]
I don't know.
No sé.
- Hey, Rach. - Hi.
[ERROR API]
Uh, you're never gonna believe it. Monica and Chandler are moving in again.
That's great news, right? I mean, for them, right?
[ERROR API]
Oh, wow.
But on the bright side, we get to be roommates again.
[ERROR API]
Yeah. You know, about that, um...
Ross, ahem, I really appreciate your offer to let me move in and everything...
[ERROR API]
...but don't you think it's gonna be weird?
Why? Why? Why would it...? Why would it be weird?
[ERROR API]
Well, you know, because of us.
Bueno, ya sabes, por nosotros.
Because of our history.
Por nuestra historia.
- No. - No?
- No. - ¿No?
No, no.
It would only be weird if we were still in that place.
Solo sería raro si todavía estuviéramos en esa situación.
I mean, are you still in that place?
O sea, ¿tú sigues en esa situación?
- No, not at all. - Good. Me neither.
- No, para nada. - Bien. Yo tampoco.
So it's not a problem.
Así que no es un problema.
We're just two friends who happen to be roommates.
Somos solo dos amigos que resulta que son compañeros de piso.
Okay, but, Ross, eventually, you and I are gonna be dating.
Está bien, pero, Ross, eventualmente, tú y yo vamos a salir.
Really? We are?
¿En serio? ¿Vamos a hacerlo?
Well, yeah. I'm gonna have a boyfriend and you're gonna have a girlfriend.
Bueno, sí. Yo voy a tener novio y tú vas a tener novia.
Oh. Heh.
Oh. Je.
That'd be great.
Sería genial.
But if you think it's gonna be okay, we'll just work out a system.
Pero si crees que va a estar bien, simplemente encontraremos un sistema.
It'll be like in college. I'll hang a hanger on the door and put a sign:
Será como en la universidad. Colgaré una percha en la puerta y pondré un cartel:
"Come back later. I'm getting lucky."
"Vuelve más tarde. Estoy teniendo suerte."
Yeah, I didn't think of that.
Sí, no había pensado en eso.
So are you sure about this whole moving-in thing?
Entonces, ¿estás seguro de esto de mudarse juntos?
I mean, it's a really big step. And what's the rush?
O sea, es un paso muy grande. ¿Y cuál es la prisa?
That's very funny.
Eso es muy gracioso.
He's being silly because he knows we enjoy the silliness.
Está siendo tonto porque sabe que disfrutamos de las tonterías.
No, I'm serious, okay? I mean, think about it.
No, hablo en serio, ¿vale? O sea, piénsalo.
You move in, you start fighting over stupid game rooms...
Te mudas, empiezan a pelear por habitaciones tontas...
...next thing you know, you break up.
...y al final, rompen.
Ross, you were right before. It was just a stupid fight about a room.
Ross, tenías razón antes. Fue solo una pelea tonta por una habitación.
Okay, there are no stupid fights.
Está bien, no hay peleas tontas.
This isn't about the room.
Esto no se trata de la habitación.
This is about what the room represents.
Esto se trata de lo que representa la habitación.
And unfortunately, this room could destroy you.
Y desafortunadamente, esta habitación podría destruirlos.
- Yeah, I'm not so worried. - Yeah, no, me neither.
- Sí, no estoy tan preocupada. - Sí, no, yo tampoco.
Fine. It's your life.
Bien. Es tu vida.
I just don't wanna see you break up.
Solo no quiero verte romper.
Which you will do if you move in together.
Lo cual harán si se mudan juntos.
But if that's what you want, there's nothing I can do.
Pero si eso es lo que quieres, no hay nada que pueda hacer.
Don't do it!
¡No lo hagan!
- You still wanna move in together, right? - Of course.
- Todavía quieren mudarse juntos, ¿verdad? - Por supuesto.
Ross didn't scare you?
¿Ross no te asustó?
Scared me out of ever wanting to live with him.
Me asustó de querer vivir con él alguna vez.
- Come here, I gotta show you something. - Okay.
- Ven aquí, tengo que mostrarte algo. - Vale.
Oh, my God, someone's killed Square Man.
Dios mío, alguien ha matado a Hombre Cuadrado.
This is where the Barcalounger could go.
Aquí es donde podría ir el Barcalounger.
You see, you can see the TV, and still, it's walking distance to the kitchen.
Verás, puedes ver la televisión, y aún así, está a poca distancia de la cocina.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Oh, eso es muy tierno.
I wanna show you something.
Quiero mostrarte algo.
You know those big road signs that say "merge"?
¿Conoces esas señales grandes de carretera que dicen "incorpórate"?
Mm-hm.
You know? So I was thinking we could get one of those signs...
¿Sabes? Estaba pensando que podríamos conseguir una de esas señales...
...and hang it over our bed.
...y colgarla sobre nuestra cama.
Because that's you and I together.
Porque eso somos tú y yo juntos.
"Merge."
"Fusionar."
- Oh, my God, I love that. - Really?
- Dios mío, me encanta eso. - ¿En serio?
"No."
I found you in my bed
Te encontré en mi cama
How'd you wind up there?
¿Cómo terminaste ahí?
You are a mystery
Eres un misterio
Little black curly hair
Pelito negro rizado
Little black, little black Little black, little black
Pelito negro, pelito negro, pelito negro, pelito negro
Little black curly hair
Pelito negro rizado
Thank you.
Gracias.
Um...
If you wanna receive e-mails about my upcoming shows...
Si quieres recibir correos sobre mis próximos shows...
...then please give me money so I can buy a computer.
...por favor, dame dinero para comprar una computadora.
So, uh... Ahem.
Entonces, eh... Ahem.
Where are the other guys?
¿Dónde están los otros chicos?
Well, let's see, Monica and Chandler are occupied.
Bueno, veamos, Monica y Chandler están ocupados.
- Fighting? - No, the other thing.
- ¿Peleando? - No, en lo otro.
I really think it's great they worked things out.
Realmente creo que es genial que hayan resuelto las cosas.
Yeah, there's no breaking them up, is there?
Sí, no hay quien los separe, ¿verdad?
Hey, can I borrow the key to your house so I can make a copy?
Oye, ¿me prestas la llave de tu casa para hacer una copia?
- Here. - Thank you.
Aquí. - Gracias.
Now, are you sure?
Ahora, ¿estás seguro?
Because once I make a copy, there's no turning back.
Porque una vez que haga una copia, no hay vuelta atrás.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Sí, estoy seguro.
Now get out of here before I change my mind.
Ahora sal de aquí antes de que cambie de opinión.
Uh, listen, Ross.
Uh, escucha, Ross.
You really think this moving in with Rachel is a good idea?
¿De verdad crees que esto de mudarse con Rachel es una buena idea?
I've been back and forth.
He estado pensándolo.
Yeah, well, maybe you should go back, okay?
Sí, bueno, quizás deberías volver a pensarlo, ¿ok?
Rachel moves in, and before you know it...
Rachel se muda, y antes de que te des cuenta...
...you're where you don't wanna be, back together.
...estarás donde no quieres estar, juntos de nuevo.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Sí, no creo.
She's already talking about, you know, dating other guys.
Ella ya está hablando de, ya sabes, salir con otros chicos.
That's not gonna work out.
Eso no va a funcionar.
Then she's gonna come home all weepy, and you'll be telling her:
Entonces ella volverá llorando, y tú le dirás:
"Oh, that's okay. You'll find someone."
"Oh, está bien. Encontrarás a alguien."
And then, bam, she finds you.
Y entonces, bam, te encuentra a ti.
Huh. Oh, maybe you're right.
Huh. Oh, quizás tengas razón.
I am telling you, Ross, she is definitely gonna fall in love with you again.
Te digo, Ross, ella definitivamente se va a enamorar de ti otra vez.
Now, is that what you want?
Ahora, ¿es eso lo que quieres?
- Heh. Is that what I want? - Yes.
- Heh. ¿Es eso lo que quiero? - Sí.
Here she comes. I'm gonna make your life much easier.
Ahí viene. Voy a hacer tu vida mucho más fácil.
All right, well, the place was closed, so I'll copy it later.
Está bien, bueno, el lugar estaba cerrado, así que lo copiaré más tarde.
Or not.
O no.
Uh, Rach, why don't you just move in with me?
Uh, Rach, ¿por qué no te mudas conmigo?
- Ahh. - Oh.
- Whoa, whoa, Joey. - No, no, no. It's okay.
- Whoa, whoa, Joey. - No, no, no. Está bien.
Look, Rach, I know I scared you off with that whole naked-Thursdays thing...
Mira, Rach, sé que te asusté con eso de los jueves desnudos...
...but we don't have to do that.
...pero no tenemos que hacer eso.
Well, it would be easier to move just right across the hall.
Bueno, sería más fácil mudarse justo al otro lado del pasillo.
Wait a minute, unless you're thinking about naked Wednesdays.
Espera un minuto, a menos que estés pensando en los miércoles de desnudos.
Thursday's clearly not good for you. Pick a day.
Los jueves claramente no te convienen. Escoge un día.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
Come on in. Thanks for coming back.
Pasa. Gracias por volver.
Okay, there have been a lot of people interested in the room.
Okay, ha habido mucha gente interesada en la habitación.
But I have narrowed it down, and you are one of the finalists.
Pero he reducido la lista y tú eres uno de los finalistas.
- Great. - Okay, now, before I make my decision...
- Genial. - Okay, ahora, antes de tomar mi decisión...
...I just wanna make sure that our personalities match, okay?
...solo quiero asegurarme de que nuestras personalidades encajen, ¿okay?
So I made up a little test.
Así que preparé una pequeña prueba.
Now, I'm gonna say a word, and then you say the first thing that comes to mind.
Ahora, yo diré una palabra y tú dirás lo primero que se te ocurra.
- I can do that. - Okay, here we go.
- Puedo hacer eso. - Okay, aquí vamos.
- Pillow. - Fight.
- Almohada. - Pelea.
Very good.
Muy bien.
Okay. G.
- String? - Excellent.
- ¿Cuerda? - Excelente.
Okay. Um...
Está bien. Um...
Doggy.
Perro.
- Kitten? - Ooh, sorry.
- ¿Gatito? - Ooh, lo siento.
No, no, no. So close, though. But, you know, okay, bye-bye.
No, no, no. Muy cerca, sin embargo. Pero, ya sabes, okay, adiós.