"We've got three minutes till the reactor blows.
[ERROR API]
We'll never make it!"
"You've got to get out of here! Save yourself!"
[ERROR API]
"No, I won't leave you."
"Don't worry about me. I'm a robot. I'm just a machine!"
[ERROR API]
- "No, you're not. Not to me." - Oh, my God.
- What? - I am extremely talented.
[ERROR API]
- Yeah. You're great. - Yeah.
- Okay, let's take it from... - No, I was really acting my ass off.
[ERROR API]
I thought I was pretty good too.
Yeah, you're solid. You're just no me.
[ERROR API]
You know what? I think that's enough for now.
I don't want to be over-rehearsed. Ha-ha-ha.
[ERROR API]
Fine. I'll do it without you!
I don't need you or anybody else!
[ERROR API]
I'm gonna make it on my own!
You'll see! You'll all see!
[ERROR API]
So, what's this thing you're auditioning for?
It's a new TV show. Yeah.
[ERROR API]
I'm up for the part of Mac, Machiavelli, or "Mac"!
I'm a detective and I solve crimes with the help of my robot partner.
[ERROR API]
He's a computerized, humanoid...
...electronically enhanced secret enforcer.
[ERROR API]
Or, "C.H.E.E.S.E."
- So, Mac and C.H.E.E.S. E? - That's the title!
[ERROR API]
They really lucked out that the initials spell "cheese."
That is lucky.
[ERROR API]
Huh. So, Joey, if you get this, you're gonna be, like...
...the star of your own TV show.
[ERROR API]
I mean, you'll be like the "Big Cheese" or the "Big Mac." Hey, you love those!
Don't get your hopes up, because it's probably not gonna happen.
[ERROR API]
Now, why would you say that, Joseph?
Well, I mean, come on, you guys. My own TV show?
[ERROR API]
- I don't know if I'm good enough. - I am. Heh.
What are you talking about? You're a terrific actor.
[ERROR API]
- You really think so? - How can you even ask that question?
- She's pretty. - Yeah. And she's really nice too.
[ERROR API]
She taught me all about, you know, how to work with cameras...
...and "smell the fart" acting.
[ERROR API]
- I'm sorry, what'd you say? - Excuse me?
It's like you got so many lines to learn so fast...
[ERROR API]
...that sometimes you need a minute to remember your next one.
So while you're thinking of it, you take this big pause where you look all intense.
[ERROR API]
You know, like this:
- Oh. - Okay.
[ERROR API]
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
¡Aquí está mi escena! ¡Aquí está mi escena!
Mrs. Wallace? I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray, your sister's neurosurgeon.
[ERROR API]
You sister is suffering from a...
Well, Eva, we've done some excellent work here.
[ERROR API]
And I would have to say, your problem is quite clear.
All you want is a dinkle
Todo lo que quieres es un dinkle
What you envy's a schwang
Lo que envidias es un schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
Algo con lo que puedas hacer pipí
Or play with or simply let hang
O jugar o simplemente dejarlo colgar
I play Al Pacino's butt.
Hago de trasero de Al Pacino.
All right? He goes into the shower and then, I'm his butt.
¿Todo bien? Él entra a la ducha y entonces, yo soy su trasero.
- Oh, my God. - Come on, you guys.
Ay, Dios mío. Anda, chicos.
This is a real movie and Al Pacino's in it, and that's big!
¡Esto es una película de verdad y Al Pacino está en ella, y eso es importante!
No, it's terrific. You deserve this after all your years of struggling...
No, es fantástico. Te lo mereces después de todos tus años de lucha...
...you've finally been able to crack your way into show business.
...finalmente has logrado abrirte camino en el mundo del espectáculo.
Okay, fine, make jokes. I don't care. This is a big break for me.
Está bien, haz chistes. No me importa. Esto es una gran oportunidad para mí.
- No, you're right, it is. - Yeah.
No, tienes razón, lo es. Sí.
So, you gonna invite us all to the big opening?
Entonces, ¿nos vas a invitar a todos a la gran inauguración?
All right, I'm out of here. Wish me luck.
Muy bien, me voy de aquí. Deséame suerte.
Good luck, good luck We all wish you good luck
Buena suerte, buena suerte. Todos te deseamos buena suerte.
Yeah, whatever.
Sí, lo que sea.
It's your turn.
Es tu turno.
Oh, are we playing this?
Oh, ¿estamos jugando a esto?
- Hey. - Hey. How did the audition go?
Hola. Hola. ¿Cómo fue la audición?
Terrible. I messed up every line. I shouldn't even be an actor.
Terrible. Me equivoqué en todas las líneas. Ni siquiera debería ser actor.
Wait. Are you doing that thing where you pretend it didn't go well...
Espera. ¿Estás haciendo eso de fingir que no fue bien...
...but it really did go well?
...pero en realidad fue bien?
- Yeah, did I fool you? - Totally!
Sí, ¿te engañé? ¡Totalmente!
- So, it did go well? - It went amazingly well!
Entonces, ¿sí fue bien? ¡Fue increíblemente bien!
- Great. - That's great.
Genial. Eso es genial.
- It's down to me and two other guys. - Oh, my God.
Depende de mí y de otros dos tipos. Dios mío.
I know both of them, and they're really good.
Los conozco a ambos y son muy buenos.
One's from those allergy commercials who's always being chased...
Uno es de esos comerciales de alergias que siempre lo persiguen...
...by those big flowers. - Oh, I love that guy.
...esas flores grandes. Me encanta ese tipo.
Oh. What are you doing?
Oh. ¿Qué estás haciendo?
What am I doing?
¿Qué estoy haciendo?
I'm so nervous, you know? The callback isn't till tomorrow at 5.
Estoy tan nervioso, ¿sabes? La siguiente audición no es hasta mañana a las 5.
I feel like my head's gonna explode.
Siento que me va a explotar la cabeza.
Well, it is overdue.
Bueno, ya era hora.
Don't worry, okay? You're gonna be fine.
No te preocupes, ¿vale? Vas a estar bien.
Yeah, but it's so much pressure.
Sí, pero es mucha presión.
No offense, but what you guys all do is very different.
Sin ofender, pero lo que ustedes hacen es muy diferente.
I don't know if you'd understand.
No sé si entenderías.
Yeah, none of the rest of us have to deal with pressure at our jobs.
Sí, ninguno de nosotros tiene que lidiar con presión en nuestros trabajos.
Yes, I know what time it is...
Sí, sé qué hora es...
...but I'm looking at the WENIS and I'm not happy.
...pero estoy mirando el WENIS y no estoy contento.
Well, I'm tearing the lettuce.
Bueno, estoy cortando la lechuga.
- Uh-huh? Is it dirty? - No, don't worry, I'm gonna wash it.
¿Ajá? ¿Está sucia? No, no te preocupes, la voy a lavar.
Don't. I like it dirty.
No lo hagas. Me gusta sucia.
That's your call.
Tú decides.
So, uh, what are you going to do next?
Entonces, eh, ¿qué vas a hacer ahora?
Well, I thought that I would cut up the tomatoes.
Bueno, pensé que cortaría los tomates.
Are they firm?
¿Están firmes?
They're all right.
Están bien.
You sure they haven't gone bad? You sure they're not very, very bad?
¿Seguro que no se han echado a perder? ¿Seguro que no están muy, muy mal?
No, really. They're okay.
No, en serio. Están bien.
You gonna slice them up real nice?
¿Vas a cortarlos bien?
Ahem. Actually, I was gonna do them julienne.
Ejem. En realidad, iba a cortarlas en juliana.
I'm out of here.
Me largo de aquí.
Monica, I'm quitting. I just helped an 81 -year-old woman put on a thong...
Monica, renuncio. Acabo de ayudar a una mujer de 81 años a ponerse un calzón...
...and she didn't even buy it.
...y ni siquiera lo compró.
I'm quitting. That's it. I'm talking to my boss right now.
Renuncio. Eso es todo. Voy a hablar con mi jefe ahora mismo.
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
Sí, lo hago. Sí, lo hago.
Okay, bye. Call me when you get this message.
Okay, adiós. Llámame cuando recibas este mensaje.
Well, what happened?
Bueno, ¿qué pasó?
Well, he came in for a massage, and everything was fine until...
Bueno, vino a un masaje, y todo estaba bien hasta...
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
And all of a sudden, his hands weren't the problem anymore.
Y de repente, sus manos ya no eran el problema.
- Was it? - Oh, Boy Scouts could've camped under there.
- ¿Sí? - Dios mío, ahí cabía una tropa de Boy Scouts.
You ate my sandwich.
Te comiste mi sándwich.
It was a simple mistake. It could happen to anyone.
Fue un error simple. Le podría pasar a cualquiera.
Oh, really?
¿Ah, sí?
Now calm down.
Ahora cálmate.
Come look in my office. Some of it may still be in the trash.
Ven a ver mi oficina. Quizás todavía quede algo en la basura.
- What? - Well, it was quite large.
- ¿Qué? - Bueno, era bastante grande.
I had to throw most of it away.
Tuve que tirar la mayor parte.
You threw my sandwich away?
¿Tiraste mi sándwich?
My sandwich?
¿Mi sándwich?
My sandwich!
¡Mi sándwich!
It's just, I want this part so much, you know?
Es solo que quiero mucho este papel, ¿sabes?
If I don't get this part, I'm never gonna eat macaroni and cheese again.
Si no consigo este papel, ¡nunca más volveré a comer macarrones con queso!
No, I didn't say that. That doesn't count.
No, no dije eso. Eso no cuenta.
Come on, guys. It's not like I moved to Europe.
Vamos, chicos. No es como si me hubiera mudado a Europa.
I just moved across the hall.
Solo me mudé al otro lado del pasillo.
And we would have you over all the time...
Y te invitaríamos todo el tiempo...
...if it weren't for Monica's allergies.
...si no fuera por las alergias de Monica.
You're right, I could never lie to you.
Tienes razón, nunca podría mentirte.
She hates you.
Ella te odia.
Should I get that? Ha-ha-ha.
¿Contesto? Jajajaja.
Hello? Uh, no, Joey's not here right now.
¿Hola? Uh, no, Joey no está aquí ahora mismo.
Can I take a message?
¿Puedo tomar un mensaje?
Yeah, okay. So the audition's been moved from 5 to 2:30?
Sí, está bien. Entonces, ¿la audición se movió de las 5 a las 2:30?
Okay, great. Bye.
Okay, genial. Adiós.
- Aren't you dressed yet? - Am I naked again?
- ¿Todavía no estás vestida? - ¿Estoy desnuda otra vez?
We're supposed to meet my parents in 15 minutes.
Tenemos que encontrarnos con mis padres en 15 minutos.
Okay. I was just talking to the guys. Just look at them.
Está bien. Estaba hablando con los chicos. Solo míralos.
I mean, is it okay if they come visit?
Quiero decir, ¿está bien si vienen de visita?
What about my allergies?
¿Qué pasa con mis alergias?
Right. Your allergies.
Cierto. Tus alergias.
All her. She hates you.
Todo de ella. Ella te odia.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Yes! All right.
¡Sí! ¡Genial!
How cool would it be if you could watch like a real life-size version of this?
¿Qué tan genial sería si pudieras ver una versión real a tamaño natural de esto?
- I mean, how crazy would that be? - As crazy as soccer?
- ¿Quiero decir, qué tan loco sería eso? - ¿Tan loco como el fútbol?
Hello?
¿Hola?
What are you talking about? The audition's not till 5.
¿De qué hablas? La audición es hasta las 5.
Well, nobody told me.
Bueno, nadie me lo dijo.
Who'd you talk to?
¿Con quién hablaste?
Never mind.
Olvídalo.
You mean you didn't get it from this?
¿Quieres decir que no lo obtuviste de esto?
The allergy guy got the part. Thanks.
El tipo de las alergias consiguió el papel. Gracias.
Maybe we can fix it, you know?
Quizás podamos arreglarlo, ¿sabes?
Maybe we can send him some big, big flowers and scare him!
¡Quizás podamos enviarle unas flores enormes y asustarlo!
How could you do this to me?
¿Cómo pudiste hacerme esto?
This part could've turned my whole career around.
Este papel podría haber cambiado mi carrera por completo.
I messed up, okay? I'm sorry. I really messed up.
La regué, ¿de acuerdo? Lo siento. Realmente la regué.
You don't even live here anymore. Why'd you answer my phone?
Ya ni siquiera vives aquí. ¿Por qué contestaste mi teléfono?
- I have a machine! - Which I bought for you.
- ¡Tengo un contestador! - Que te compré.
Taught you how to use it. You thought it was a copier.
Te enseñé a usarlo. Pensaste que era una fotocopiadora.
If there was anything I could do, I would do it, okay?
Si hubiera algo que pudiera hacer, lo haría, ¿de acuerdo?
But everybody's allowed one mistake, right?
Pero todo el mundo comete un error, ¿verdad?
He could have gotten me a VCR. He could have gotten me golf clubs.
Podría haberme conseguido un VCR. Podría haberme conseguido palos de golf.
But no, he has to get me the "woman repeller."
Pero no, tiene que darme el "repelente de mujeres".
The eyesore from the "Liberace House of Crap!"
¡El espanto de la "Casa de Basura de Liberace"!
- It's not that bad. - Easy for you to say.
- No es tan malo. - Fácil para ti decirlo.
You don't have to sport a reject from the "Mr. T Collection."
No tienes que lucir un rechazo de la "Colección Mr. T".
Chandler. Chandler.
I pity the fool who puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!
¡Me da lástima el tonto que se pone mis joyas! ¡Sí! ¡Sí!
I pity the fool that...
Me da lástima el tonto que...
Hi...
Hola...
When you were late last night, Kathy and I got to talking...
Cuando te retrasaste anoche, Kathy y yo nos pusimos a hablar...
...and one thing led to another and...
...y una cosa llevó a la otra y...
And what? Did you sleep with her?
¿Y qué? ¿Dormiste con ella?
- No! No, I just kissed her. - What? That's even worse!
- ¡No! No, solo la besé. - ¿Qué? ¡Eso es aún peor!
- How is that worse? - I don't know! But it's the same!
- ¿Cómo es peor? - ¡No sé! ¡Pero es lo mismo!
You're right, I have no excuses. I was totally over the line.
Tienes razón, no tengo excusas. Me pasé totalmente de la raya.
"Over the line?"
"¿Pasado de la raya?"
You're so far past the line that you can't even see the line!
Estás tan lejos de la raya que ni siquiera puedes ver la raya.
Yeah, the line is a dot to you!
¡Sí, la raya es un punto para ti!
I'm not saying that you should magically forgive me.
No digo que debas perdonarme mágicamente.
But you're not perfect. You've made some errors in judgment too.
Pero tú tampoco eres perfecto. Tú también has cometido algunos errores de juicio.
Name one.
Nombra uno.
What happened?
¿Qué pasó?
Aw, man! He promised he wouldn't take the chairs!
¡Ay, hombre! ¡Prometió que no se llevaría las sillas!
What the hell happened? How were you locked in?
¿Qué demonios pasó? ¿Cómo te quedaste encerrado?
And where the hell's all of our stuff?
¿Y dónde demonios está todas nuestras cosas?
This guy came by to look at the unit...
Este tipo vino a ver la unidad...
...and he said he didn't think it was big enough to fit a grown man.
...y dijo que no creía que fuera lo suficientemente grande para un hombre adulto.
So you got in voluntarily?
¿Así que entraste voluntariamente?
I was trying to make a sale!
¡Estaba intentando hacer una venta!
Oh, man, if I ever run into that guy again, you know what I'm gonna do?
Oh, hombre, si vuelvo a encontrar a ese tipo, ¿sabes lo que voy a hacer?
Bend over?
¿Doblarte?
There's Lorraine.
Ahí está Lorraine.
Okay, now remember, no trading. You get the pretty one, I get the mess.
Está bien, ahora recuerda, nada de intercambios. Tú te quedas con la bonita, yo me quedo con el desastre.
- Hi, Joey. - Hey.
- Hola, Joey. - Hola.
Well, well. Look what you brought.
Vaya, vaya. Mira lo que trajiste.
And what did you bring?
¿Y tú qué trajiste?
She's checking her coat.
Está dejando su abrigo.
Joey, I'm gonna go wash the cab smell off my hands.
Joey, voy a lavarme el olor a taxi de las manos.
Will you get me a white Zinfandel and a glass of red for Janice?
¿Me podrías traer un Zinfandel blanco y una copa de tinto para Janice?
Janice?
¿Janice?
Oh, my God!
¡Oh, Dios mío!
Joey's tailor took advantage of me.
El sastre de Joey se aprovechó de mí.
What?
¿Qué?
No way. I've been going to the guy for 12 years.
No puede ser. He ido con él por 12 años.
He said he was gonna do my inseam...
Dijo que me iba a arreglar el tiro...
...then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite...
...luego me subió la mano por la pierna y entonces hubo un claro...
What?
¿Qué?
Cupping.
Manoseo.
That's how they do pants!
¡Así es como arreglan los pantalones!
Ross, will you tell him?
Ross, ¿le dices tú?
- Isn't that how a tailor measures pants? - Yes, yes, it is. In prison!
- ¿No es así como un sastre mide los pantalones? - Sí, sí, lo es. ¡En la cárcel!
I said name one!
¡Dije que nombrara uno!
- I can't believe I did this. What an idiot. - Stop beating yourself up.
- No puedo creer que hice esto. Qué idiota. - Deja de culparte.
People make mistakes. These things happen.
La gente comete errores. Estas cosas pasan.
There aren't any messages you've forgotten to give me, are there?
No hay ningún mensaje que hayas olvidado darme, ¿verdad?
Apparently, you're not very good at it.
Aparentemente, no eres muy bueno en eso.
- Do you think he'll ever forgive me? - Of course he will.
- ¿Crees que me perdone alguna vez? - Claro que sí.
Chandler, the most important thing is that you forgive yourself.
Chandler, lo más importante es que te perdones a ti mismo.
- You know what, I kind of have. - Already?
- ¿Sabes qué? Como que lo hice. - ¿Ya?
That was pretty bad, what you did.
Eso fue bastante malo, lo que hiciste.
You know what? He will forgive you.
¿Sabes qué? Él te perdonará.
I like to bring a pad with me when I go answer the phone, just in case. Okay.
Me gusta llevar una libreta cuando voy a contestar el teléfono, por si acaso. ¿De acuerdo?
You didn't see how mad he was, you know?
No viste lo enojado que estaba, ¿sabes?
I'm sure he will forgive you.
Estoy seguro de que te perdonará.
Look, we've all been there, you know? You fight, you make up.
Mira, todos hemos pasado por eso, ¿sabes? Se pelean, se reconcilian.
That's the way it works.
Así es como funciona.
It took two people to break up this relationship!
¡Se necesitaron dos personas para romper esta relación!
Yeah! You and that girl from the copy place...
¡Sí! Tú y esa chica de la copistería...
...which yesterday you took full responsibility for!
...¡de la que ayer asumiste toda la responsabilidad!
I didn't know what I was taking responsibility for, okay?
No sabía de qué me estaba haciendo responsable, ¿de acuerdo?
I didn't finish the whole letter.
No terminé la carta completa.
- What? - I fell asleep.
- ¿Qué? - Me quedé dormida.
You fell asleep?
¿Te quedaste dormida?
It was 5:30 in the morning.
Eran las 5:30 de la mañana.
And you had rambled on for 18 pages.
Y habías divagado por 18 páginas.
Front and back!
¡Por delante y por detrás!
And by the way? Y-O-U, apostrophe R-E means, "you are."
Y por cierto, T-U-Y-O, apóstrofe S significa "tuyo".
Y-O-U-R means "your."
T-U-Y-O significa "tu".
I can't believe I thought of getting back together with you.
No puedo creer que pensara en volver contigo.
We are so over!
¡Hemos terminado!
Fine by me!
¡Me parece bien!
And just so you know, it's not that common...
Y para que lo sepas, no es tan común...
...it doesn't happen to every guy, and it is a big deal!
...no le pasa a todos los chicos, ¡y es algo importante!
I knew it!
¡Lo sabía!
- You had no right to go out with him. - That is the most ridiculous...
- No tenías derecho a salir con él. - Eso es lo más ridículo...
- You sold me out! - I did not sell you out!
- ¡Me vendiste! - ¡No te vendí!
- Yes, you did! You absolutely sold me... - Would you let me talk?
- ¡Sí, lo hiciste! Absolutamente me vendiste... - ¿Me dejas hablar?
Did you just flick me?
¿Me acabas de pellizcar?
Okay, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was just... Ow!
Okay, bueno, no me dejaste terminar y solo estaba... ¡Ay!
- Stop it! Ow! - Ow!
- ¡Para! ¡Ay! - ¡Ay!
- Stop. - Stop.
- Para. - Para.
- All right. No, let's not do this. - No!
- Está bien. No, no hagamos esto. - ¡No!
- Happy thoughts. - No!
- Pensamientos felices. - ¡No!
- Stop it! - Oh! Oh!
- ¡Para! - ¡Oh! ¡Oh!
Okay, now I'm gonna kick some ass!
Okay, ¡ahora voy a patear traseros!
- Ow! - Ow!
- ¡Ay! - ¡Ay!
- Ow. Ow. Ow. - I know, I know.
- Ay. Ay. Ay. - Lo sé, lo sé.
All right. Now, I will let go if you both stop.
Está bien. Ahora, soltaré si ambos paran.
- Fine. - Fine.
- Vale. - Vale.
There we go.
Ahí está.
Ha. You know what? If we were in prison, you guys would be like my bitches.
Ja. ¿Saben qué? Si estuviéramos en prisión, ustedes serían como mis perritas.
Okay, buddy boy, here it is.
Okay, amiguito, aquí tienes.
You hide my clothes? I'm wearing everything you own.
¿Me escondes mi ropa? Llevo puesto todo lo tuyo.
Oh, my God!
¡Oh, Dios mío!
Look at me, I'm Chandler! Could I be wearing any more clothes?
¡Mírame, soy Chandler! ¿Podría estar usando más ropa?
Maybe if I wasn't going "commando."
Quizás si no estuviera "sin ropa interior".
Whew. I tell you, it's hot with all this stuff on. I'd better not do any lunges.
Uf. Te digo, hace calor con todo esto puesto. Mejor no hago ninguna sentadilla.
Joey?
¿Joey?
Got you the Joey special. Two pizzas!
Te conseguí la especialidad de Joey. ¡Dos pizzas!
Joe?
¿Joey?
Hello? Damn it!
¿Hola? ¡Maldición!
Hello?
¿Hola?
No, Joey's not here right now, but I can take a message. I think.
No, Joey no está aquí ahora mismo, pero puedo tomar un mensaje. Creo.
He's still got a chance for the part? That's great news!
¿Todavía tiene una oportunidad para el papel? ¡Qué gran noticia!
Well, no, obviously not for the actor who was mauled by his dog.
Bueno, no, obviamente no para el actor que fue destrozado por su perro.
Well, that's great. I will give Joey the message. Thank you.
Bueno, eso es genial. Le daré el mensaje a Joey. Gracias.
Yes!
¡Sí!
Okay.
Mac...
...audition...
...audición...
...at 2.
...a las 2.
Allergy...
Alergia...
...actor...
...attacked.
...atacado.
By dog...
Por perro...
...not...
...no...
...flowers.
...flores.
- Hey. - Please tell me you got the message.
- Hola. - Por favor, dime que recibiste el mensaje.
- What message? - The actor playing Mac couldn't do it.
- ¿Qué mensaje? - El actor que interpreta a Mac no pudo hacerlo.
- They needed to see you at 2:00. - What? It's 6:00!
- Te necesitaban ver a las 2:00. - ¿Qué? ¡Son las 6:00!
Look! I wrote it! I wrote it on the board!
¡Mira! ¡Lo escribí! ¡Lo escribí en la pizarra!
I wrote it on the board, then went looking all over for you!
Lo escribí en la pizarra y luego te busqué por todas partes.
I went to Ross's, the coffee house.
Fui a lo de Ross, a la cafetería.
I went to any place that they make sandwiches!
¡Fui a cualquier lugar donde hagan sándwiches!
- I can't believe this, Chandler! - I'm sorry.
- ¡No puedo creer esto, Chandler! - Lo siento.
I don't know what to say!
¡No sé qué decir!
You might say, "Congratulations."
Podrías decir: "Felicidades".
I saw the board, I went to the audition, I got the part!
¡Vi el tablero, fui a la audición, conseguí el papel!
Was that supposed to be funny? I was worried over here.
¿Se suponía que eso era gracioso? Estaba preocupado.
- I'm sorry. - At times that fake-out thing is mean.
- Lo siento. - A veces esa broma de engaño es cruel.
Okay, man. I'm sorry. I did not mean to make you feel bad.
Está bien, amigo. Lo siento. No quise hacerte sentir mal.
Well, that's good.
Bueno, eso es bueno.
Because you didn't. And I'm incredibly happy for you!
¡Porque no lo hiciste! ¡Y estoy increíblemente feliz por ti!
That's mean!
¡Eso es cruel!
- You had me going there! - We could do this all day.
- ¡Me engañaste! - Podemos hacer esto todo el día.
Yeah, you're right.
Sí, tienes razón.
Look, let's talk about what a huge star I'm gonna be.
Mira, hablemos de la gran estrella que voy a ser.
You are gonna be a huge star. I'm gonna hug you.
Vas a ser una gran estrella. Voy a abrazarte.
- You hug me. - All right.
- Tú me abrazas. - De acuerdo.
- Do we do this too much? - I think so.
- ¿Hacemos esto demasiado? - Creo que sí.
- Yeah. Get off me. - Yeah.
- Sí. Quítate de encima. - Sí.
"Come on, C.H.E.E.S.E., I'm not leaving without you.
"Vamos, C.H.E.E.S.E., no me voy sin ti."
Try routing your backup power source through your primary CPU."
"Intenta dirigir tu fuente de energía de respaldo a través de tu CPU principal."
"I can't! My circuits are fried! They're fried, I tell you!"
"¡No puedo! ¡Mis circuitos están fritos! ¡Están fritos, se los digo!"
Wow.
Guau.
"Well, then I'll just have to carry you."
"Bueno, entonces tendré que cargarte."
"That'll be a neat trick...
"Eso será un truco genial..."
...when you're dead!"
"...¡cuando estés muerto!"
Ross, you don't have to yell.
Ross, no tienes que gritar.
There was just an explosion, okay? My hearing would be impaired.
Solo hubo una explosión, ¿de acuerdo? Mi audición estaría afectada.
I thought you were excellent.
Pensé que fuiste excelente.
In fact, for a minute there, I was like, "Ooh, where did Ross go?"
De hecho, por un minuto pensé: "Ooh, ¿a dónde se fue Ross?"
Thank you. And I have to say that first scene where you meet Mac...
Gracias. Y tengo que decir que esa primera escena donde conoces a Mac...
- Yeah. - Oh, my God. I mean...
- Sí. - Dios mío. Quiero decir...
You know what?
¿Sabes qué?
I think that's enough for today. Thanks for your help.
Creo que es suficiente por hoy. Gracias por tu ayuda.
- Holding us back. - Totally.
- Nos detienen. - Totalmente.