Hey, remember when I had a monkey?
[ERROR API]
- Yeah. Mm-hm.
Yeah. What was I thinking?
[ERROR API]
Hey, so, what's with the 20 percent tip? Did I do something wrong?
Twenty percent is a pretty generous tip.
[ERROR API]
You know what's more generous than that? Fifty percent.
- You know what's even more generous? - I see where you're going.
[ERROR API]
- What's up with the greed, Joe? - All right, look, I'm sorry, you guys.
It's just that I gotta get these new headshots made...
[ERROR API]
...and they're really expensive, you know.
I'm down to like three.
[ERROR API]
Actually, two, because one of them I kind of blackened in some teeth.
Why'd I do that? Ugh.
[ERROR API]
Well, isn't there something you can do to earn a little extra money?
I mean, can't you pick up, I don't know, an extra shift here?
[ERROR API]
Or, you know, I used to beg for money.
Of course, it helps if you've got, you know, a little of this going on.
[ERROR API]
- Wow, I still have it. Ha, ha. - Yeah.
Wait, don't you have an audition today? Yeah. Maybe you'll get that job.
[ERROR API]
Oh, ha-ha-ha.
Oh, wait a minute.
[ERROR API]
I used to get medical experiments done on me all the time.
Ah, finally, an explanation.
[ERROR API]
No, I used to get paid for all kinds of medical stuff, remember?
Let's see. Uh... Well, I don't wanna donate sperm again.
[ERROR API]
I really prefer doing that at the home office, you know?
Ooh, ooh, maybe they want some of my blood or spit or something, huh?
[ERROR API]
- Joey. - Yeah?
What did I tell you about talking to your friends while you're working?
[ERROR API]
Uh, do it?
That guy's been waiting for his coffee for 10 minutes.
[ERROR API]
He's complained about you three times.
Now, where was I?
[ERROR API]
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- Hey, what have you been up to? - Oh. We went to a self-defense class today.
[ERROR API]
Wow.
Guau.
Yeah. Kicking a guy in the crotch all morning really takes it out of you.
[ERROR API]
Takes it out of you? Heh.
- No, now we can kick anybody's ass. - Yeah.
[ERROR API]
After one class? I don't think so.
What, you wanna see me self-defend myself?
[ERROR API]
Go over there and pretend you're a sexual predator.
Go on, I dare you.
[ERROR API]
Of course you can defend yourself from an attack you know is coming.
That's not enough.
[ERROR API]
Look, I studied karate for a long time.
And there's a concept you should really be familiar with.
[ERROR API]
It's what the Japanese call unagi.
Isn't that a kind of sushi?
[ERROR API]
- No, it's a concept. - Yeah, it is, it is. It's freshwater eel.
All right, maybe it means that too.
Está bien, tal vez signifique eso también.
Oh, I would kill for a salmon-skin roll right now.
Oh, mataría por un rollo de piel de salmón ahora mismo.
You know what? Fine, get attacked. I don't even care.
¿Sabes qué? Bien, que te ataquen. Ni siquiera me importa.
Come on, Ross, we're sorry. Please tell us what it is.
Vamos, Ross, lo sentimos. Por favor, dinos qué es.
Unagi is a state of total awareness.
Unagi es un estado de conciencia total.
Okay? Only by achieving true unagi...
¿Ok? Solo alcanzando el verdadero unagi...
...can you be prepared for any danger that may befall you.
...puedes estar preparado para cualquier peligro que te aceche.
In case someone's trying to steal your bamboo sleeping mat...
En caso de que alguien intente robar tu esterilla de bambú para dormir...
...or your kettle of fish?
...¿o tu tetera de pescado?
All I'm saying is, it's one thing being prepared...
Lo único que digo es que una cosa es estar preparado...
...for an attack against, like, each other.
...para un ataque contra, como, el uno al otro.
Whole other story being prepared for an attack, I don't know...
Es otra historia estar preparado para un ataque, no sé...
A surprise!
¡Una sorpresa!
All right, you knew that was coming, but that doesn't mean you have unagi.
Está bien, sabías que eso venía, pero eso no significa que tengas unagi.
Ooh, if we made reservations, we could have unagi in about a half-hour.
Ooh, si hiciéramos reservaciones, podríamos tener unagi en como media hora.
You know what?
¿Sabes qué?
- Hey, hey, is Monica here? - No.
- Oye, oye, ¿está Mónica aquí? - No.
Okay, look, I need your help. I don't know what to get for Valentine's Day.
Ok, mira, necesito tu ayuda. No sé qué comprar para el Día de San Valentín.
Well, Valentine's Day was two weeks ago, so I wouldn't get her a calendar.
Bueno, el Día de San Valentín fue hace dos semanas, así que no le regalaría un calendario.
Heh. She was working on Valentine's Day, so we're celebrating it tonight.
Ella estaba trabajando el Día de San Valentín, así que lo celebramos esta noche.
Oh, hey, why don't you book a day for both of you at one of those romantic spas?
Oh, oye, ¿por qué no reservas un día para ambos en uno de esos spas románticos?
Ooh, Joey, that's actually a really good idea.
Ooh, Joey, esa es en realidad una muy buena idea.
Yeah, and of course, crotchless panties.
Sí, y por supuesto, bragas sin entrepierna.
Well, as appealing as that does sound to her boyfriend...
Bueno, tan atractivo como eso le suena a su novio...
...and her brother...
...y a su hermano...
...I can't. We promised we'd make each other gifts this year.
...no puedo. Prometimos hacernos regalos mutuamente este año.
- Oh, I love that. - You guys.
- Oh, me encanta eso. - Ustedes.
You can't make crotchless panties? You take...
¿No puedes hacer bragas sin entrepierna? Tomas...
- You take a pair of scissors and just cut... - Okay, okay, okay.
- Tomas un par de tijeras y solo cortas... - Ok, ok, ok.
So making things, that sounds so much fun.
Así que hacer cosas, eso suena muy divertido.
I thought so too, until I papier-mâchéd one of my eyes shut.
Yo también lo pensé, hasta que me pegué un ojo con papel maché.
I love papier-mâché. What did you make?
Me encanta el papel maché. ¿Qué hiciste?
I made a:
Hice un:
- What is that? - Nothing.
- ¿Qué es eso? - Nada.
Oh.
So, what are you gonna do?
Entonces, ¿qué vas a hacer?
Have you guys made anything that I could take credit for?
¿Han hecho algo de lo que yo pueda llevarme el mérito?
Ooh, I have, I have. I started making these little sock bunnies.
Ooh, sí, sí. Empecé a hacer estos pequeños conejitos de calcetín.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Oh, por el amor de Dios.
Hey, wait a minute. That is my sock.
Oye, espera un minuto. Ese es mi calcetín.
Now it's your little bunny friend.
Ahora es tu pequeño amigo conejo.
Okay.
This actually is a:
Esto en realidad es un:
- Hey. - Hey, honey.
- Oye. - Hola, cariño.
Can I ask you a question about the Valentine's Day gifts?
¿Puedo hacerte una pregunta sobre los regalos del Día de San Valentín?
- Oh, yeah. - Do we have to make the entire thing?
- Oh, sí. - ¿Tenemos que hacer la cosa entera?
Yes. Why, did you forget to make yours?
Sí. ¿Por qué, olvidaste hacer el tuyo?
Of course not.
Por supuesto que no.
I just have to, uh, go over to the place where I made it and pick it up.
Solo tengo que, eh, ir al lugar donde lo hice y recogerlo.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Vale. - Vale.
I can't wait. It's gonna be the best Valentine's Day ever.
No puedo esperar. ¡Será el mejor Día de San Valentín de la historia!
I can't believe it. Make the presents. Make the presents.
No puedo creerlo. Haz los regalos. Haz los regalos.
- What? - Just so excited to make the presents!
- ¿Qué? - ¡Solo estoy emocionado de hacer los regalos!
Shoot.
Maldición.
Hi, I'm Joey Tribbiani.
Hola, soy Joey Tribbiani.
And with all due respect, I'd like to donate some fluids.
Y con el debido respeto, me gustaría donar algunos fluidos.
We're at the end of one of our research cycles...
Estamos al final de uno de nuestros ciclos de investigación...
...so we're not looking for applicants now.
...así que no estamos buscando solicitantes ahora.
That's too bad. I've kind of been saving up.
Qué lástima. He estado ahorrando.
Uh, you sure there's no studies I can participate in?
Uh, ¿estás seguro de que no hay estudios en los que pueda participar?
Well, here's a schedule of what's coming up.
Bueno, aquí tienes un horario de lo que viene.
Ah, thanks.
Ah, gracias.
Oh, but this one starts now.
Oh, pero este empieza ahora.
That one is available now, but only identical twins are eligible.
Ese está disponible ahora, pero solo los gemelos idénticos son elegibles.
- It's a twin study. - But it's $2000.
- Es un estudio de gemelos. - Pero son $2000.
- Sorry. - Oh.
- Perdón. - Oh.
Well, how about this one?
Bueno, ¿qué tal este?
"Testing the Effects of Joey Tribbiani on Attractive Nurse Receptionists."
"Probando los efectos de Joey Tribbiani en atractivas recepcionistas de enfermería."
We already got the results back on that one, and they're not good.
Ya obtuvimos los resultados de ese y no son buenos.
- That was good. - Wasn't that a blast?
- Eso estuvo bien. - ¿No fue genial?
- Danger! Danger! - God, Ross!
- ¡Peligro! ¡Peligro! - ¡Dios mío, Ross!
What the hell was that?
¿Qué demonios fue eso?
A lesson in the importance of unagi.
Una lección sobre la importancia del unagi.
You're a freak.
Eres un bicho raro.
Perhaps.
Quizás.
Now, I'm curious.
Ahora, tengo curiosidad.
At what point during those girlish screams would you have begun to kick my ass?
¿En qué momento durante esos gritos de niña habrías empezado a patearme el trasero?
All right, so we weren't prepared.
Está bien, así que no estábamos preparados.
I'm sorry I had to take such drastic measures to make my point.
Lamento haber tenido que tomar medidas tan drásticas para dar mi punto.
But, look, I just want you guys to be safe.
Pero, miren, solo quiero que ustedes estén seguros.
Oh...
Danger!
¡Peligro!
Ah, huh? Unagi.
Ah, ¿eh? Unagi.
Two thousand bucks is a lot of money.
Dos mil dólares es mucho dinero.
Boy, I wish I had a twin.
Vaya, ojalá tuviera un gemelo.
Where could I find someone...
¿Dónde podría encontrar a alguien...
...who looks exactly like me?
...que se parezca exactamente a mí?
Hey.
Oye.
Chandler.
I sensed it was you.
Sentí que eras tú.
What?
¿Qué?
Unagi.
I'm always aware.
Siempre estoy alerta.
Okay, are you aware that unagi is an eel?
Está bien, ¿eres consciente de que el unagi es una anguila?
- What's up? - I can't figure out what to make Monica.
- ¿Qué pasa? - No se me ocurre qué hacerle a Monica.
Oh. Why don't you make her one of your little jokes?
Oh. ¿Por qué no le haces una de tus bromitas?
I'm going crazy, okay?
Me estoy volviendo loco, ¿vale?
Do you have anything around here that looks homemade?
¿Tienes algo por aquí que parezca hecho en casa?
Oh, you know what? She'd love this.
Oh, ¿sabes qué? Le encantaría esto.
It's an exact replica of Apollo 8. I made it in the sixth grade.
Es una réplica exacta del Apolo 8. Lo hice en sexto grado.
Yeah, I guess I could use that. I could say, "Your love sends me to the moon."
Sí, supongo que podría usar eso. Podría decir: "Tu amor me envía a la luna".
Yeah, yeah. Except Apollo 8 didn't actually land on the moon.
Sí, sí. Excepto que el Apolo 8 en realidad no aterrizó en la luna.
But you could write, um:
Pero podrías escribir, eh:
"Your love lets me orbit the moon twice and return safely."
"Tu amor me permite orbitar la luna dos veces y regresar a salvo".
Wait, I can't give this to her.
Espera, no puedo darle esto.
- Why not? - It says "Captain Ross" on the side.
- ¿Por qué no? - Dice "Capitán Ross" en el costado.
- And it says "I hate Monica" on the bottom. - Oh.
- Y dice "Odio a Monica" abajo. - Oh.
- Danger! - Aah!
- ¡Peligro! - ¡Aah!
Ah. Salmon-skin roll.
Ah. Rollo de piel de salmón.
Okay, okay.
Está bien, está bien.
Yes, honey, I made it myself.
Sí, cariño, lo hice yo misma.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
No puedo hacerlo. No puedo hacerlo.
Oh, oh. A mixed tape. A mixed tape.
Oh, oh. Una cinta de música. Una cinta de música.
- Hey, hi. - Hey.
- Hola, hola. - Hola.
- You ready to exchange gifts? - Sure. Okay, you go first.
- ¿Listo para intercambiar regalos? - Claro. Okay, tú primero.
- Okay, come here, come here. - Okay.
- Okay, ven aquí, ven aquí. - Okay.
Okay, now, it's not wrapped, because I just finished it.
Okay, no está envuelto, porque acabo de terminarlo.
Okay.
But I made you a tape of what I think are all romantic songs.
Pero te hice una cinta con lo que creo que son todas canciones románticas.
What a great gift.
Qué gran regalo.
Oh.
Is "The Way You Look Tonight" on it?
¿Está "The Way You Look Tonight" en ella?
Maybe. We'll have to listen and see.
Quizás. Tendremos que escuchar para ver.
- Oh, I love it. Thank you so much. Mwah. - Aw. Okay. Mwah.
- Oh, me encanta. Muchas gracias. Mwah. - Aw. Okay. Mwah.
Okay, you ready to open yours?
Okay, ¿listo para abrir el tuyo?
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Sí. - Okay.
It's a sock bunny.
Es un conejito de calcetín.
Ha, ha. Yeah, yeah. Remember how I call you "bunny"?
Ja, ja. Sí, sí. ¿Recuerdas cómo te llamo "conejito"?
Not really.
En realidad no.
Well, I did one time. And I wanna start doing it more.
Bueno, lo hice una vez. Y quiero empezar a hacerlo más.
- That's what this is about. - I see.
- De eso se trata. - Ya veo.
You know, um, Phoebe makes sock bunnies.
Sabes, eh, Phoebe hace conejitos de calcetín.
No. No, she doesn't.
No. No, ella no.
Phoebe, what she makes, that's... They're sock rabbits.
Phoebe, lo que ella hace, eso es... Son conejos de calcetín.
They're completely different. Okay, okay.
Son completamente diferentes. Okay, okay.
Okay, I didn't make it. I'm sorry. I totally forgot about tonight...
Okay, no lo hice yo. Lo siento. Olvidé por completo lo de esta noche...
...and that we were supposed to make the presents.
...y que se suponía que debíamos hacer los regalos.
- Oh, it's okay. I don't... - No, no, it's not okay. It's not.
- Oh, está bien. Yo no... - No, no, no está bien. No lo está.
I mean, you're so incredible.
Quiero decir, eres tan increíble.
You went through all this time and effort to make this tape for me.
Te tomaste todo este tiempo y esfuerzo para hacerme esta cinta.
You know, I'm just gonna... I'm gonna make this up to you. I will.
Sabes, te lo voy a compensar. Lo haré.
I am going to cook you anything you want in here.
Te voy a cocinar lo que quieras aquí.
And I'm going to do anything you want in there.
Y voy a hacer lo que quieras allá.
Well, I did put a lot of thought into the tape.
Bueno, sí le puse mucha atención a la cinta.
Wow.
Guau.
- You are way too young to have seen that. - Oops. Ha, ha.
- Eres demasiado joven para haber visto eso. - Ups. Ja, ja.
Your birthday's in a month and a half.
Tu cumpleaños es en un mes y medio.
What do you say I forget to get you a present for that too?
¿Qué dices si también olvido darte un regalo para eso?
You are totally and completely 100 percent forgiven.
Estás total y completamente perdonado al 100 por ciento.
- We have got to wash that. - Yeah.
- Tenemos que lavar eso. - Sí.
Hey, do you remember that jacket that you loved so much...
Oye, ¿te acuerdas de esa chaqueta que tanto te gustaba...
...that you thought was too expensive? - You have done enough.
...que te parecía demasiado cara? - Ya has hecho suficiente.
Ha, ha. I'm gonna wake up early and get it for you.
Ja, ja. Me voy a levantar temprano y te la voy a comprar.
No, you don't have... Get it in black, not brown.
No, no tienes que... Cómprala negra, no marrón.
- Oop. Your cake is ready. - Oop.
- ¡Uy! Tu pastel está listo. - ¡Uy!
It's like that old saying, "Have sex, eat some cake."
Es como ese viejo dicho: "Haz el amor, come pastel."
Hey, Mon. Hey, Chan. Just getting a soda.
Hola, Mon. Hola, Chan. Solo voy por un refresco.
Who the hell are you?
¿Quién demonios eres tú?
I'm Joey.
Soy Joey.
How are you doing?
¿Cómo estás?
No, no, no!
¡No, no, no!
"How you doing?"
"¿Cómo estás?"
"How you doing?" Damn it, Carl. Go wait in the hall.
"¿Cómo estás?" Maldición, Carl. Ve a esperar al pasillo.
- Look, I got to apologize on behalf of Carl. - Who the hell is Carl?
- Mira, tengo que disculparme en nombre de Carl. - ¿Quién demonios es Carl?
Oh, did I not mention?
Oh, ¿no te lo mencioné?
Carl is a guy I hired to be my identical twin for a medical research project.
Carl es un tipo que contraté para que fuera mi gemelo idéntico para un proyecto de investigación médica.
You know, sometimes the good ideas are just right in front of you, aren't they?
Sabes, a veces las buenas ideas están justo delante de ti, ¿no?
Look, I know it sounds crazy, but I think it might work.
Mira, sé que suena loco, pero creo que podría funcionar.
But the only problem is Carl's acting is:
Pero el único problema es que la actuación de Carl es:
The only problem?
¿El único problema?
Yeah. He's the reason I didn't get that big Minute Maid commercial.
Sí. Es la razón por la que no conseguí ese gran comercial de Minute Maid.
We were supposed to be brothers, but he messed it up.
Se suponía que éramos hermanos, pero él lo arruinó.
Hey. Can I get a little piece of that cake?
Oye. ¿Me das un pedacito de ese pastel?
Pizza. We like pizza. Get out!
Pizza. Nos gusta la pizza. ¡Fuera!
- Pat Sajak? - Yep.
- ¿Pat Sajak? - Sí.
- Alex Trebek? - Oh, of course.
- ¿Alex Trebek? - Oh, claro.
- Chuck Woolery? - Definitely.
- ¿Chuck Woolery? - Definitivamente.
Phoebe, you will not find a single game-show host...
Phoebe, no encontrarás a un solo presentador de concursos...
...whose ass I cannot kick.
...a quien no pueda patearle el trasero.
- Say it. - Say we are unagi.
- Dilo. - Di que somos unagi.
It's not something you are, it's something you have.
No es algo que eres, es algo que tienes.
Say it.
Dilo.
I could easily get out of this...
Podría salirme fácilmente de esto...
...but there's a chance you could get very, very hurt.
...pero existe la posibilidad de que te lastimes muy, muy gravemente.
All right, Carl, we're next. Now, remember, what is this not gonna be?
Muy bien, Carl, somos los siguientes. Ahora, recuerda, ¿qué es lo que NO va a ser?
- Another Minute Maid fiasco. - That's right.
- Otro fiasco de Minute Maid. - Así es.
And what are you not gonna do?
¿Y qué NO vas a hacer?
- I'm not gonna talk, because... - Ah. Damn it, Carl.
- No voy a hablar, porque... - Ah. Maldición, Carl.
Can I have the next one, please?
¿Me das el siguiente, por favor?
Thank you.
Gracias.
Joey and Tony Tribbiani.
Joey y Tony Tribbiani.
That's us.
Ese somos nosotros.
But, uh, this is a study for identical twins.
Pero, eh, este es un estudio para gemelos idénticos.
That's right. Two thousand dollars.
Así es. Dos mil dólares.
But you're not identical twins.
Pero ustedes no son gemelos idénticos.
Damn it, Carl.
Maldición, Carl.
Oh, my good God.
Oh, Dios mío.
Hey. Continuing the countdown of your favorite meals.
Oye. Continuando la cuenta regresiva de tus comidas favoritas.
Tonight, number three:
Esta noche, el número tres:
Macaroni and cheese with cut-up hot dogs.
Macarrones con queso y salchichas picadas.
Look, you have done enough, okay? You have to stop this now.
Mira, ya has hecho suficiente, ¿vale? Tienes que parar ahora.
I will, but not tonight.
Lo haré, pero no esta noche.
For dinner music, I thought we could listen to that tape that you made me.
Para la música de la cena, pensé que podríamos escuchar esa cinta que me hiciste.
- Oh, the mixed tape. - Mm-hm.
- Oh, ¿la cinta mezclada? - Mm-hm.
When I'm awfully low
Cuando estoy muy bajo
Oh. "The Way You Look Tonight" is on here.
Oh. "The Way You Look Tonight" está aquí.
Dance with me.
Baila conmigo.
I will feel a glow
Sentiré un brillo
Just thinking of you
Solo pensando en ti
And the way you look tonight
Y en cómo te ves esta noche
You are just the sweetest.
Eres lo más dulce.
I love the way you look every night, Chandler.
Me encanta cómo te ves cada noche, Chandler.
That's why I made you this tape.
Por eso te hice esta cinta.
Happy birthday. Love, Janice. Mwah.
Feliz cumpleaños. Con cariño, Janice. Mwah.
No, you're the sweetest.
No, tú eres lo más dulce.
Okay, ladies, that ends today's class. Let's remember, let's be safe out there.
Muy bien, chicas, hasta aquí la clase de hoy. Recordemos, tengamos cuidado ahí fuera.
- Great class. Heh. - Thanks, man.
- Gran clase. Je. - Gracias, amigo.
Yeah, yeah. I was watching.
Sí, sí. Estaba mirando.
Um, hey, a couple of questions, though.
Eh, tengo un par de preguntas, sin embargo.
Um, you know that last move...
Eh, ¿sabes ese último movimiento...
...where that woman tripped you and then pinned you to the floor?
...donde esa mujer te derribó y te inmovilizó en el suelo?
What would you do next?
¿Qué harías después?
Well, then she'd take her keys and jam them in your...
Bueno, entonces ella tomaría sus llaves y te las clavaría en...
No, no, no. What would you do next?
No, no, no. ¿Qué harías después?
- Who, me, the attacker? - Yes, that's right.
- ¿Yo, el atacante? - Sí, así es.
Why?
¿Por qué?
I tried attacking two women. Did not work.
Intenté atacar a dos mujeres. No funcionó.
- What? - No, I mean, it's okay.
- ¿Qué? - No, quiero decir, está bien.
I mean, they're my friends. In fact, I was married to one of them.
Quiero decir, son mis amigas. De hecho, estuve casado con una de ellas.
Let me get this straight. You attacked your ex-wife?
A ver si te entiendo. ¿Atacaste a tu ex-esposa?
Oh, no, no, no. Heh.
Oh, no, no, no. Je.
I tried.
Lo intenté.
But I couldn't. That's why I'm here.
Pero no pude. Por eso estoy aquí.
Maybe we could attack them together.
Quizás podríamos atacarlas juntas.
That's a no.
Eso es un no.
I am so, so, so sorry.
Lo siento muchísimo, muchísimo.
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
Oh! And I will cook anything you want in here...
Oh! Y te cocinaré lo que quieras aquí...
...and do anything you want in there.
...y haré lo que quieras allá.
Yeah, you will, and are you kidding me?
Sí, lo harás, ¿y me estás bromeando?
Come on, Monica, it's our Valentine's Day.
Vamos, Monica, es nuestro Día de San Valentín.
Please, please, please?
¿Por favor, por favor, por favor?
- Okay. - Okay.
- Vale. - Vale.
My funny valentine
Mi divertido San Valentín
Sweet comic valentine You make me...
Dulce y cómico San Valentín Me haces...
- So are we going in there? - I am.
- ¿Entonces vamos a entrar? - Yo sí.
Your looks are laughable
Tus miradas son ridículas
Aha.
Ajá.
Nowhere to run.
No hay dónde correr.
I don't like sitting up here. I'm gonna go over...
No me gusta estar sentado aquí arriba. Voy a ir...
No, Rachel, they got here first.
No, Rachel, llegaron primero.
- Why is Ross doing that? - Danger!
- ¿Por qué hace eso Ross? - ¡Peligro!
Oh, my God. Why is he jumping on those women?
Dios mío. ¿Por qué está saltando sobre esas mujeres?
We should help them.
Deberíamos ayudarlas.
I don't think they need any help.
No creo que necesiten ayuda.