Well, that thing's clearly in the way.
Bueno, esa cosa claramente estorba.
All right. A-ha. Heh.
De acuerdo. Ajá. Je.
Damn fridge!
¡Maldita nevera!
- Hi, Joey. How you doing? - Great...
- Hola, Joey. ¿Cómo estás? - Genial...
...roomie. - Ah!
...compañero de piso. - ¡Ah!
- Yeah, I guess we are roommates now. - I know. Now that you bring it up...
- Sí, supongo que ahora somos compañeros de piso. - Lo sé. Ya que lo mencionas...
...uh, our fridge is broken. We have to get a new one.
...eh, nuestra nevera está rota. Tenemos que comprar una nueva.
I checked around and your half is $400. Thanks a lot.
Investigué y tu parte son $400. Muchas gracias.
I'm not paying for half of that.
No voy a pagar la mitad de eso.
I'm only staying here until my apartment gets fixed.
Solo me quedaré aquí hasta que arreglen mi apartamento.
Look, Rach, my parents bought this fridge just after I was born. Okay?
Mira, Rach, mis padres compraron esta nevera justo después de que yo naciera. ¿Vale?
Now, I have never had a problem with it. Then you show up and it breaks!
Nunca tuve un problema con ella. ¡Entonces apareces tú y se rompe!
What does that tell you?
¿Qué te dice eso?
That refrigerators don't live as long as people?
¿Que las neveras no viven tanto como las personas?
All right, you know that the ATM only lets you take out 300 at a time...
De acuerdo, sabes que el cajero automático solo te deja sacar 300 a la vez...
...so I'll take a check for the other 100.
...así que te haré un cheque por los otros 100.
Heh. You're joking, right?
Je. ¿Estás bromeando, verdad?
Of course I'm joking. I don't take checks.
Claro que bromeo. No acepto cheques.
Thank God you're pretty.
Menos mal que eres guapa.
- Hey! - Hey.
- ¡Oye! - Oye.
Hey, do you guys know any cute guys?
Oigan, ¿conocen a chicos guapos?
Well, of course, I do. My good friend, Joey, over here.
Bueno, claro que sí. Mi buen amigo, Joey, aquí presente.
Oh, I'm sorry. Thank you, Chandler.
Oh, lo siento. Gracias, Chandler.
Anyway, there's a charity ball this weekend and Ralph Lauren bought a table...
En fin, hay un baile benéfico este fin de semana y Ralph Lauren compró una mesa...
...so I kind of have to go.
...así que tengo que ir.
- What's the charity? - I don't know.
- ¿Cuál es la caridad? - No lo sé.
Something, either trees or disease, I...
Algo, o árboles o una enfermedad, yo...
- Ralph mumbles a lot. - Does Ralph mumble...
- Ralph murmura mucho. - ¿Murmura Ralph...
...when you're not paying attention? - Yeah. It's weird.
...cuando no le prestas atención? - Sí. Es raro.
But the thing is, I need to find a date.
Pero el caso es que necesito encontrar una cita.
What kind of guy are you looking for?
¿Qué tipo de chico buscas?
Someone that has his own tux or the ability to rent a tux.
Alguien que tenga su propio esmoquin o la capacidad de alquilar uno.
So he has to be a male who has at least $50.
Así que tiene que ser un hombre que tenga al menos $50.
Ooh, so close.
Ooh, muy cerca.
- Hey, everybody. - Hey.
- Hola a todos. - Hola.
- Uh, this is Elizabeth. - Hi, Elizabeth.
- Eh, ella es Elizabeth. - Hola, Elizabeth.
- I'm the student. - Ha-ha-ha.
- Soy la estudiante. - Ja-ja-ja.
Isn't she cute? Nope.
¿No es linda? No.
This is none of my business, but weren't you guys supposed...
Esto no es asunto mío, pero ¿no se suponía que ustedes...
...to not be seen in public together? - Oh, we're not together.
...no se vieran en público juntos? - Oh, no estamos juntos.
No. We're just two people who happen to have run into each other...
No. Solo somos dos personas que se han encontrado...
...here at the coffee house. Heh, this is...
...aquí en la cafetería. Je, esto es...
Oh, sly.
Oh, astuto.
I really wanted to meet you guys, but I have to run.
Realmente quería conocerlos, pero tengo que irme.
- I'll see you later? - Okay.
- ¿Nos vemos luego? - Vale.
- Bye, Ross. - Bye. See you.
- Adiós, Ross. - Adiós. Nos vemos.
- Oh... - Oops.
- Oh... - Ups.
- Didn't mean to run into you like that, sir. - That is quite all right, ma'am.
- Disculpe, señor, no quise chocar con usted. - Está todo bien, señorita.
Bye.
Adiós.
So why's she leaving? Is it a school night and she has a lot of homework to do?
Entonces, ¿por qué se va? ¿Es noche de estudio y tiene mucha tarea?
Yes. Her molecular epidemiology paper is due tomorrow.
[ERROR API]
Well, tell her "good luck" with that.
Anyone else, huh? Bring them on.
[ERROR API]
- Oh! When's her birthday? - I don't know, Rachel. Why?
Well, you know it's just been so long since I've been to Chuck E. Cheese.
[ERROR API]
- I like Elizabeth. - Well, thanks.
In fact, I like her so much that you tell her I want my cookies early this year.
[ERROR API]
A box of Thin Mints and some Tagalongs.
Guys, give him a break. Ross, seriously, how's it going with her?
[ERROR API]
Well, it's actually been great.
She's 20, so she's not looking for anything too serious...
[ERROR API]
...which is perfect for me now.
Well, that is great. And seriously, she seems very nice.
[ERROR API]
I know you guys like to give me a hard time...
...but it means a lot to me that you like her.
[ERROR API]
- Just knowing you guys are, like... - Okay, I got a good one.
Okay, um... Heh.
[ERROR API]
What is she, like, 12?
Chandler, do you think we talk about our relationship enough?
[ERROR API]
Yeah. Do we have any Fruit Roll Ups?
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Okay, I just thought of the perfect guy for Rachel to take to her thing.
[ERROR API]
That's so funny, we found someone too.
That's good. I guess she'll have a choice between my guy and your weirdo.
[ERROR API]
- Why would our guy be a weirdo? - Because that's just your taste.
See, Rachel's not gonna pick your stupid guy.
[ERROR API]
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
- ¿Ah, sí? - Sí.
My guy is a lawyer who does volunteer work.
[ERROR API]
And he has one of these.
A face ass?
[ERROR API]
- A chin dimple. - Well, uh, our guy works with Chandler.
And he's really nice and smart and he's a great dresser.
[ERROR API]
- Have you seen your guy's body? - No. Our guy's just a floating head.
Well, my guy is spectacular, okay? He's a massage client.
[ERROR API]
And one time, um, when he was on the table, I looked at it. And I mean, all of it.
- You're not supposed to look. - Yeah, like there are police for that.
[ERROR API]
- What, you look? You massaged me. - I know.
All right, your guy may have a great body, but our guy...
[ERROR API]
...is really funny. - Chandler funny?
- Our guy's a great dancer. - My guy's well-read.
[ERROR API]
- Our guy has great hair. - My guy has great teeth.
Our guys smells incredible.
[ERROR API]
Do you want our guy to be your guy?
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Well, you don't look good, Joe.
[ERROR API]
Well, the fridge broke, so I had to eat everything.
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
[ERROR API]
Hey, what was in that brown jar?
- That's still in there? - Not anymore.
[ERROR API]
Ahem, so, anyway, how do you want to pay me?
Is this a service you're providing me?
¿Me estás ofreciendo este servicio?
No, for my new fridge. For our new fridge.
No, es para mi refrigerador nuevo. Para nuestro refrigerador nuevo.
Our new fridge?
¿Nuestro refrigerador nuevo?
- I don't live here anymore. - So what?
- Ya no vivo aquí. - ¿Y qué?
Look, okay, suppose we were a, uh, divorced couple.
Mira, está bien, supongamos que éramos una... eh... pareja divorciada.
- Uh-huh. - And I got custody of the kid. Right?
- Ajá. - Y yo obtuve la custodia del niño. ¿Correcto?
Now, suppose the kid dies and I gotta buy a new kid.
Ahora, supón que el niño muere y tengo que comprar un niño nuevo.
Okay.
Give me $400!
¡Dame $400!
- Professor Geller? - Hmm?
- ¿Profesor Geller? - ¿Mmm?
Oh, a student I don't know.
Oh, una estudiante que no conozco.
I was wondering if I could talk to you for a moment?
¿Me preguntaba si podría hablar con usted un momento?
Yes, of course. What would this be regarding?
Sí, por supuesto. ¿Sobre qué sería?
- Making out in your office. - Wh... Shh!
- Besándonos en tu oficina. - ¿Qu... Shh!
Uh, of course. Why don't we go inside.
Eh, por supuesto. ¿Por qué no pasamos?
Mm... Oh, oh.
- What? - Doorknob. Doorknob.
- ¿Qué? - Pomo de la puerta. Pomo de la puerta.
Sorry. Ha-ha-ha.
Lo siento. Ja-ja-ja.
- Um, I actually do need to talk to you. - Oh. Okay, what about?
- Um, en realidad sí necesito hablar contigo. - Oh. Está bien, ¿sobre qué?
- Spring vacation. - Spring vacation?
- Vacaciones de primavera. - ¿Vacaciones de primavera?
Yeah, we have time off, and a lot of people are going on trips...
Sí, tenemos tiempo libre, y mucha gente se va de viaje...
- Professor Geller. - Yes, Professor Fiesenstinlender?
- Profesor Geller. - ¿Sí, Profesora Fiesenstinlender?
I'll be with you in one moment.
Estaré con usted en un momento.
So I will take one box of the Thin Mints.
Entonces tomaré una caja de las Thin Mints.
You don't understand. Elizabeth was about to ask me to go on a trip with her.
No entiendes. Elizabeth estaba a punto de pedirme que fuera de viaje con ella.
Is that taking it slow? I'm not ready for this, okay?
¿Eso es ir despacio? No estoy listo para esto, ¿vale?
- What do I tell her? - Tell her the truth. You're not ready.
- ¿Qué le digo? - Dile la verdad. No estás listo.
I could do that.
Podría hacer eso.
- Well, what if she gets upset? - Then you distract her with a Barbie doll.
- Bueno, ¿y si se molesta? - Entonces distráela con una muñeca Barbie.
Or...
O...
...you could just, you know, you...
...podrías, ya sabes, tú...
What the hell are you doing?
¿Qué demonios estás haciendo?
Wha...?
¿Q...?
What the hell am I doing? You just broke my fridge!
¿Qué demonios estoy haciendo? ¡Acabas de romper mi refrigerador!
What? How do you know if... How do you know it's even broken?
¿Qué? ¿Cómo sabes si... ¿Cómo sabes si está roto?
Oh, you think I don't know what breaks my fridge?
Oh, ¿crees que no sé qué rompe mi refrigerador?
Excuse me.
Disculpe.
Well, what do you know? Broken!
Bueno, ¿tú qué sabes? ¡Roto!
That'll be $400.
Serán $400.
Joey, I saw you push him.
Joey, te vi empujarlo.
You pushed him.
Lo empujaste.
Joey, I did not break this. Okay? That has been broken for a while.
Joey, yo no rompí esto. ¿De acuerdo? Eso ha estado roto por un tiempo.
- Remember I told you about our fridge? - Uh-huh.
- ¿Recuerdas que te hablé de nuestro refrigerador? - Ajá.
I still haven't gotten the check for your half yet.
Todavía no he recibido el cheque de tu parte.
Do not give him any money.
No le des dinero.
I'm not talking to you! You broke my fridge!
¡No te estoy hablando a ti! ¡Rompiste mi refrigerador!
- You wanted to see me, Professor Geller? - Yes. Yes. Please come in.
- ¿Quería verme, Profesor Geller? - Sí. Sí. Pase, por favor.
Mm, ooh, ooh.
- Doorknob? - Yeah. It kind of grows on you.
- ¿Pomo de la puerta? - Sí. Te acostumbras.
Actually, I wanted to finish talking to you about spring vacation.
En realidad, quería terminar de hablar contigo sobre las vacaciones de primavera.
Oh, good.
[ERROR API]
Look, I...
Mira, yo...
Look, I've been having a great time with you.
[ERROR API]
And I just don't want us to move too fast or put too much pressure on us.
So I'm sorry, I just don't think we should go away together yet.
[ERROR API]
It's too soon.
Uh, Ross, I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
[ERROR API]
I just wanted to tell you that I'm going to Florida for a couple weeks.
No.
I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
[ERROR API]
- What I meant was... - You are so adorable.
That. Let's talk about that.
[ERROR API]
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- How did it go with Elizabeth? - Huh? Oh, oh.
[ERROR API]
Fine. It was just a misunderstanding. She didn't want me to go with her.
She just wanted to let me know that she's going to Florida for spring vacation.
[ERROR API]
Wait, is she going for spring vacation or going for spring break.
What's the difference?
[ERROR API]
A spring vacation, you're doing nice things with your grandparents.
Spring break, you're doing frat guys.
[ERROR API]
Hey, you know what? Not all spring breaks are like that.
- What did you do on yours? - I went to Egypt with my dad.
[ERROR API]
I can see it now. "Look, Dad, it's the Sphinx."
I think Elizabeth is a little more serious than, "Spring break!"
[ERROR API]
All right? Come on, she's taking my class.
- And slept with the professor. - I'm gonna call her.
[ERROR API]
Hey, you guys, I want you to meet Sebastian.
- Hi. - We just, uh...
[ERROR API]
We just met at the newsstand. We both grabbed for the last Field and Stream. Ha!
What, I read that.
[ERROR API]
- Can I get you a cup of coffee? - Oh, yes. Thank you.
- Rachel, what the hell is this? - What?
[ERROR API]
You ask us to find you a guy, and then you come in here with a guy of your own.
- You found me a guy? - Yes.
[ERROR API]
We found you a really cute, funny guy from Chandler's work.
Yeah, and I found you one, too, who is not a weirdo.
[ERROR API]
You know what though, guys, I really appreciate that...
...but I'm just gonna take Sebastian to the charity.
[ERROR API]
Are you sure? Because our guy smells incredible.
Would you stop it with that already?
[ERROR API]
- Here you go. Sure. - Oh, thank you.
So, Sebastian, do you do any volunteer work?
[ERROR API]
- Uh, no, not really. Why? - No reason.
It's just I know a single guy who does care about other people.
[ERROR API]
Are you funny?
- Excuse me? - What are you guys doing?
[ERROR API]
Are you funny? Tell us a joke!
Look, I just wanted to have coffee with Rachel.
[ERROR API]
Well, so do a lot of people.
- Actually, uh, I gotta get going. - Oh, but you...
[ERROR API]
- Give me a call sometime. - But you didn't give me your number.
Okay, see you later.
[ERROR API]
Turns out he is kind of funny.
I cannot believe you guys!
[ERROR API]
He was really nice and he just left because of you!
Yeah, but, "Sebastian"? What is that, a cat's name?
[ERROR API]
You know what I noticed, Rachel, he scares easy.
Now, is that the kind of guy you want to take to a ball?
[ERROR API]
"Sebastian, would you like to dance?"
"Uh, okay. I gotta go. Aah!"
[ERROR API]
All right, guys stop it. Rachel, we're very sorry.
That is a very insensitive thing for us to do.
[ERROR API]
You know what? Let us make it up to you. We've two great guys for you.
Yeah, what have you got to lose?
[ERROR API]
You might even end up with someone really special. If you pick my guy.
- All right. - Okay. So you will meet our guys?
[ERROR API]
Yes, I'll meet them.
It doesn't matter which one you choose. It's up to you.
[ERROR API]
Our guy is perfect.
Or you could go out with the guy Phoebe deemed...
[ERROR API]
...not good enough to go out with herself. - Ugh!
Phoebe, there you are! Okay, you broke my fridge.
[ERROR API]
You owe me 400 bucks.
- Okay, sure. - Really?
[ERROR API]
Ooh, technically, you owe me $600 for sending out happy thoughts...
...on your last 10 auditions.
[ERROR API]
Call it even?
Okay.
There you are. So, what did Elizabeth say?
[ERROR API]
Well, turns out she is going to Daytona for "spring break, woo-hoo."
That means wet T-shirt contests, guys doing shots off of girls' bodies...
[ERROR API]
...waking up next to people you don't even know.
Man, she is gonna have a great time!
[ERROR API]
Is she staying at the Hotel Corona?
- You know the hotels? - I was there, Spring Break '81!
[ERROR API]
In 1981, you were 13.
So what? I drove down, sold T-shirts. I had a blast.
[ERROR API]
You know who knows how to party? Drunk college chicks.
Okay, she can't go.
[ERROR API]
You can't tell her not to go. You just started dating.
- Then what am I supposed to do? - Nothing. Just be cool with it.
[ERROR API]
What if she goes down there and sleeps with a bunch of guys?
Well, maybe you don't marry this one.
[ERROR API]
I'm so glad you're going on this trip.
Yeah, I've been working so hard this semester.
[ERROR API]
I really need to go crazy, you know? Blow off some steam.
Sure. Sure.
[ERROR API]
Look, I don't know if your plans are finalized yet...
...but I know another great way to blow off steam.
[ERROR API]
- What? - Are you into crafts at all?
- Ross, are you okay? - Uh, yeah. Of course I'm okay.
- Ross, ¿estás bien? - Eh, sí. Claro que estoy bien.
Heh, I'm just being, uh, supportive.
Je, solo estoy siendo, eh, solidaria.
Supportive of you and this whole trip...
Solidaria contigo y con todo este viaje...
...and what... What is, uh...? What's this?
...y qué... ¿Qué es, eh...? ¿Qué es esto?
- It's a bathing suit? - To wear in front of people?
- ¿Es un traje de baño? - ¿Para usarlo en público?
- Is that supportive? - Is this?
- ¿Eso es ser solidaria? - ¿Esto lo es?
- Hey. - Good, good, good.
- Hola. - Bien, bien, bien.
- Hey. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
- We're glad you decided to meet our guy. - Oh.
- Nos alegra que hayas decidido conocer a nuestro chico. - Oh.
You're gonna like him so much.
Te va a caer muy bien.
- Uh, when do you want to meet him? - I don't know.
- Eh, ¿cuándo quieres conocerlo? - No sé.
- I don't work late tomorrow night. - Tomorrow night is good.
- No trabajo hasta tarde mañana. - Mañana por la noche está bien.
But why put off something till tomorrow that you can do right now. Ha-ha-ha.
Pero, ¿por qué dejar para mañana algo que puedes hacer ahora mismo? Ja-ja-ja.
- Eldad, come here! - What?
- ¡Eldad, ven aquí! - ¿Qué?
- Eldad, this is Rachel. - How are you?
- Eldad, esta es Rachel. - ¿Cómo estás?
A little blind-sided, but, you know, good.
Un poco sorprendida, pero, ya sabes, bien.
Eldad, sit down. Move over. Move over now.
Eldad, siéntate. Muévete. Muévete ahora.
There you go. There you are.
Ahí tienes. Ahí estás.
- Okay, we can take a hint! - Ha-ha-ha.
- ¡Okay, entendemos la indirecta! - Ja-ja-ja.
- Wait. What are you doing here? - This is Patrick.
- Espera. ¿Qué haces aquí? - Este es Patrick.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
You're too late, because she's already with our guy.
Llegaste tarde, porque ella ya está con nuestro chico.
Oh, my God, you're right, I am too late. They're sitting on the couch and talking.
Oh, Dios mío, tienes razón, ya es tarde. Están sentados en el sofá hablando.
Come on.
Vamos.
- Rachel? This is Patrick. - Yeah?
- ¿Rachel? Este es Patrick. - ¿Sí?
- Oh. Hi. - Hi.
- Oh. Hola. - Hola.
This is the guy I was telling you about.
Este es el chico del que te estaba hablando.
Believe me, this suit does not do justice to what's underneath it.
Créeme, este traje no le hace justicia a lo que hay debajo.
Okay.
But Pheebs, I'm just sort of in the middle of something.
Pero Pheebs, estoy en medio de algo.
Oh, okay. That's okay. Have a seat.
Oh, está bien. No pasa nada. Siéntate.
- You can't do that! - Maybe I should go.
- ¡No puedes hacer eso! - Quizás debería irme.
Just sit down, we're winning.
Solo siéntate, estamos ganando.
Okay, you know what? Maybe I should go.
Okay, ¿sabes qué? Quizás debería irme.
- No, no! - Have a seat!
- ¡No, no! - ¡Siéntate!
Rachel, you haven't touched Eldad's hair.
Rachel, no has tocado el pelo de Eldad.
- It is the softest hair. Touch it. - I'm good.
- Es el pelo más suave. Tócalo. - Estoy bien.
Rachel, Patrick is really rich. Give her some money.
Rachel, Patrick es muy rico. Dale algo de dinero.
Phoebe, this isn't really worth the free massage.
Phoebe, esto no vale la pena el masaje gratis.
That's right, Patrick. Bye-bye.
Así es, Patrick. Adiós.
Eldad is much more cooperative and he can dance.
Eldad es mucho más cooperativo y puede bailar.
You dance for Rachel.
Baila para Rachel.
No, don't dance for me, please!
- ¡No, no bailes por mí, por favor! -
What is the matter with you guys?
¿Qué les pasa, chicos?
Yeah, okay, let's talk it out.
Sí, okay, hablemos de ello.
Am I the only one that this is embarrassing for?
¿Soy la única a la que esto le da vergüenza?
- I'm a little embarrassed. - Shh, shh.
- Me da un poco de vergüenza. - Shh, shh.
I'll tell you who should be embarrassed. It's you guys. This is ridiculous!
Les diré quién debería avergonzarse. Ustedes. ¡Esto es ridículo!
Thank you, but I do not need you to get me a date.
Gracias, pero no necesito que me consigas una cita.
- Then why did she ask us to help... - I am still talking!
- Entonces, ¿por qué nos pidió ayuda...? - ¡Todavía estoy hablando!
Then you chase away the one guy that I actually liked.
Y luego espantas al único chico que me gustó.
No offense to you guys. Really, congratulations on...
Sin ofenderlos a ustedes. De verdad, felicidades por...
...all the cash.
...todo el dinero.
And you really... Wow, you do have very soft hair.
Y tú... Vaya, sí que tienes el pelo muy suave.
But I'd much rather go to the ball by myself than go through any more of this!
¡Pero preferiría ir sola al baile que pasar por esto!
Goodbye.
Adiós.
Now, do you use some sort of special conditioner on that hair?
Ahora, ¿usas algún acondicionador especial en ese pelo?
- Yes, papaya extract. - Thank you.
- Sí, extracto de papaya. - Gracias.
- So, uh, have a great time down there. - I will.
- Bueno, que te diviertas. - Lo haré.
- Did you pack that bathing suit? - Yeah.
- ¿Empacaste ese traje de baño? - Sí.
It was pretty funny when I hid it for a while, huh?
Fue bastante gracioso cuando lo escondí por un rato, ¿eh?
Anyway. Um...
En fin. Mmm...
I am worried about that bathing suit.
Estoy preocupada por ese traje de baño.
Not because it's revealing, which I'm fine with.
No porque sea revelador, que me parece bien.
No, I'm concerned about your health.
No, me preocupa tu salud.
Um, sun exposure.
Mmm, la exposición al sol.
Oh, don't worry, I have plenty of sun block.
Oh, no te preocupes, tengo mucho protector solar.
- It's SPF 30. - All right.
- Es FPS 30. - De acuerdo.
Well, if what's in the bottle is actually 30.
Bueno, si lo que hay en la botella es realmente 30.
I mean, sometimes you get 30, sometimes it's 4, and I swear...
Quiero decir, a veces te dan 30, a veces es 4, y te juro...
...more often than not, it's just milk.
...más a menudo de lo que crees, es solo leche.
Ross, it's gonna be okay.
Ross, todo va a estar bien.
I'm not going down there to hook up with a bunch of guys.
No voy a ir allá a ligar con un montón de chicos.
I really like you. I like how things are going between us.
Realmente me gustas. Me gusta cómo van las cosas entre nosotros.
- Really? - Yeah.
- ¿En serio? - Sí.
I'm just going down there to relax and hang out with my friends.
Solo voy a ir allá a relajarme y pasar el rato con mis amigos.
Okay. Cool. Heh.
Ok. Genial. Je.
- Oh, here they are. - Hey, Elizabeth!
- Oh, aquí están. - ¡Hola, Elizabeth!
Bye!
¡Adiós!
Call me!
¡Llámame!
Rachel, we're sorry for pushing those guys on you.
Rachel, lamentamos haberte insistido con esos chicos.
That's all right. I ended up having a really good time.
Está bien. Al final me lo pasé muy bien.
The charity was a big success, they raised a lot of money and awareness.
La caridad fue un gran éxito, recaudaron mucho dinero y conciencia.
So, what was it for, anyway?
Entonces, ¿para qué era, de todos modos?
I wanna say a disease.
Quiero decir, una enfermedad.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
I just got this weird message from Ross. He said turn on MTV. I don't know.
Acabo de recibir un mensaje raro de Ross. Dijo que encendiera MTV. No sé.
- Oh, my God, look! That's Elizabeth! Ha-ha-ha.
- ¡Dios mío, mira! ¡Esa es Elizabeth! Jajaja.
Oh, oh, Professor Geller.
Oh, oh, Profesor Geller.
Ah, to be 13 again.
Ah, volver a tener 13 años.