- Hey, guys. I got some bad news. - What?
- Hola, chicos. Tengo malas noticias. - ¿Qué?
That's no way to sell newspapers. Try, "Extra! Extra! Read all about it!"
Esa no es forma de vender periódicos. Prueba: "¡Extra, extra! ¡Lean todo!".
No. Monica's restaurant got a horrible review in the Post.
No. El restaurante de Monica recibió una crítica horrible en el Post.
Oh, no!
¡Oh, no!
I didn't want her to see it, so I ran around and bought all the copies I could find.
No quería que lo viera, así que corrí y compré todas las copias que pude encontrar.
Man, this is bad. And I've had my share of bad reviews.
Hombre, esto es malo. Y yo he tenido mi cuota de críticas malas.
I still remember my first good one:
Todavía recuerdo mi primera buena:
"Everything else in this production of Our Town was simply terrible.
"Todo lo demás en esta producción de Our Town fue simplemente terrible.
Joey Tribbiani was abysmal."
Joey Tribbiani fue abismal."
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Oh, my God! Look at all the newspapers.
¡Dios mío! Mira todos los periódicos.
It must be a good review. Is it great?
Debe ser una buena crítica. ¿Es genial?
Um...
Oh, dear God.
Ay, Dios mío.
But the good news is, no one in a two-block radius will ever know.
Pero la buena noticia es que nadie en un radio de dos cuadras lo sabrá jamás.
- What about the rest of Manhattan? - Yeah, they all know.
- ¿Y el resto de Manhattan? - Sí, todos lo saben.
- Oh, my God, this is horrible. - I'm sorry.
- Dios mío, esto es horrible. - Lo siento.
I'm so humiliated.
Estoy tan humillada.
But you know what they say, there is no such thing as bad press.
Pero sabes lo que dicen, no hay mala prensa.
You don't think that, um, "the chef's mahi-mahi was awful-awful" is bad press?
¿Tú no crees que, eh, "el mahi-mahi del chef estaba horrible-horrible" es mala prensa?
I didn't write it.
Yo no lo escribí.
- God, is he right? Am I awful? - Oh, no!
- Dios, ¿es verdad? ¿Soy horrible? - ¡Oh, no!
Hey, Monica, listen to me, okay?
Oye, Monica, escúchame, ¿sí?
I'm not saying this because I'm your friend, I say it because it's true.
No te digo esto porque sea tu amiga, te lo digo porque es verdad.
Your food is abysmal!
¡Tu comida es abismal!
- Ross? - What? What?
- ¿Ross? - ¿Qué? ¿Qué?
- I am freaking out! - Are you?
¡Me estoy volviendo loca!
My due date is in one week!
¡Mi fecha de parto es en una semana!
- What are you doing up? - That is seven days.
- ¿Qué haces despierta? - Eso son siete días.
Look, I had a lot of water. Can we do this after...?
Mira, tomé mucha agua. ¿Podemos hacer esto después...?
No, no, no, no, Ross!
¡No, no, no, no, Ross!
Please, come on. We do not have any big stuff we need.
Por favor, vamos. No tenemos nada importante que necesitemos.
We don't have a changing table. We do not have a crib.
No tenemos cambiador. No tenemos cuna.
- We do not have a diaper service. - Funny you should mention diapers.
- No tenemos servicio de pañales. - Qué curioso que menciones pañales.
- I'm serious. - Look. There's nothing to worry about.
- Hablo en serio. - Mira. No hay nada de qué preocuparse.
We have plenty of time. There's a baby furniture store on West 10th.
Tenemos tiempo de sobra. Hay una tienda de muebles para bebés en West 10th.
Tomorrow, we'll go there...
Mañana iremos allí...
- ...and we'll get everything we need. Okay? - Okay. Thank you. That's great.
- ...y conseguiremos todo lo que necesitemos. ¿De acuerdo? - De acuerdo. Gracias. Eso es genial.
Wait, where on West 10th? There's a really cute shoe store...
Espera, ¿en qué parte de West 10th? Hay una tienda de zapatos muy linda...
Okay. If, uh... If you're gonna do this...
Está bien. Si, eh... Si vas a hacer esto...
...then I'm gonna go do that, so...
...entonces yo me voy a ir a hacer eso, así que...
- Wait, Ross! I'm sorry, one more thing. - Yeah.
- Espera, Ross. Lo siento, una cosa más. - Sí.
Um, our situation, you know, um, what we mean to each other...
Eh, nuestra situación, ya sabes, eh, lo que significamos el uno para el otro...
...and, I mean, we're having this baby together and we live together...
...y, quiero decir, vamos a tener este bebé juntos y vivimos juntos...
Isn't that...? Isn't that weird?
¿No es eso...? ¿No es eso raro?
Well, uh...
Bueno, eh...
- I'm just kidding. You can go pee. Ha, ha. - Oh...!
- Solo bromeo. Puedes ir a hacer pipí. Ja, ja. - Oh...!
Hey, I can't remember. Did we say we were gonna meet here...
Oye, no recuerdo. ¿Dijimos que nos íbamos a encontrar aquí...
- ...or at the movie? - At the movies...
- ...o en el cine? - En el cine...
- I'll see you there. - Joey. Now that you're here...?
- Te veo allí. - Joey. Ahora que estás aquí...?
Sure, I can hang out till I have to meet you.
[ERROR API]
- How come you're not going? - I've got a job interview to get ready for.
- I thought you already have a job. - And people say you don't pay attention.
[ERROR API]
This is a much better job. It's vice president of the company...
...that does data reconfiguration...
[ERROR API]
...and statistical factoring and for other companies.
- Wow. How do you know how to do that? - That's what I do now.
[ERROR API]
- Joey? Come taste this. - What is it?
Remember the guy that gave me a bad review? Well...
[ERROR API]
...I'm getting my revenge.
You cooked him?
[ERROR API]
No. He teaches a course on food criticism at The New School.
Before we go to the movies, I want to make him try my bouillabaisse again.
[ERROR API]
Ugh, I can't wait to read the front page tomorrow:
"Restaurant reviewer admits: 'I was wrong about Monica."'
[ERROR API]
The front page?
You really do live in your own little world, don't you?
[ERROR API]
Do you want these delivered, Mr. and Mrs. Geller?
- Oh, no, no, no. No, no. - Heh. No, no.
[ERROR API]
- We're not married. - We are having a baby together...
...but we're not involved.
[ERROR API]
I mean, uh, we... We were seeing each other a while ago...
...but then we were just friends, and then there was one drunken night...
[ERROR API]
Or, yes, stranger, we'd like this delivered, please.
- Why don't you fill out this address card? - Oh, okay.
[ERROR API]
- I noticed you picked out a lot of dinosaurs. - Oh, yeah.
That's one of the reasons why we are not a couple.
[ERROR API]
I chose those. I'm a paleontologist.
Really? That is so cool.
[ERROR API]
Oh, don't get too worked up over it. It sounds like he's a doctor, but he's not.
Oh, no. I'm fascinated by paleontology.
[ERROR API]
- Have you read the Walter Alvarez book? - Yeah, heh, I teach it in class.
Oh, my God. Standing at a cash register, I'm holding a credit card, and I'm bored.
[ERROR API]
I love your neighborhood. There's a great gym around the corner from your building.
- That's my gym. - I could tell you work out.
[ERROR API]
A paleontologist who works out. You're like Indiana Jones.
I am like Indiana Jones.
[ERROR API]
Hi, Pheebs.
Hola, Pheebs.
Hey! Oh, how did baby shopping go?
[ERROR API]
It was great! We got everything we needed.
Oh, and Ross almost got something that wasn't on the list.
[ERROR API]
Ahem, a whore.
- What? - We were paying for our stuff...
[ERROR API]
...and this sales woman just started flirting with him.
Can you believe that?
¿Puedes creerlo?
- Did she know you two weren't married? - Yeah.
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God. Well, the idea... A woman flirting with a single man?
- We must alert the church elders. - No.
[ERROR API]
You don't understand. You didn't see how brazen she was.
- Sounds like you're a little jealous. - No, I'm not.
[ERROR API]
I just think it's wrong. I mean, here I am, about to pop...
Simplemente creo que está mal. Quiero decir, aquí estoy yo, a punto de explotar...
...and he's out picking up some shopgirl at Sluts-R-Us?
...¿y él está saliendo con una dependienta de 'Chicas de Mala Muerte'?
Is that a real place?
¿Es un lugar real?
Are they hiring?
¿Están contratando?
- Hey, Phoebe. Fatty. - Wha...?
- Hola, Phoebe. Gordita. - ¿Qué...?
Hey, Chandler, why so fancy?
Oye, Chandler, ¿por qué tan elegante?
Well, I got a job interview. Big deal, too.
Bueno, tengo una entrevista de trabajo. Es importante.
It's more money. I'd be doing data reconfiguration and statistical factoring.
Es más dinero. Haría reconfiguración de datos y análisis estadístico.
- I think I know someone who does that. - Me. I do that.
- Creo que conozco a alguien que hace eso. - Yo. Yo hago eso.
So seriously, do I look okay? I'm nervous.
Entonces, en serio, ¿me veo bien? Estoy nerviosa.
Oh, yeah. You... Really, you look great.
Oh, sí. Tú... De verdad, te ves genial.
You know, just don't get your hopes up.
Solo no te hagas demasiadas ilusiones.
- Why not? - Well, the interview.
- ¿Por qué no? - Bueno, la entrevista.
- What about it? - You know.
- ¿Y qué con eso? - Ya sabes.
You don't make a very good first impression.
No das una muy buena primera impresión.
- What? - Oh, you don't know.
- ¿Qué? - Oh, no lo sabes.
- Are you serious? - Yes. When I first met you, you were like:
- ¿Hablas en serio? - Sí. Cuando te conocí, eras así:
I was like:
Yo era así:
Shh!
¡Shh!
What is it that I do?
¿Qué es lo que hago?
It's just, like, you're trying too hard, always making jokes.
Es solo que, te esfuerzas demasiado, siempre haciendo chistes.
You just... You come off a little needy.
Simplemente... Pareces un poco necesitada.
Did you like me when we first met?
¿Te caí bien cuando nos conocimos?
Chandler, I'm not gonna lie to you.
Chandler, no te voy a mentir.
But I am gonna run away from you.
Pero sí me voy a escapar de ti.
Hi. I'm Monica Geller, chef at Allessandro's.
Hola. Soy Monica Geller, chef en Allessandro's.
Still?
¿Todavía?
I think the things you said were unfair...
Creo que lo que dijiste fue injusto...
...and I would like you to give my bouillabaisse another chance.
...y me gustaría que le dieras otra oportunidad a mi bullabesa.
I don't see any reason why I'd do that to myself again.
No veo ninguna razón por la que me haría eso de nuevo.
Either eat it or be in it.
O cómetelo o métete en ello.
SP0on?
¿Cuchara?
- So, what do you think? - I'm torn...
- Entonces, ¿qué piensas? - Estoy dividida...
...between my integrity and my desire to avoid a beating.
...entre mi integridad y mi deseo de evitar una paliza.
But I must be honest. Your soup is abysmal.
Pero debo ser honesta. Tu sopa es pésima.
Thattagirll Eh? We should get out of here, there's a new class coming in.
Esa chica. ¿Eh? Deberíamos irnos, está entrando una nueva clase.
Welcome to Introduction to Cooking. Before we start...
Bienvenidos a Introducción a la Cocina. Antes de empezar...
...can anyone tell me the difference between hollandaise and béarnaise sauce?
...¿alguien puede decirme la diferencia entre la salsa holandesa y la bearnesa?
- I can. - Okay, go ahead.
- Yo puedo. - De acuerdo, adelante.
Well, um, they both have a egg yolk and butter base.
Bueno, eh, ambas tienen una base de yema de huevo y mantequilla.
But a béarnaise, um, has shallots, chervil, and most importantly, tarragon.
Pero la bearnesa, eh, tiene chalotas, perifollo y, lo más importante, estragón.
- Ha, ha, very good. What's your name? - Monica.
- Ja, ja, muy bien. ¿Cómo te llamas? - Monica.
- Monica, you go to the head of the class! - Okay!
- ¡Monica, tú a la cabeza de la clase! - ¡De acuerdo!
All this stuff takes up a lot of room.
Todas estas cosas ocupan mucho espacio.
Hey, how, uh, serious are you about keeping Ben in your life?
Oye, ¿qué tan seria eres acerca de mantener a Ben en tu vida?
My son? Pretty serious.
¿Mi hijo? Muy seria.
Oh, hey, Katie. What are you doing here?
Oh, hola, Katie. ¿Qué haces aquí?
The delivery went out and I realized they forgot this.
Salió el pedido y me di cuenta de que olvidaron esto.
Ah, it must have been obvious, since it was the only thing left in your store.
Ah, debió ser obvio, ya que era lo único que quedaba en tu tienda.
Listen, to be honest, home deliveries aren't really part of my job description.
Mira, para ser honesta, las entregas a domicilio no son realmente parte de mi descripción de trabajo.
Oh.
Oh, um, I actually came here to ask you out.
Oh, eh, en realidad vine a invitarte a salir.
Oh. Wow. Uh, yeah, that sounds great.
Oh. Vaya. Eh, sí, suena genial.
I'm just gonna put this back in my pocket and pretend that didn't happen.
Voy a guardar esto en mi bolsillo y pretender que eso no pasó.
Uh, I'm free now. You want to grab some coffee...?
Eh, estoy libre ahora. ¿Quieres ir por un café...?
- Sure. - Horny bitch.
- Claro. - Perra caliente.
No, you're a horny bitch! No, you're a horny bitch!
¡No, tú eres una perra caliente! ¡No, tú eres una perra caliente!
No, you're a horny bitch!
¡No, tú eres una perra caliente!
So you guys go, have a really good time.
Así que ustedes vayan, pásenla muy bien.
I'm just gonna grab my coat. And, uh, my whip.
Solo voy a buscar mi abrigo. Y, eh, mi látigo.
You know, because of Indiana Jones.
Ya sabes, por Indiana Jones.
Not because I'm into S&M.
No porque me guste el S&M.
I'm not into anything weird, you know? Heh.
No me gustan las cosas raras, ¿sabes? Je.
Just normal sex.
Solo sexo normal.
So I'm gonna grab my coat.
Así que voy a buscar mi abrigo.
So you had a good day, huh? Big commission, picked up a daddy.
Así que tuviste un buen día, ¿eh? Gran comisión, conseguiste un papá.
Are you okay with this?
¿Estás bien con eso?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please. You guys have fun.
Oh, sí. Sí, por favor. Ustedes diviértanse.
- Okay. Heh. - Yeah.
- Okay. Je. - Sí.
It was nice to see you.
Fue un placer verte.
Oh, and it was great to see you too. And you look fantastic.
Oh, y fue genial verte también. Y te ves fantástica.
- Ah, heh. - Although you missed a button.
- Ah, je. - Aunque te faltó un botón.
Oh, actually, I, um...
Oh, en realidad, yo, eh...
Oh, okay, I see what you're doing there.
Oh, okay, ya veo lo que estás haciendo ahí.
I can't even believe this. I really come off that badly?
Ni siquiera puedo creer esto. ¿Realmente salgo tan mal?
Ugh, it's okay. You calm down after a while...
Ugh, está bien. Te calmas después de un rato...
...and then people can see how sweet and wonderful you are.
...y entonces la gente puede ver lo dulce y maravillosa que eres.
Good. Because I'm sure this interview's gonna last a couple of weeks.
Bien. Porque estoy segura de que esta entrevista durará un par de semanas.
All right, don't freak out, okay? I will help you.
Está bien, no te asustes, ¿vale? Te ayudaré.
- How long before you have to leave? - An hour.
- ¿Cuánto tiempo antes de que tengas que irte? - Una hora.
- I can't help you. - Phoebe...
- No puedo ayudarte. - Phoebe...
We'll do our best. I'm the interviewer and I'm meeting you for the first time.
Haremos lo mejor que podamos. Yo soy la entrevistadora y te conozco por primera vez.
- Okay. - Hi. Come on in. I'm Regina Phalanges.
- Okay. - Hola. Pasa. Soy Regina Phalanges.
- Chandler Bing. - Oh, Bing.
- What an unusual name. - Well, you should meet my Uncle Bada.
- Qué nombre tan inusual. - Bueno, deberías conocer a mi tío Bada.
I'll let myself out.
Me iré sola.
H93'-
Your alfredo's dry. Did you use your cheese?
Tu alfredo está seco. ¿Usaste tu queso?
When you say "use," do you mean "eat as a pre-cooking snack"?
Cuando dices "usar", ¿quieres decir "comer como aperitivo antes de cocinar"?
- And the cream? - Cheese makes me thirsty.
- ¿Y la crema? - El queso me da sed.
- Okay. Let's move on. - All right.
- Okay. Sigamos. - De acuerdo.
Oh. Something smells good over at Monica's station.
Oh. Algo huele bien en la estación de Monica.
My God! This is absolutely amazing! You've never made this before?
¡Dios mío! ¡Esto es absolutamente increíble! ¿Nunca habías hecho esto antes?
Oh, no. I don't know anything about cooking.
Oh, no. No sé nada de cocina.
I had to ask what it was called when the water makes those bubbles.
Tuve que preguntar cómo se llamaba cuando el agua hace esas burbujas.
Wow. Hats off to the chef.
Vaya. Mis respetos al chef.
I'm sorry, your mouth was full. I didn't hear what you said.
Lo siento, tenías la boca llena. No oí lo que dijiste.
- Hats off to who now? - The chef!
- ¿Mis respetos a quién ahora? - ¡Al chef!
Heh, that's right!
¡Je, así es!
I think you'll find if I work here that I don't micromanage.
Creo que descubrirás que si trabajo aquí, no seré una microgestora.
I don't shy away from delegating.
No me da miedo delegar.
Mm-hm. That's good to know. But let's stop focusing on what you don't do...
Mm-hm. Eso es bueno saberlo. Pero dejemos de enfocarnos en lo que no haces...
...and focus on what you do do.
...y enfoquémonos en lo que sí haces.
What I do do...
Lo que sí hago...
...is manage to, uh, create an atmosphere of support...
...es lograr, eh, crear una atmósfera de apoyo...
...for the people working with me.
...para la gente que trabaja conmigo.
I see. Nice sidestep on the "do do" thing.
Ya veo. Buena evasiva con lo de "hacer hacer".
- Hardest thing I've ever done in my life. - Oh, you gotta go!
- Lo más difícil que he hecho en mi vida. - ¡Oh, tienes que ir!
- Okay, don't worry. You're ready. - Really?
- Está bien, no te preocupes. Estás listo. - ¿En serio?
Absolutely! Just fight all your natural instincts, and you'll be great.
¡Absolutamente! Solo lucha contra todos tus instintos naturales y estarás genial.
Ah, Monica, my star student.
Ah, Monica, mi alumna estrella.
Heh. You called me that before...
Je. Me llamaste así antes...
...so I took the liberty of fashioning a star out of foil.
...así que me tomé la libertad de hacer una estrella de papel de aluminio.
Now, no pressure. If you like my cookies, you give me the star.
Ahora, sin presión. Si te gustan mis galletas, me das la estrella.
Mm. Mm-mm-mm.
Wow, a star!
¡Vaya, una estrella!
I know you all hate me, and I'm sorry, but I don't care.
Sé que todos me odian, y lo siento, pero no me importa.
- Okay, Joey, you're up next. - Yeah.
- Está bien, Joey, tú sigues. - Sí.
Oh, my God! This is amazing!
¡Oh, Dios mío! ¡Esto es increíble!
You get an A.
Tienes un A.
I got an A? In school? Hey, I'm a dork!
¿Tengo una A? ¿En la escuela? ¡Oye, soy un nerd!
Joey, I'm so proud of you.
Joey, estoy tan orgulloso de ti.
- I think you should give him your star. - Excuse me?
- Creo que deberías darle tu estrella. - ¿Disculpa?
- He doesn't even know what he's doing. - We're all beginners.
- Ni siquiera sabe lo que está haciendo. - Todos somos principiantes.
- Nobody knows what they're doing. - I do. I'm a professional chef!
- Nadie sabe lo que está haciendo. - Yo sí. ¡Soy un chef profesional!
Oh, relax. It's not a courtroom drama.
Oh, relájate. No es un drama judicial.
What are you doing taking Introduction to Cooking?
¿Qué haces tomando Introducción a la Cocina?
Yeah!
¡Sí!
I'm sorry. It's just that, um, I cook at this restaurant, Allessandrds...
Lo siento. Es que, eh, cocino en este restaurante, Allessandrds...
...and, um, I just got a really bad review.
...y, eh, acabo de recibir una crítica muy mala.
- Oh, Allessandro's? I love that place! - You do?
- ¿Oh, Alessandro's? ¡Me encanta ese lugar! - ¿De verdad?
Yes, you're an excellent chef. As a person you're a little...
Sí, eres un chef excelente. Como persona eres un poco...
- Oh, totally crazy, but you liked the food? - Ha, ha. Very much.
- Oh, totalmente loco, ¿pero te gustó la comida? - Ja, ja. Muchísimo.
Okay, then. I don't stink. I'm a good chef! Okay.
Está bien, entonces. No apesto. ¡Soy un buen chef! Está bien.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I don't want to go. I'm having fun.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no quiero ir. Me estoy divirtiendo.
Actually, did either of you pay for this class?
De hecho, ¿alguno de ustedes pagó por esta clase?
Hey, if my friend says it's time to go, it's time to go!
¡Oye, si mi amigo dice que es hora de irse, es hora de irse!
Also, I was the point person on my company's transition...
Además, yo fui la persona encargada de la transición de mi empresa...
...from the KL5 to GR6 systems.
...de los sistemas KL5 a GR6.
- You must have had your hands full. - That I did. That I did.
- Debiste tener mucho trabajo. - Sí que lo tuve. Sí que lo tuve.
So let's talk a little bit about your duties.
Así que hablemos un poco de tus funciones.
My duties?
¿Mis funciones?
All right.
De acuerdo.
You'll be heading a whole division, so you'll have a lot of duties.
Dirigirás toda una división, así que tendrás muchas funciones.
- I see. - But there'll be 30 people under you...
- Ya veo. - Pero tendrás 30 personas a tu cargo...
...so you can dump a certain amount on them.
...así que puedes descargarles una cierta cantidad.
- Good to know. - We could go into detail...
- Bueno saberlo. - Podríamos entrar en detalles...
No, don't, I beg of you.
No, no lo hagas, te lo ruego.
All right, then. We'll have a definite answer for you on Monday.
Está bien, entonces. Tendremos una respuesta definitiva para ti el lunes.
But I can say with some confidence, you'll fit in well here.
Pero puedo decir con cierta confianza, encajarás bien aquí.
- Really? - Absolutely.
- ¿En serio? - Absolutamente.
- You can relax. You did great. - I gotta say, thank you.
- Puedes relajarte. Lo hiciste genial. - Tengo que decir, gracias.
I was really nervous. I'm told I come on too strongly, too many jokes.
Estaba muy nervioso. Me dicen que soy demasiado directo, que hago demasiados chistes.
And then it was really hard to side step that "duty" thing.
Y luego fue muy difícil esquivar esa cosa del "deber".
Duties?
¿Deberes?
Doodies?
¿Cacas?
Poo?
¿Caca?
Oh, my God. This doesn't count. Okay? The interview was over.
Dios mío. Esto no cuenta. ¿Vale? La entrevista ya había terminado.
That was the real Chandler Bing. This is some crazy guy in the hall.
Ese era el verdadero Chandler Bing. Este es un loco en el pasillo.
Call security! There's a crazy guy out in the hall!
¡Llamen a seguridad! ¡Hay un loco en el pasillo!
Poo?
¿Caca?
I'll look forward to your call.
Espero tu llamada.
_H6Y- _H6Y-
- You're back from your date. - How are you?
- ¿Regresaste de tu cita? - ¿Cómo estás?
I'm fine. But that's not important. What's important is how was she?
Estoy bien. Pero eso no es importante. Lo importante es, ¿cómo estuvo ella?
Uh, it was fun. We just had coffee.
Uh, fue divertido. Solo tomamos café.
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh, coffee, a little rub-rub-rub under the table?
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh, ¿café, un poquito de masajito debajo de la mesa?
Heh, what's going on? Do you not like Katie?
Je, ¿qué pasa? ¿No te cae bien Katie?
No. No, she was nice.
No. No, ella era simpática.
I mean, she was a little slutty, but who isn't?
Quiero decir, era un poco fácil, pero ¿quién no lo es?
Well, I liked her.
Bueno, a mí me gustó.
Of course you did. You'd date a gorilla if it called you Indiana Jones.
Claro que sí. Te saldrías con un gorila si te llamara Indiana Jones.
Did you get a fresh batch of pregnancy hormones today?
¿Recibiste un nuevo lote de hormonas del embarazo hoy?
No. It's just that... Katie bothered me.
No. Es solo que... Katie me molestó.
Why? What was wrong with her?
¿Por qué? ¿Qué tenía de malo?
Ugh, there was nothing wrong with her. All right? She was perfectly lovely.
Ugh, no tenía nada de malo. ¿Vale? Era perfectamente encantadora.
- Okay. So, what's the matter? - I don't want you to date her.
- Vale. Entonces, ¿qué pasa? - No quiero que salgas con ella.
Heh, what? Why? What, are you jealous?
Je, ¿qué? ¿Por qué? ¿Estás celoso?
Yes. And not because I want you to go out with me.
Sí. Y no porque quiera que salgas conmigo.
Because I don't want you to go out with anybody.
Porque no quiero que salgas con nadie.
I know it's a terrible thing to even think this and it's inappropriate...
Sé que es algo terrible incluso pensarlo y es inapropiado...
...but I want you to be at my constant beck and call, 24 hours a day.
...pero quiero que estés a mi entera disposición, las 24 horas del día.
I'm very sorry, but that is just the way that I feel.
Lo siento mucho, pero así es como me siento.
- Okay. - What?
- De acuerdo. - ¿Qué?
I won't date. I'll, uh...
No saldré con nadie. Yo, eh...
I'll be here with you all the time.
Estaré aquí contigo todo el tiempo.
Really?
¿En serio?
But I'm being so unreasonable.
Pero estoy siendo muy irrazonable.
True, but you're allowed to be unreasonable. You're having our baby.
Cierto, pero tienes derecho a ser irrazonable. Estás esperando a nuestro bebé.
Oh...
Oh, Ross, thank you. Thank you.
Oh, Ross, gracias. Gracias.
You feel better?
¿Te sientes mejor?
No, not really. You're pressing the baby into my bladder...
No, no realmente. Estás apretando al bebé contra mi vejiga...
...and now I have to pee. Sorry.
...y ahora tengo que hacer pipí. Perdón.
- Okay. - Rash?
- Vale. - ¿Rash?
- Yeah? - Just one thing. Um...
- ¿Sí? - Solo una cosa. Um...
We live together. You're having our baby. I'm not gonna see anybody else.
Vivimos juntos. Estás esperando a nuestro bebé. No voy a ver a nadie más.
Are you sure you don't want something more?
¿Estás segura de que no quieres algo más?
Wow. I don't know, maybe...
Vaya. No sé, tal vez...
Oh, Rach, I was just messing around. Heh.
Ay, Rach, solo estaba bromeando. Je.
- Like you did when I had to pee? - Oh! Ha! I knew that.
- ¿Como cuando tuve que ir al baño? - ¡Ay! ¡Ja! Lo sabía.
I knew that! I was just messing with you too!
¡Lo sabía! ¡Yo también te estaba bromeando!
Okay. Because for a minute you seemed...
Está bien. Porque por un minuto parecías...
- No, no, no, no. No! It's just... Ha! - ...like you actually...
- No, no, no, no. ¡No! Es solo... ¡Ja! - ...como si en realidad...
That's just because I'm such a good messer!
¡Eso es solo porque soy muy buena bromeando!
Ah! Ah, heh.
Ah. Ah, je.
- Rash? - Yeah?
- ¿Rash? - ¿Sí?
- The bathroom? - Right.
- ¿El baño? - Correcto.
I had a great time. I learned how to bake, ate great food.
La pasé muy bien. Aprendí a hornear, comí buena comida.
The first A I've gotten since 7th grade and I didn't have to sleep with the teacher.
La primera A que saco desde séptimo grado y no tuve que acostarme con el profesor.
- Oh, look. Acting for Beginners. - Yeah.
- Oh, mira. Actuación para principiantes. - Sí.
Wanna feel good about yourself?
¿Quieres sentirte bien contigo mismo?
- What the hell! - Okay.
- ¡Qué demonios! - Está bien.
All right, let's start with some basics.
Muy bien, empecemos con lo básico.
Can anybody tell me what the difference between upstage and downstage is?
¿Alguien puede decirme cuál es la diferencia entre el fondo y el proscenio?
Yeah, this was a stupid idea.
Sí, esta fue una idea estúpida.