All right!
¡Genial!
Yes! From home to the hospital in seven minutes!
[ERROR API]
Yes. The hard part is truly over.
We're off to a great start, aren't we?
[ERROR API]
I knew I'd get here fast, but this has to be a record!
- Oh, you made it! - Hi.
[ERROR API]
- How the hell did you beat us here? - We took a cab. Did you walk?
No, we took a cab too. But I did test runs...
[ERROR API]
- Hi. - Hey, you made it!
Okay, is there some kind of magic tunnel to this hospital?
[ERROR API]
Ross, you stay here and talk. I'm gonna go have a baby.
Okay. Hi, this is Rachel Green. I'm Ross Geller. We called from the car.
[ERROR API]
We have a semi-private labor room waiting...
Oh, whoa! I'm sorry. Semi-private? We asked for a private room.
[ERROR API]
Yes, I see that here. We can't guarantee a private room.
- Currently, they're all unavailable. - Man, if only you'd gotten here sooner.
[ERROR API]
I'm sorry. Semi-private rooms are all we have.
Okay. Just give us a second. Ross?
[ERROR API]
Yeah?
¿Sí?
- Give her some money. - I really think they're out of rooms.
[ERROR API]
They're saving them for important people! What if I was the president?
We'd be in a lot of trouble. You don't know where any countries are.
[ERROR API]
Okay.
Say, would you mind checking again?
[ERROR API]
See if any, uh, private rooms may have opened up?
This is a hospital.
[ERROR API]
You know what? I don't really care for your tone.
This is not the only hospital in the city. We have no problem... Whoa. Oh, gosh!
[ERROR API]
- What, what? - Contraction! Ow! Ow!
- Oh! - Ow, ow, ow, ow. Ooh, ooh.
[ERROR API]
- Like to see a semi-private room? - Yeah, it couldn't hurt to look.
You're 2 centimeters dilated. We need to get to 10.
[ERROR API]
- It will be a while. - Oh, okay.
- I'll be back in an hour to check on you. - Thank you.
[ERROR API]
- I guess we have some time to kill. - Yeah, guess so.
- Oh, check these out. - Oh.
[ERROR API]
Never done this before.
Yeah, well, it looks great.
[ERROR API]
Thank you very much. I think we're ready to...
Hi, I'm Ross. I'm here to ruin this magical day for you.
[ERROR API]
- Not at all. Marc Horger. My wife, Julie. - Don't worry about it.
- Hi, Julie. This is Rachel. - Oh, hi, Rachel.
[ERROR API]
- Is this your first? - It is.
- Well, little Jamie here is our third. - Wow.
[ERROR API]
So if you have any questions, just holler.
- That's so sweet. - Yeah.
[ERROR API]
- Let me give you guys some privacy. - Nonsense. We're all in this together.
We are gonna share every moment of this with you.
[ERROR API]
- I think we're gonna have some fun. - Yeah.
- Oh, okay, I guess. - Hey, smile!
[ERROR API]
- No. - I really don't want any...
- No. - De verdad no quiero nada...
Oh, thank you.
Oh, gracias.
Oh, Ross. Here comes another contraction.
Oh, Ross. Aquí viene otra contracción.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh... - Okay, just breathe...
- Ooh, ooh, ooh... - Okay, solo respira...
- Oh, honey, I think I'm having one too! - Oh, my God!
- Oh, cariño, ¡creo que estoy teniendo una también! - ¡Dios mío!
- Ow, ow, ow, ow. - Oh, oh, oh.
- Ay, ay, ay, ay. - Oh, oh, oh.
- Hey, look at this. Here you go! - Oh, no!
- Oye, mira esto. ¡Aquí tienes! - ¡Oh, no!
Oh, wow. Three hours and still no baby.
Vaya. Tres horas y todavía no hay bebé.
Ugh, the miracle of birth sure is a snooze-fest.
Uf, el milagro del nacimiento es un rollo.
- Hey, you wanna see something? - Sure. What?
- Oye, ¿quieres ver algo? - Claro. ¿Qué?
This will be fun. Watch me freak out Chandler.
Esto será divertido. Mírame asustar a Chandler.
- Honey? - Yeah?
- Cariño? - ¿Sí?
Listen, uh, I've been doing some thinking...
Escucha, eh, he estado pensando...
...and I don't know whether it's because we're here...
...y no sé si es porque estamos aquí...
...or Rachel's giving birth...
...o porque Rachel está dando a luz...
...but, um, I think we should try to have a baby.
...pero, um, creo que deberíamos intentar tener un bebé.
Okay.
What's that now?
¿Qué dices ahora?
Okay. I've been thinking about it too. I think we're ready.
Okay. Yo también he estado pensando en eso. Creo que estamos listos.
Are you kidding? You think we're ready to have a baby?
¿Estás bromeando? ¿Crees que estamos listos para tener un bebé?
Oh, this is fun.
Oh, esto es divertido.
You're ready to have a baby? My boy's all grown up!
¿Estás listo para tener un bebé? ¡Mi niño ya es todo un hombre!
You said you were ready.
Dijiste que estabas listo.
I was screwing with you to get your voice high and weird...
Te estaba tomando el pelo para que tu voz se pusiera aguda y rara...
...like mine is now!
...¡como la mía ahora!
Yes, but haven't you wanted a kid forever?
Sí, pero ¿no has querido un hijo para siempre?
Okay, just back oh', mister!
Okay, ¡ya basta, señor!
Because I am ready to have a baby.
Porque yo sí estoy lista para tener un bebé.
I just want Joey to be the father.
Solo quiero que Joey sea el padre.
- What? Are you crazy? - Right there! That's all I wanted!
- ¿Qué? ¿Estás loco? - ¡Ahí mismo! ¡Eso es todo lo que quería!
I'm sorry. The doctor insisted on closing the curtain for the exam.
Lo siento. El doctor insistió en cerrar la cortina para el examen.
Oh, that's very... Really, very, very okay.
Oh, eso está muy... De verdad, muy, muy bien.
Julie's cervix is dilated 7 centimeters. That's about four fingers!
El cérvix de Julie está dilatado 7 centímetros. ¡Son como cuatro dedos!
- Doctor let me feel it. - Have you felt Rachel's?
- Doctor, déjeme sentirlo. - ¿Has sentido el de Rachel?
- No, I don't... - We won't be doing that.
- No, yo no... - No haremos eso.
Well, you could feel Rachel's, then feel mine to compare.
Bueno, podrías sentir el de Rachel y luego sentir el mío para comparar.
- Am I interrupting? - Yes! Thank you!
- ¿Estoy interrumpiendo? - ¡Sí! ¡Gracias!
- No, no... - Later.
- No, no... - Luego.
- You can't leave me with them. - Sorry.
- No puedes dejarme con ellos. - Lo siento.
No, Ross, Ross? Ross? My child has no father!
No, Ross, ¿Ross? ¿Ross? ¡Mi hijo no tiene padre!
I'm so glad you're here, but it's gonna be a while. I wish you'd called first.
Me alegra mucho que estés aquí, pero va a tardar. Ojalá hubieras llamado antes.
- I'm coming back later with your father. - Oh, good.
- Vuelvo más tarde con tu padre. - Oh, bien.
- I need to talk to you before the birth. - Okay. What's up?
- Necesito hablar contigo antes del parto. - Okay. ¿Qué pasa?
I brought something that I want to give you.
Traje algo que quiero darte.
Assuming, of course, that you want it.
Asumiendo, claro, que lo quieras.
Ma, you're asking me to marry you?
¿Mamá, me estás pidiendo que me case contigo?
Your grandma's engagement ring, I want you to give it to Rachel.
El anillo de compromiso de tu abuela, quiero que se lo des a Rachel.
- Mom, no. Come on. Thank you... - Just hear me out...
- Mamá, no. Vamos. Gracias... - Solo escúchame...
No! Okay? We're not getting married because she's pregnant.
¡No! ¿Okay? No nos vamos a casar porque ella esté embarazada.
Honestly, this isn't just some girl you picked up in a bar and humped.
Honestamente, esta no es solo una chica que recogiste en un bar y te la tiraste.
A child should have a family.
Un niño debería tener una familia.
I can't deal with this now. I'm sorry.
No puedo lidiar con esto ahora. Lo siento.
Think about it. If you don't, I'll talk more about humping.
Piénsalo. Si no lo haces, hablaré más sobre el acto sexual.
Give me that.
Dámela.
- Hi, dear. - Hi. Thank you so much for coming.
- Hola, cariño. - Hola. Muchas gracias por venir.
Ross, get in here!
¡Ross, entra aquí!
She dragged me out of the labor room to ask me why I'm not with Rachel.
Me sacó de la sala de partos para preguntarme por qué no estoy con Rachel.
Yeah.
Sí.
- Why aren't you with Rachel? - Are you kidding?
- ¿Por qué no estás con Rachel? - ¿Me estás bromeando?
We're not gonna be together because we're having a baby.
No vamos a estar juntos porque vamos a tener un bebé.
It seems you belong together.
Parece que ustedes pertenecen juntos.
I can't deal with this right now. I have to go have a baby.
No puedo lidiar con esto ahora. Tengo que ir a tener un bebé.
Right. And with who again?
Cierto. ¿Y con quién era?
He's crazy. Why doesn't he wanna be with Rachel?
Está loco. ¿Por qué no quiere estar con Rachel?
I know.
Lo sé.
She's like the perfect woman. I know she turned me down...
Ella es como la mujer perfecta. Sé que me rechazó...
...but if she wanted to be with me, I would take her in my arms and...
...pero si ella quisiera estar conmigo, la tomaría en mis brazos y...
I haven't bummed you guys out like this in a while.
No los he desanimado así en un tiempo.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- Who's that? - New people.
- ¿Quiénes son? - Gente nueva.
What happened to the Disgustingtons?
¿Qué pasó con los Disgustingtons?
They're having their baby. It's not fair, Ross. I got here first!
Están teniendo a su bebé. No es justo, Ross. ¡Yo llegué primero!
After you left, they wheeled her off.
Después de que te fuiste, se la llevaron.
Not before she gave me a nice, juicy shot of little Jamie, crowning away.
No sin antes darme una buena y jugosa toma del pequeño Jamie, asomando.
- Wow. Sorry. - Ugh.
- Vaya. Lo siento. - Uf.
So, uh, how are the new people?
Entonces, eh, ¿cómo son los nuevos?
Well, they have some unusual pet names for each other.
Bueno, tienen nombres de mascotas un poco inusuales para el otro.
Including, um, "Evil Bitch" and, uh, "Sick Bastard."
Incluyendo, um, "Bitch Maligna" y, eh, "Bastardo Enfermo".
- Oh, gosh, a contraction. Ooh, ow! - Yeah? Okay, okay. Just breathe.
- Oh, Dios, una contracción. ¡Ay, ay! - ¿Sí? Ok, ok. Solo respira.
- Are you looking at her? - No!
- ¿La estás mirando? - ¡No!
- Don't look at her, you sick bastard! - I swear I wasn't looking at her!
- ¡No la mires, bastardo enfermo! - ¡Juro que no la estaba mirando!
She's in labor. You like that, you sick son of a bitch?
Ella está de parto. ¿Te gusta eso, hijo de puta?
I'm just gonna...
Solo voy a...
See? It's because you were looking, you fat pervert.
¿Ves? Es porque la estabas mirando, pervertido gordo.
No, no. I'm sure no one was looking. Just want some privacy.
No, no. Estoy seguro de que nadie estaba mirando. Solo quiero algo de privacidad.
You miss your girlfriend?
¿Extrañas a tu novia?
- Just ignore them. - Ugh.
- Solo ignóralos. - Uf.
- You okay? - Yeah.
- ¿Estás bien? - Sí.
- Ross. - What?
- Ross. - ¿Qué?
- He's looking at me. - Hey!
- Me está mirando. - ¡Oye!
Wanna live to see your baby?
¿Quieres vivir para ver a tu bebé?
Don't you talk to my husband like that, you stupid bastard!
¡No le hables así a mi esposo, estúpido bastardo!
Oh, good God! If you want a baby so bad, just go steal it!
¡Oh, Dios mío! Si quieres un bebé tanto, ¡solo ve y róbalo!
Since when are you so crazy about babies?
¿Desde cuándo estás tan loco por los bebés?
I'm not crazy about babies. I'm crazy about us.
No estoy loco por los bebés. Estoy loco por nosotros.
What?
¿Qué?
We talk about having babies someday, not now...
Hablamos de tener bebés algún día, no ahora...
...but I'm starting to think that we can handle it. We're good.
...pero estoy empezando a pensar que podemos manejarlo. Somos buenos.
We're really good.
Somos realmente buenos.
We are pretty good.
Somos bastante buenos.
But nothing has to happen until you're ready.
[ERROR API]
Well, maybe I'm ready now.
I mean, it's a little scary, but maybe it's right.
[ERROR API]
It's not right! We're not ready for a kid!
- What? - I'm kidding. This is gonna be fun.
[ERROR API]
So we're gonna try? I mean, we're trying?
We're trying to get pregnant.
[ERROR API]
Mm.
I'm not comfortable doing this in front of the babies.
[ERROR API]
- So when do you want to start trying? - All right, hold on a sec.
- Period math? - Yeah.
[ERROR API]
Well, we could start trying now.
- Right here? - No, not here.
- ¿Justo aquí? - No, no aquí.
Maybe here.
Quizás aquí.
We got time to kill. We're in a building that's full of beds!
[ERROR API]
And it's so clean!
Come on, you stupid machine! Come on!
[ERROR API]
- Aw, it ate your money? - No.
- I'll see you downstairs then. - All right.
[ERROR API]
All right.
De acuerdo.
Hey, I got one! I got one!
[ERROR API]
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
- Oh, up or down'? - Oh. Down, please.
[ERROR API]
I hate to be a ball-buster, but can I just do it?
- Could you press up too? - Sure.
[ERROR API]
- I feel bad. I broke my leg once too. - How did yours happen?
It's a long, embarrassing story.
[ERROR API]
Let's just say, there was a typographical error with a sex manual.
- How about you? - Car accident.
[ERROR API]
- Idiot on a cell not paying attention? - Yeah. Me.
- Oh, hey, that's me. - Okay.
[ERROR API]
Hey, uh, I take it you're just visiting someone.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Ajá. Sí.
Well, um, if you have some time, and you wanna visit someone else...
[ERROR API]
Yeah. I would like that.
- Great. I'm in room... - Wait! What? No! Elevator! No!
[ERROR API]
You gotta press the button.
They're bringing in another woman.
[ERROR API]
Ugh. Is she pregnant yet?
She doesn't need to be. She'll still have the baby before I do.
[ERROR API]
- Oh, Ross! Another contraction. - Oh, okay. Here, here.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh, ow, ooh, ow! - That's it.
[ERROR API]
- Oh, that sounded like a bad one. - Yeah, it was.
Mine haven't been so bad. Oh, here comes one now.
[ERROR API]
Mm, mm.
Oh, that was a big one.
[ERROR API]
Could you help me'? The patient I'm looking for has a broken leg.
He's in a wheelchair. He's early to mid-30$, very attractive.
[ERROR API]
- I know who you're talking about. - Yay! Great! What room is he in?
Sorry. That information is restricted.
[ERROR API]
- She's with me. Dr. Drake Ramoray. - Dr. Drake who?
- Está conmigo. Dr. Drake Ramoray. - ¿Dr. Drake quién?
Ramoray. It's Portuguese. We need that information. I'm a doctor.
Ramoray. Es portugués. Necesitamos esa información. Soy doctor.
- At this hospital? - Damn it! We're losing precious time.
- ¿En este hospital? - ¡Maldición! Estamos perdiendo tiempo valioso.
You want this man's blood on your head...
Quieres la sangre de este hombre en tu conciencia...
- Hands. - Hands.
- Manos. - Manos.
It is essential that you tell me what room he is staying in.
Es esencial que me diga en qué habitación se está quedando.
He's a patient of mine.
Es un paciente mío.
- He's in room 816. - 816. Thank you.
- Está en la habitación 816. - 816. Gracias.
- And what is his name? - No.
- ¿Y cómo se llama? - No.
- I think we found a place. - Okay.
- Creo que encontramos un lugar. - De acuerdo.
- Wait. Wanna set the mood a little? - Okay.
- Espera. ¿Quieres crear un poco de ambiente? - De acuerdo.
- We'll dim the lights. - Okay.
- Atenuaremos las luces. - De acuerdo.
Or turn them out altogether.
O apagarlas por completo.
Uh, no scented candles. Okay, here. There we go.
Uh, no velas aromáticas. De acuerdo, aquí. Ahí está.
Okay, okay. Making me sterile, but okay.
Okay, okay. Me estás volviendo estéril, pero está bien.
Okay. I'm sorry. Oh, wait. Do we have a condom?
Okay. Lo siento. Oh, espera. ¿Tenemos condón?
Oh, right! Ha, ha.
¡Oh, claro! Ja, ja.
Yes, 98.6. You're gonna be fine.
Sí, 37. Vas a estar bien.
Ooh, this is it!
¡Ooh, aquí es!
- That's him! - Great. Go get him!
- ¡Ese es él! - Genial. ¡Ve por él!
Wait a second. Or maybe you could go in first.
Espera un segundo. O tal vez podrías entrar tú primero.
He's not really my type.
Él no es realmente mi tipo.
Not you. Dr. Ramoray. Ask him questions and see what he's like.
No tú. El Dr. Ramoray. Hazle preguntas y ve cómo es.
- People tell doctors everything. - You said he's great.
- La gente les cuenta todo a los doctores. - Dijiste que es genial.
Guys I meet seem nice at first, then turn out to be big jerks.
Los chicos que conozco parecen agradables al principio, y luego resultan ser unos imbéciles.
- You do attract some stinkers. - I know.
- Sí que atraes a unos patanes. - Lo sé.
Dr. Long, I've been at this for 17 hours.
Dr. Long, he estado en esto por 17 horas.
Three women have had their babies.
Tres mujeres han dado a luz.
Give me good news. How many centimeters am I dilated? Eight? Nine?
Dame buenas noticias. ¿Cuántos centímetros tengo de dilatación? ¿Ocho? ¿Nueve?
- Three. - Just 3?
- Tres. - ¿Solo 3?
I'm dilated 3!
¡Tengo 3 de dilatación!
We are moving along slowly. Don't worry, you're doing great.
Estamos avanzando lentamente. No te preocupes, lo estás haciendo genial.
- I'll be back soon. - Thank you.
- Volveré pronto. - Gracias.
I'm not waiting. I'm gonna push this baby out.
No voy a esperar. Voy a dar a luz a este bebé.
I'm doing it. Three centimeters. That's gotta be like this, right?
Lo estoy haciendo. Tres centímetros. Tiene que ser así, ¿verdad?
- Actually, it's more like this. - Oh, stupid metric system.
- En realidad, es más así. - Oh, estúpido sistema métrico.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
¡Oh! ¡Oh! ¡Oh!
We'll take you straight to the delivery room.
Te llevaremos directamente a la sala de partos.
Oh, for the love of God!
¡Oh, por el amor de Dios!
I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray. I have a few routine questions I need to ask you.
Soy el Dr. Drake Ramoray. Tengo algunas preguntas de rutina que necesito hacerle.
I've been dealing with Dr. Wells.
He estado tratando con la Dra. Wells.
I know. I'm a neurologist. To be safe...
Lo sé. Soy neurólogo. Para estar seguros...
...Dr. Wells wanted a more comprehensive overview. So he sent me.
...la Dra. Wells quería una evaluación más completa. Por eso me envió.
Dr. Wells is a woman.
La Dra. Wells es una mujer.
That was a test. Good response.
Eso fue una prueba. Buena respuesta.
- All right. Uh, full name? - Clifford Burnett.
- Muy bien. Uh, ¿nombre completo? - Clifford Burnett.
- Date of birth? - November 16, 1968.
- ¿Fecha de nacimiento? - 16 de noviembre de 1968.
Age?
¿Edad?
- Can't you figure that out? - I'm a doctor, not a mathematician.
- ¿No puedes calcularlo? - Soy doctor, no matemático.
- I'm 33. - Okay.
- Tengo 33. - De acuerdo.
- And, uh, are you married? - No.
[ERROR API]
Oh, really? So 33 and single? Would you say you have commitment issues?
Are all the questions this personal?
[ERROR API]
Yes.
Sí.
Well, if you must know, I'm a widower.
[ERROR API]
- Oh, that's terrible. I'm really sorry. - Yeah.
Do you sleep with women and never call them again?
¿Te acuestas con mujeres y nunca las vuelves a llamar?
- No. - Excellent. Excellent.
[ERROR API]
And, uh, finally, are you into any weird stuff, you know, sexually?
- No! - Ooh. Wrong answer.
[ERROR API]
- What else? What else? - Uh, he's 33.
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
- A widower. - Oh.
[ERROR API]
He seemed like a standup guy. And he's not into anything weird sexually.
Enter Pheebs.
[ERROR API]
- This room's available. - Okay! Wait, listen to me!
Since I've been waiting, four women...
[ERROR API]
...one higher than the centimeters I'm dilated...
...have come and gone with their babies. I'm next. My turn. It's only fair.
[ERROR API]
If you bring in one more woman who has her baby before me, I will sue you.
Not this hospital. I'm gonna sue you. My husband is a lawyer.
[ERROR API]
- Uh, Rach? - You get back on that case, honey!
I don't think the next patient is far along.
[ERROR API]
Okay. Well, then bring her in.
Oh, my God!
¡Oh, Dios mío!
I can't believe this!
¡No puedo creerlo!
And yet, somehow, it's true.
[ERROR API]
I mean, this is so great. We're gonna be baby buddies!
Squeeze your legs together, cover the baby's ears.
[ERROR API]
- Hi, sweetie! - Hi, sweetheart.
This is my husband, Sid. I don't think you've met. Ross, Rachel, this is Sid.
[ERROR API]
I nabbed him at the dermatologist's. Thank God for adult acne!
I can't believe it. I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
[ERROR API]
Really?
¿En serio?
What did he say?
¿Qué dijo?
You have to speak loudly, he's almost completely deaf.
[ERROR API]
- Oh, there you go. - Of course he is.
Congratulations. I didn't even know you got married.
[ERROR API]
- Oh, no. We didn't. - No, no, we...
What?
¿Qué?
We're just having this baby together, but, uh, that's all. You know?
[ERROR API]
Why?
¿Por qué?
Uh, we're just not in that place, you know? But we're very excited about this.
[ERROR API]
Oh. Well, then shut me up.
Just tell me how.
[ERROR API]
Uh-oh. Oh, I feel another one coming.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh!
[ERROR API]