- Hey, guys. - Hey.
- Hola, chicos. - Hola.
Honey, I got us that room at the Woodford Inn this weekend.
Cariño, conseguí esa habitación en el Woodford Inn para este fin de semana.
That place in Vermont? You can take a hint.
¿Ese lugar en Vermont? Ya te puedes dar por enterado.
You can't go away this weekend. It's Emma's birthday.
No puedes irte este fin de semana. Es el cumpleaños de Emma.
- Yeah. - We're having a party.
- Sí. - Vamos a hacer una fiesta.
Can't you have the party when we get back?
¿No pueden hacer la fiesta cuando regresemos?
- No. - No. It won't be her real birthday.
- No. - No. No será su verdadero cumpleaños.
Gee, if only she were 1 and had no idea what the hell a birthday was.
Vaya, si tan solo tuviera 1 año y no tuviera idea de qué demonios es un cumpleaños.
Come on, you guys, this is really important to us.
Vamos, chicos, esto es muy importante para nosotros.
Sorry, but Chandler and I could really use a weekend away...
Lo siento, pero Chandler y yo realmente necesitamos un fin de semana libre...
...you know, to reconnect, emotionally. - There's this thing I really want us to do.
...ya saben, para reconectar, emocionalmente. - Hay algo que realmente quiero que hagamos.
I read about it in Maxim.
Lo leí en Maxim.
Well, can't you just go to Vermont the next day?
Bueno, ¿no pueden ir a Vermont al día siguiente?
Yeah, we want everyone to be there.
Sí, queremos que todos estén allí.
As much as I hate to delay your doing weird sex stuff to my little sister.
Por mucho que odie retrasar que hagan cosas raras y sexuales con mi hermana pequeña.
And, I mean, you know, you guys, this is a big deal.
Y, quiero decir, ya saben, ustedes, esto es algo grande.
I mean, how can we have her first birthday party...
Quiero decir, ¿cómo podemos tener su primera fiesta de cumpleaños...
...without her aunt and her uncle?
...sin su tía y su tío?
All right, we'll stay. We can just drive up after the party.
Está bien, nos quedaremos. Podemos ir después de la fiesta.
Fine. But if we end up not doing this Maxim thing because of this party...
Bien. Pero si al final no hacemos esto de Maxim por esta fiesta...
Believe me, that is not why we won't be doing that.
Créeme, esa no es la razón por la que no lo haremos.
You know, Pheebs, when I was little, on my birthday...
Sabes, Pheebs, cuando era pequeña, en mi cumpleaños...
...my daddy would hide a present in every room of the house.
...mi papá escondía un regalo en cada habitación de la casa.
And then he would draw a treasure map to help me find them all.
Y luego dibujaba un mapa del tesoro para ayudarme a encontrarlos todos.
Aw, I love family traditions like that.
Ay, me encantan esas tradiciones familiares.
When Ursula and I were kids, on our birthday...
Cuando Ursula y yo éramos niñas, en nuestro cumpleaños...
...our stepdad would sell his blood to buy us food.
...nuestro padrastro vendía su sangre para comprarnos comida.
- Hey, guys. - Hi.
- Hola, chicos. - Hola.
- I brought the camera for Emma's video. - Oh, good!
- Traje la cámara para el video de Emma. - ¡Oh, bien!
We had this idea to make a birthday video for Emma...
Tuvimos esta idea de hacer un video de cumpleaños para Emma...
...and we'll give it to her when she's 18. - Oh, cool.
...y se lo daremos cuando cumpla 18. - Oh, genial.
- Wow, it's like a time capsule. - Yeah.
- Vaya, es como una cápsula del tiempo. - Sí.
Oh, just think, she's gonna be watching that video on a TV...
Oh, piensen, ella va a ver ese video en una televisión...
...that hasn't even been invented yet...
...que ni siquiera se ha inventado todavía...
...with friends who, right now, are just, like, babies.
...con amigos que, ahora mismo, son solo, como, bebés.
And they'll be living in a floating city that the humans built...
Y vivirán en una ciudad flotante que los humanos construyeron...
...to escape the ant people.
...para escapar de la gente hormiga.
That's the hope.
Esa es la esperanza.
- So is Emma awake yet? - No, it's still naptime.
- ¿Ya se despertó Emma? - No, todavía es hora de la siesta.
- But she'll be up soon. - Where's Joey?
- Pero se despertará pronto. - ¿Dónde está Joey?
I said, it's still naptime.
Dije que todavía es hora de la siesta.
- Hey, there's Uncle Joey. - Hey.
- Miren, ahí está el tío Joey. - Hola.
Hey, say something to Emma on her 18th birthday.
Oye, di algo para Emma en su cumpleaños número 18.
- Eighteen, huh? - Joey, no!
- ¿Dieciocho, eh? - ¡Joey, no!
What? What? It's for her hot friends.
¿Qué? ¿Qué? Es para sus amigas guapas.
When they see this, you'll be 52.
Cuando vean esto, tendrás 52 años.
And starting to think about settling down.
Y empezarás a pensar en sentar cabeza.
Hey, Joey, will you please set this up for people to put Emma's presents on?
Oye, Joey, ¿podrías poner esto para que la gente ponga los regalos de Emma?
Love to. Yeah.
Me encantaría. Sí.
- We were supposed to bring presents? - Yeah. I wrote Emma a song.
- ¿Se suponía que debíamos traer regalos? - Sí. Le escribí una canción a Emma.
Oh, yeah. How was I supposed to know?
[ERROR API]
- Joey, it's a birthday party. - Yeah, but for a 1 -year-old.
What's the point? The other day she laughed for, like, an hour at a cup.
[ERROR API]
Just a cup with a picture of Elmo on it, dressed as a farmer.
And he's standing next to this cow, and the cow says, "El-moo."
[ERROR API]
Man, that's a funny cup.
Hey.
Oye.
- Where's the birthday girl? - Oh, she's still napping.
[ERROR API]
She was probably up all night excited about the party she knows is happening.
I know you guys really want to get to Vermont, and this isn't a big deal to you.
[ERROR API]
But it really is to us, okay? Emma will never have a first birthday again.
You're right. We're sorry.
[ERROR API]
Let's wake up Emma and get the fun time started!
No, she didn't sleep well last night, so we can't wake her.
[ERROR API]
Are you frigging kidding me, Green?
- Hi! - Hey!
- ¡Hola! - ¡Hola!
- I'm so glad you came. - I can't believe Emma's already 1.
[ERROR API]
I remember your first birthday.
Ross was jealous of all the attention we were giving you.
[ERROR API]
He pulled on his testicles so hard...
...we had to take him to the emergency room.
[ERROR API]
There's something you didn't know about your dad.
Hey, Mr. And Mrs. Geller. Let me help you with that.
[ERROR API]
- Thank you. - Oh, man, this is great, huh?
The three of us together again. You know what would be fun?
[ERROR API]
If we gave this present to Emma from all of us.
Which one are you?
[ERROR API]
- I can't believe Emma's still asleep. - I know. What are we gonna do?
I've got a plan. I've got a plan.
[ERROR API]
I'm going to ram this platter really hard into your ribs.
You're gonna scream out, and that'll wake her up.
[ERROR API]
I'm not going to Vermont with this Monica.
Hey, Pheebs? You know what?
[ERROR API]
I was thinking since you wrote a song...
...maybe I could do something for Emma using my talents.
[ERROR API]
So you're gonna hit on her?
- No, no, no. My talents as an actor. - Oh.
[ERROR API]
You know, I could, like, maybe...
I could do a dramatic reading of one of her books.
[ERROR API]
Or you could stick a fork in an apple.
- Hey, I think Emma might like it. - Oh, Emma might like what?
[ERROR API]
- Uh, my present. - What did you get her?
- Actually, we prepared performances. - Separate performances.
[ERROR API]
But equally real.
That sounds like fun.
Eso suena divertido.
You know what, actually?
[ERROR API]
People are getting a little antsy waiting for Emma to wake up from her nap.
So would you mind performing them once now?
[ERROR API]
- Sure, yeah! - Okay.
Okay. All right. Everybody, let's get this party started, huh?
[ERROR API]
Joey and Phoebe are gonna perform a little something for us.
Joey y Phoebe van a interpretar algo para nosotros.
Oh, great.
Oh, genial.
Aren't you gonna be embarrassed having nothing prepared?
¿No te dará vergüenza no tener nada preparado?
I do it every week with three cameras pointed at me and a whole crew waiting.
Yo lo hago cada semana con tres cámaras apuntándome y todo un equipo esperando.
So, Joey, what are you gonna do for us?
Entonces, Joey, ¿qué vas a hacer para nosotros?
I will be doing a dramatic reading of one of Emma's books.
Haré una lectura dramática de uno de los libros de Emma.
Oh, okay. Which one?
Oh, vale. ¿Cuál?
Uh, well, it's one of her favorites.
Eh, bueno, es uno de sus favoritos.
"Riding the Storm Out: Coping With Postpartum Depression."
"Superando la tormenta: Lidiar con la depresión posparto."
Love You Forever.
Te amaré por siempre.
"Love You Forever, by Robert Munsch. Published by Firefly Books. Printed...
"Te amaré por siempre, de Robert Munsch. Publicado por Firefly Books. Impreso..."
...in Mexico.
...en México.
Ahem. A mother held her new baby and very slowly rocked him...
Ejem. Una madre sostenía a su bebé recién nacido y muy lentamente lo mecía...
...back and forth, back and forth, back and forth.
...de un lado a otro, de un lado a otro, de un lado a otro.
And while she held him, she sang, 'I'll love you forever.
Y mientras lo mecía, cantaba: 'Te amaré por siempre.
I'll like you for always. As long as I'm living...
Te querré siempre. Mientras yo viva...
...my baby you'll be."'
...mi bebé serás.'
"And while he rocked her, he sang:
"Y mientras ella lo mecía, él cantaba:
'I'll love you forever. I'll like you for always.
'Te amaré por siempre. Te querré siempre.
As long as I'm living...
Mientras yo viva...
...my baby you'll be."'
...mi bebé serás.'"
Oh, wow!
¡Oh, wow!
That was amazing.
Eso fue increíble.
Thank you so much for that gift.
Muchas gracias por ese regalo.
I was not ready for this today.
No estaba lista para esto hoy.
- Amazing. Amazing. - Phoebe, I'm sorry.
- Increíble. Increíble. - Phoebe, lo siento.
- Phoebe has prepared something. - That's right.
- Phoebe ha preparado algo. - Así es.
I prepared a song for Emma, from my heart to hers.
Preparé una canción para Emma, de mi corazón al suyo.
For there's no greater gift than the gift of music.
Porque no hay regalo más grande que el regalo de la música.
Emma
Your name poses a dilemma
Tu nombre plantea un dilema
'Cause not much else rhymes with Emma
Porque no rima mucho con Emma
Maybe the actor, Richard Crenna
Quizás el actor, Richard Crenna
He played the commanding officer in Rambo.
Interpretó al oficial al mando en Rambo.
Happy birthday, Emma
Feliz cumpleaños, Emma
Is that it?
¿Eso es todo?
No, of course not.
No, claro que no.
No, I've also, you know, prepared a reading.
No, también, ya sabes, preparé una lectura.
Um, "Sex and the Single Mother."
Um, "Sexo y madre soltera."
- "Finding your G-spot." - Oh, no, no, no!
- "Encontrando tu punto G." - ¡Oh, no, no, no!
Hello, Emma. Happy 18th birthday.
Hola, Emma. Feliz cumpleaños número 18.
Right now, that seems so far away, 17 years.
Ahora mismo, eso parece muy lejano, 17 años.
Yes. You'll be all grown up by then, and we'll be...
Sí. Ya estarás toda crecida para entonces, y nosotros...
Well, your grandfather and I might not be here.
Bueno, tu abuelo y yo podríamos no estar aquí.
That's true. This message could be coming to you...
Es verdad. Este mensaje podría llegarte...
...from beyond the grave, Emma.
...desde ultratumba, Emma.
- After all, my parents died very young. - And my cholesterol's off the charts.
- Después de todo, mis padres murieron muy jóvenes. - Y mi colesterol está por las nubes.
Remember, Emma, heart disease kills women too.
Recuerda, Emma, las enfermedades del corazón también matan a las mujeres.
Okay, cut! Great. Great. That was just...
Ok, ¡corten! Genial. Genial. Eso fue solo...
- Yeah. - Oh, good.
- Sí. - Oh, bien.
Ross, uh, don't forget to get a shot of Emma's cake.
Ross, eh, no olvides tomarle una foto al pastel de Emma.
- It's in a box in the fridge. - Okay, sure.
- Está en una caja en el refrigerador. - Okay, claro.
You're gonna love this cake. I got it from a bakery in New Jersey, Carino's.
Te va a encantar este pastel. Lo compré en una pastelería de Nueva Jersey, Carino's.
Oh, my God, that place has the creamiest frosting.
¡Dios mío, ese lugar tiene el betún más cremoso!
I used to hitchhike there when I was a kid.
Solía ir haciendo autostop cuando era niño.
Well, anyway, they make these great novelty cakes...
Bueno, en fin, hacen estos pasteles de novedad geniales...
...in all different shapes. And if you give them a photo, they'll copy it in icing.
...en todas las formas. Y si les das una foto, la copian en betún.
- Did you do a picture of Emma? - Yes. On a cake shaped like a bunny.
- ¿Hiciste una foto de Emma? - Sí. En un pastel con forma de conejito.
Uh, Rach? Does this bakery by any chance also bake...
Eh, ¿Rach? ¿Esta pastelería por casualidad también hornea...
...erotic cakes?
...pasteles eróticos?
Say, for bachelorette parties?
¿Por ejemplo, para despedidas de soltera?
Ross, what are you talking...? Oh, my God!
Ross, ¿de qué estás hablando...? ¡Dios mío!
They put my baby's face on a penis!
¡Le pusieron la cara de mi bebé a un pene!
Now it's a party!
¡Ahora sí es una fiesta!
Wait, you guys, this isn't funny, all right?
Esperen, chicos, esto no es gracioso, ¿de acuerdo?
If I wanted this cake to be a disaster, I would have baked it myself!
Si quisiera que este pastel fuera un desastre, ¡lo habría horneado yo misma!
Uh... Is it okay that I still think it looks delicious?
Eh... ¿Está bien que todavía piense que se ve delicioso?
- Jack, look at this. - I know what you're thinking, Judy.
- Jack, mira esto. - Sé lo que estás pensando, Judy.
The resemblance is uncanny.
El parecido es asombroso.
I am this close to tugging on my testicles again.
Estoy a punto de tocarme los testículos otra vez.
No, no, this is not what I ordered, okay?
No, no, esto no es lo que pedí, ¿vale?
I went all the way to New Jersey so that I could have the perfect cake...
Fui hasta Nueva Jersey para tener el pastel perfecto...
...for my daughter's birthday. And I need a bunny cake right now!
...para el cumpleaños de mi hija. ¡Y necesito un pastel de conejito ahora mismo!
Ask them if it would be faster if we cut the baby's face off the penis...
Pregúntales si sería más rápido si le cortamos la cara del bebé al pene...
...so we could put it on the bunny.
...para poder ponérsela al conejito.
That is a weird sentence.
Esa es una frase rara.
Oh, believe you me, I am going to bring this cake back.
Oh, créeme, voy a devolver este pastel.
I don't even want it in my home. Don't touch it!
¡Ni siquiera lo quiero en mi casa. ¡No lo toques!
I'm so confused!
¡Estoy tan confundida!
Yes, I still want my daughter's picture, but on a bunny cake!
Sí, todavía quiero la foto de mi hija, ¡pero en un pastel de conejito!
Yellow cake, chocolate frosting with nuts!
Pastel amarillo, betún de chocolate con nueces.
To be fair, this one does have nuts.
Para ser justos, este sí tiene nueces.
Hey, Mon, it was nice of you to loan Rachel your car...
Oye, Mon, fue muy amable de tu parte prestarle tu coche a Rachel...
...so she could get the cake. - It was nice of her to pull my hair...
...para que pudiera ir por el pastel. - Fue muy amable de su parte jalarme el pelo...
...till I dropped the key.
...hasta que se me cayó la llave.
Well, while we're waiting, you could tape your message to Emma...
Bueno, mientras esperamos, podrías grabar tu mensaje para Emma...
...for her 18th birthday, huh? Okay?
...para su cumpleaños número 18, ¿eh? ¿Okay?
Hi, Emma. It's the year 2020.
Hola, Emma. Es el año 2020.
Are you still enjoying your nap?
¿Sigues disfrutando tu siesta?
We're Aunt Monica and Uncle Chandler, by the way.
Somos la tía Monica y el tío Chandler, por cierto.
You may not recognize us...
Quizás no nos reconozcas...
...because we haven't spoken to your parents in 17 years.
...porque no hemos hablado con tus padres en 17 años.
We used to be married.
Solíamos estar casados.
But then we missed a weekend away together, and things kind of unraveled...
Pero luego nos perdimos un fin de semana juntos, y las cosas se desmoronaron...
...because of you.
...por tu culpa.
Happy birthday.
Feliz cumpleaños.
Ross, Rachel promised it would be over by now.
Ross, Rachel prometió que ya habría terminado.
We seriously have to go if we want to get to Vermont.
En serio tenemos que irnos si queremos llegar a Vermont.
- The last train leaves in a half-hour. - And I have a massage client soon.
- El último tren sale en media hora. - Y tengo un cliente de masajes pronto.
You guys, just, please, a little bit longer.
Chicos, por favor, un poco más de tiempo.
I promise, Rachel will be back with the cake any minute.
Te lo prometo, Rachel volverá con el pastel en cualquier minuto.
Monica, remember the frosting, huh?
Mónica, recuerda el betún, ¿eh?
All right, five more minutes.
Está bien, cinco minutos más.
Hello?
¿Hola?
Oh, no, what happened?
Oh, no, ¿qué pasó?
Okay, okay, where are you?
Okay, okay, ¿dónde estás?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Okay, voy para allá.
Was that Emma? Is she up?
¿Fue Emma? ¿Se despertó?
Rachel got pulled over for speeding.
A Rachel la detuvieron por exceso de velocidad.
She forgot her license. So I have to bring it to her.
Olvidó su licencia. Así que tengo que llevársela.
- If you're leaving, I'm definitely going. - Wait, if anybody gets to go, it's us!
- Si te vas tú, yo me voy seguro. - Espera, si alguien tiene que ir, ¡somos nosotros!
We've been complaining the longest!
¡Hemos estado quejándonos por más tiempo!
No, wait, you guys. No, you can't leave.
No, esperen, chicos. No se pueden ir.
Rachel already feels bad that the cake's messed up.
Rachel ya se siente mal porque el pastel está arruinado.
How do you think she'll feel when she comes back and you're gone?
¿Cómo crees que se sentirá cuando regrese y ustedes ya no estén?
I don't know. You'll tell us on Monday.
No lo sé. Nos lo dirás el lunes.
Joey, you're in charge, okay? You make sure nobody leaves.
Joey, tú te encargas, ¿okay? Asegúrate de que nadie se vaya.
Got it!
¡Entendido!
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
¡Oye! ¿A dónde crees que vas?
To the bathroom.
Al baño.
Well, the rest of you get comfortable, okay...
Bueno, el resto de ustedes pónganse cómodos, ¿okay...?
...because we are gonna be here for a...
...porque vamos a estar aquí por un...
- Wait, there's a window in there. - Oh, no! He's not getting away that easy!
- Espera, hay una ventana ahí. - ¡Oh, no! ¡No se va a escapar tan fácil!
What are you doing? Get the hell out of here!
¿Qué estás haciendo? ¡Lárgate de aquí!
Well, that one did not have Emma's face on it.
Bueno, esa no tenía la cara de Emma.
- No, it did not. - No.
- No, no la tenía. - No.
Well, we'd better get going. It's late.
Bueno, será mejor que nos vayamos. Es tarde.
Jack's not allowed to drive at night anymore.
A Jack ya no le permiten conducir de noche.
He has trouble staying in his lane.
Tiene problemas para mantenerse en su carril.
Last winter I went up on a church lawn and drove right through a manger scene.
El invierno pasado me subí a un césped de iglesia y atravesé una escena del pesebre.
The papers thought it was a hate crime.
Los periódicos pensaron que era un crimen de odio.
- Anyway, it was lovely seeing you. - Okay.
- En fin, fue un placer verlos. - Okay.
- Bye. Bye, dear. - Nighty-night.
- Adiós. Adiós, querido. - Buenas noches.
- Nighty-night. - Bye.
- Buenas noches. - Adiós.
- How could you just let them leave? - Hey, hey.
- ¿Cómo pudiste dejarlos ir así? - Oye, oye.
I'm not gonna mess with Jack. He's a great man. He fought for our country.
No voy a meterme con Jack. Es un gran hombre. Luchó por nuestro país.
No, he didn't. He pretended to be a Quaker to get out of Korea.
No, no lo hizo. Fingió ser cuáquero para evitar ir a Corea.
Well, that's it. He's the last one to go. I'm locking you guys in. Ha.
Bueno, eso es todo. Es el último en irse. Los voy a encerrar. Ja.
You do know I can just turn them the other way around, right?
¿Sabes que puedo simplemente girarlas al revés, verdad?
Oh, I forgot you used to live here.
Oh, olvidé que solías vivir aquí.
- Hello? - Joey, it's Estelle.
- ¿Hola? - Joey, soy Estelle.
- Hey. - So how'd your audition go today?
- Oye. - ¿Y cómo te fue en la audición hoy?
- What audition? - The one I told you about last week.
- ¿Qué audición? - La que te conté la semana pasada.
What? You never said anything about an audition.
¿Qué? Nunca dijiste nada sobre una audición.
Let me start over. I just got a call about an audition.
Déjame empezar de nuevo. Acabo de recibir una llamada sobre una audición.
I think you can still make it.
Creo que todavía puedes llegar.
It's down at the Astor Theater, and you need to have a monologue prepared.
Es en el Astor Theater, y necesitas tener un monólogo preparado.
A monologue? I don't have a...
¿Un monólogo? No tengo un...
I got it. Uh...
Lo tengo. Uh...
So I'm gonna take off.
Así que me voy a ir.
- What? - What? Wait! You don't get to leave.
- ¿Qué? - ¿Qué? ¡Espera! No te vas.
I've got a massage client waiting outside my door any minute.
Tengo un cliente de masajes esperando afuera en cualquier minuto.
And we paid for a room that we're supposed to be in right now!
¡Y pagamos por una habitación en la que se supone que deberíamos estar ahora mismo!
Well, okay, now...
Bueno, está bien, ahora...
...only one of us has to stay with Emma.
...solo uno de nosotros tiene que quedarse con Emma.
Okay, and as the person who realized that, I get to go.
Okay, y como la persona que se dio cuenta de eso, me toca irme.
No, no, no. No. No.
Let's figure out a fair way to decide who's staying.
Vamos a encontrar una forma justa de decidir quién se queda.
Oh, I got it.
Oh, ya entendí.
Okay, everyone pick a number from one to 10, all right?
Okay, todos elijan un número del uno al 10, ¿de acuerdo?
Whoever gets the highest number gets to go first.
Quien saque el número más alto se va primero.
- Okay, 10. - Okay, Monica picks 10. I call nine.
- Okay, 10. - Okay, Monica elige 10. Yo pido nueve.
Anyone else?
¿Alguien más?
- No, let's just draw straws. - Okay.
- No, saquemos suertes. - Okay.
Or we could flip a coin and multiply the answer...
O podríamos lanzar una moneda y multiplicar la respuesta...
- I'm begging you to stop. - Right.
- Te ruego que pares. - Bien.
Okay, how about this? We got wind-up toys for Emma for her birthday.
Okay, ¿qué tal esto? Compramos juguetes de cuerda para Emma para su cumpleaños.
We can make them race, and whoever comes in last stays.
Podemos hacer que compitan, y quien quede último se queda.
Yeah, let's do that!
¡Sí, hagámoslo!
That sounds more fun than the thing we were gonna do in Vermont!
¡Eso suena más divertido que lo que íbamos a hacer en Vermont!
- Okay, everybody, pick your toys! - Okay. I want the dolphin!
- Okay, ¡todos, elijan sus juguetes! - Okay. ¡Quiero el delfín!
- That's a bear. - I'm too excited!
- Ese es un oso. - ¡Estoy demasiado emocionada!
Phoebe, you get the bear. Joey, you get the robot.
Phoebe, tú te quedas con el oso. Joey, tú te quedas con el robot.
- Oh, yeah. - And Chandler and I get the dog.
- Oh, sí. - Y Chandler y yo nos quedamos con el perro.
And the race is going to go from here to here.
Y la carrera va a ser de aquí hasta aquí.
Now, the one who comes in last stays!
¡Ahora, el que quede último se queda!
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, wind your toys.
Okay, señoras y señores, denle cuerda a sus juguetes.
- Okay. On your mark, get set, go! - Go! Go!
- Okay. ¡Listos, preparados, fuera! - ¡Fuera! ¡Fuera!
Come on, robot!
¡Vamos, robot!
What are you barking at?
¿Por qué estás ladrando?
Well, how is that gonna help?
Bueno, ¿cómo va a ayudar eso?
I bought you! How did I forget that that's all you do?
¡Te compré! ¿Cómo olvidé que eso es todo lo que haces?
Way to go, robot!
¡Bien hecho, robot!
Good job, Alan.
Buen trabajo, Alan.
- Hey, good race, you guys. - Yeah, see you later.
- Oye, buena carrera, chicos. - Sí, hasta luego.
No. No, no. Wait.
No. No, no. Espera.
We didn't lose.
No perdimos.
The rules clearly stated that the last one to cross the finish line was the loser.
Las reglas decían claramente que el último en cruzar la meta era el perdedor.
Well, our dog never crossed the finish line. So technically...
Bueno, nuestro perro nunca cruzó la meta. Así que técnicamente...
They left.
Se fueron.
There isn't time to go to the bakery. We're just gonna come home.
No hay tiempo para ir a la pastelería. Simplemente volveremos a casa.
Everybody left?
¿Todos se fueron?
All right. Well, just tell Emma that we'll be there as soon as we can. Bye.
Está bien. Bueno, solo dile a Emma que estaremos allí tan pronto como podamos. Adiós.
- Rachel! - Oh, God, sorry!
- ¡Rachel! - ¡Oh, Dios, lo siento!
I can't believe they gave you a ticket. You're such a good driver.
No puedo creer que te pusieran una multa. Eres una conductora tan buena.
- Emma's awake. - Yeah?
- Emma está despierta. - ¿Sí?
I can't believe this.
No puedo creer esto.
This is her first birthday, she's awake, we're not even there.
Es su primer cumpleaños, está despierta, ni siquiera estamos allí.
Everybody left. We still have this stupid obscene cake.
Todos se fueron. Todavía tenemos este estúpido pastel obsceno.
Hey, maybe I can fix that. You know, try to turn it into something else.
Oye, tal vez pueda arreglar eso. Sabes, intentar convertirlo en otra cosa.
Oh, don't even bother.
Ay, ni te molestes.
We've already ruined her first birthday.
Ya arruinamos su primer cumpleaños.
And do you know how important these early experiences are, Ross? Very!
¿Y sabes lo importantes que son estas primeras experiencias, Ross? ¡Muy!
According to the back cover of that book that you gave me.
Según la contraportada de ese libro que me diste.
Rach, she's not gonna remember this.
Rach, ella no va a recordar esto.
I guess.
Supongo.
Oh, I just had such an idea of what this day would be like, you know?
Ay, solo tenía una idea de cómo sería este día, ¿sabes?
Emma laughing...
Emma riendo...
...and everybody gathered around her cake, singing "Happy Birthday."
...y todos reunidos alrededor de su pastel, cantando "Feliz Cumpleaños".
And then we would all... Hey, get out of the road, you stupid student driver!
Y entonces todos... ¡Oye, quítate del camino, estúpido conductor novato!
They have to learn.
Tienen que aprender.
- Hey. - What?
- Hey. - ¿Qué?
This is not bad.
Esto no está mal.
Oh, my God. Look, you made it into a bunny. How did you do that?
Dios mío. Mira, lo convertiste en un conejito. ¿Cómo hiciste eso?
Well, I just made these two things cheeks.
Bueno, solo hice estas dos cosas como mejillas.
And then I split this to make ears.
Y luego partí esto para hacer las orejas.
Well, I am very impressed.
Bueno, estoy muy impresionada.
Some can sing, some can dance.
Algunos pueden cantar, otros pueden bailar.
I, apparently, can turn phallic cakes into woodland creatures.
Yo, aparentemente, puedo convertir pasteles fálicos en criaturas del bosque.
Now, another way to organize your stuffed animals is by size.
Ahora, otra forma de organizar tus peluches es por tamaño.
I'm sorry, is this a game for Emma or for Monica?
Perdona, ¿esto es un juego para Emma o para Monica?
Game?
¿Juego?
Emma, do you even know it's your birthday today? You're 1.
Emma, ¿sabes siquiera que es tu cumpleaños hoy? Tienes 1.
One year old. That's little.
Un año. Es poco.
That's my girl.
Esa es mi niña.
That's how old you are.
Esa es tu edad.
Did I teach her that? Did I just impart wisdom?
¿Se lo enseñé yo? ¿Impartí sabiduría?
Aw, I want one.
Ay, quiero uno.
Me too.
Yo también.
There's no one around. Why don't we just take this one?
No hay nadie cerca. ¿Por qué no tomamos este?
- And head to Canada. - I was kidding.
- Y nos vamos a Canadá. - Estaba bromeando.
I wasn't. Let's get going.
Yo no. Vámonos.
- Hey, are Ross and Rachel back? - No, not yet.
- Oye, ¿ya volvieron Ross y Rachel? - No, todavía no.
- Good, I didn't miss the party. - What about your massage client?
- Bien, no me perdí la fiesta. - ¿Y tu cliente de masajes?
I just felt so bad missing this. So I just slipped him a little something, you know.
Me sentí tan mal por perderme esto. Así que le di una pequeña propina, ¿sabes?
As long as I'm back in five or six hours, it'll be all right.
Mientras regrese en cinco o seis horas, estará bien.
Okay.
If Ross and Rachel ask, I've been here the whole time. The whole time.
Si Ross y Rachel preguntan, he estado aquí todo el tiempo. Todo el tiempo.
I've been here the whole time.
He estado aquí todo el tiempo.
Joey, we just saw you come in. You ran past us on the stairs.
Joey, te acabamos de ver entrar. Pasaste corriendo junto a nosotros en las escaleras.
I don't care that you left. I'm just glad that you're here. Thanks, you guys.
No me importa que te hayas ido. Solo me alegra que estés aquí. Gracias, chicos.
Hey, guys, come on. You gotta see what Emma just did.
Oigan, vamos. Tienen que ver lo que Emma acaba de hacer.
- What? - Emma, how old are you?
- ¿Qué? - Emma, ¿cuántos años tienes?
How old are you today?
¿Cuántos años tienes hoy?
Oh, Emma, that's right. You're that many.
Oh, Emma, es verdad. Tienes esa edad.
Oh, my God, our daughter's a genius.
Dios mío, nuestra hija es una genio.
- This means... - No! No science camp!
- Esto significa... - ¡No! ¡No al campamento de ciencias!
- Damn it! I'll put a candle on the cake. - Oh...
- ¡Maldición! Pondré una vela en el pastel. - Oh...
Oh, and, Emma, look at your stuffed animals lined up so neatly.
Ah, y, Emma, mira tus peluches alineados tan ordenadamente.
Thanks.
Gracias.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, allá vamos.
Emma's first birthday cake.
El primer pastel de cumpleaños de Emma.
Go ahead, Emma, blow out the candle.
Adelante, Emma, sopla la vela.
Come on, Emma. You can do it.
Vamos, Emma. Tú puedes.
- What's wrong? Are you okay? - Oh, yeah, nothing.
- ¿Qué pasa? ¿Estás bien? - Oh, sí, nada.
These are happy tears. Ha, ha.
Son lágrimas de felicidad. Ja, ja.
This is just what I wanted.
Esto es justo lo que quería.
Hey, you made it into a bunny.
Oye, lo convertiste en un conejito.
What is wrong with me? It looked more delicious when it was a penis.
¿Qué me pasa? Se veía más delicioso cuando era un pene.
- Okay. Yeah. - Okay, you ready?
- Vale. Sí. - ¿Listo?
- And record. - Okay.
- Y grabando. - Vale.
Hi, Emma. Well, your first birthday is over, and...
Hola, Emma. Bueno, tu primer cumpleaños ya pasó, y...
Go! Go! Come on!
¡Vamos! ¡Vamos! ¡Tú puedes!
Go! Go, Alan! Run, you hairy bastard!
¡Vamos! ¡Vamos, Alan! ¡Corre, bastardo peludo!