- Mm, hey. - Hi.
- Mmm, hola. - Hola.
Pheebs, what's wrong?
Pheebs, ¿qué pasa?
Ah, I'm just so exhausted from dragging around this huge engagement ring.
Ay, estoy tan agotada de cargar con este anillo de compromiso tan grande.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
- Congratulations. - Wow.
- Felicidades. - Guau.
So did he get on one knee? Did he have a speech prepared?
¿Y se arrodilló? ¿Tenía un discurso preparado?
Oh, did he cry?
Oh, ¿lloró?
Yeah, big surprise, I like proposals.
Sí, qué sorpresa, me gustan las propuestas.
Well, it was really sweet, and, like, the most romantic thing ever.
Bueno, fue muy tierno y, como, lo más romántico del mundo.
Here's to Phoebe, who's found the greatest guy in the world.
Por Phoebe, que ha encontrado al mejor chico del mundo.
To Phoebe and...
Por Phoebe y...
I want to say "Mike"?
¿Quiero decir "Mike"?
- To Phoebe and Mike. - Hey.
- Por Phoebe y Mike. - Hola.
- Thank you. - Oh.
- Gracias. - Oh.
- Oh, and I have something for you. - Hmm.
- Oh, y tengo algo para ti. - Mmm.
It's my little black book. It's got the numbers of all the guys I've dated.
Es mi agenda. Tiene los números de todos los chicos con los que salí.
Oh, ha, ha. Phoebe, that's nice, but you know what? I think I'm okay.
Oh, ja, ja. Phoebe, eso es lindo, pero ¿sabes qué? Creo que estoy bien.
Give it to one of your other single girlfriends.
Dáselo a alguna de tus otras amigas solteras.
I would, but you're the last one.
Lo haría, pero eres la última.
Give me the book!
¡Dame el libro!
"Pablo Diaz.
"Pablo Díaz.
Brady Smith." Ha.
Brady Smith". Ja.
"Guy in Van"?
"¿Chico en la camioneta"?
Oh, my first love.
Oh, mi primer amor.
Ah.
What does the red X next to Bob Gremore's name mean?
¿Qué significa la X roja al lado del nombre de Bob Gremore?
Dead.
Muerto.
Oh, it's okay. No, he was old. Yeah.
Oh, está bien. No, era mayor. Sí.
And he lived a full life. He was in the first wave at Omaha Beach.
Y vivió una vida plena. Estuvo en la primera oleada en Omaha Beach.
I should've given you guys my black book when I got married.
Debería haberles dado mi agenda cuando me casé.
Although, it wasn't so much a book as a napkin.
Aunque, no era tanto un libro como una servilleta.
With Janice's phone number on it.
Con el número de teléfono de Janice.
Phoebe, isn't Jethro Tull a band?
Phoebe, ¿no es Jethro Tull una banda?
Oh, yes, they are.
Oh, sí, lo es.
Hey, honey.
Hola, cariño.
Hey, sweetie.
- Is Monica not here? - No.
- ¿Mónica no está aquí? - No.
Oh, then I'll tell you.
Oh, entonces te lo diré.
My agency was bidding for a big account, and they got it.
Mi agencia estaba compitiendo por una gran cuenta, y la consiguieron.
- It's my first national commercial. - Cool.
- Es mi primer comercial nacional. - Genial.
And I don't want to brag, but a lot of the ideas were mine.
Y no quiero presumir, pero muchas de las ideas fueron mías.
Hell, you weren't there. All the ideas were mine.
Demonios, tú no estabas ahí. Todas las ideas fueron mías.
That's great. Hey, can you cast me in it?
Eso es genial. Oye, ¿puedes ponerme en él?
Oh, I really don't think you're right for the part.
Oh, realmente no creo que seas adecuada para el papel.
What do you mean? I can do anything. I'm a chameleon, huh?
¿Qué quieres decir? Puedo hacer cualquier cosa. Soy un camaleón, ¿eh?
I'm old.
Soy viejo.
Huh, I'm tired, huh?
¿Eh, estoy cansado, eh?
Oh, I am hot. I'm cold, huh? Come on, what can't I do?
Oh, tengo calor. Tengo frío, ¿eh? Vamos, ¿qué no puedo hacer?
First of all, bravo.
Primero que nada, bravo.
Uh, but I don't think you're right for this.
Uh, pero no creo que seas adecuada para esto.
The part's a stuffy college professor.
El papel es de un profesor universitario aburrido.
I can do that.
Puedo hacer eso.
Hello, I'm your professor.
Hola, soy su profesor.
When I'm not busy thinking of important things, or professing...
Cuando no estoy ocupado pensando en cosas importantes, o dando clases...
...I like to use... Oh, what's the product?
...me gusta usar... Oh, ¿cuál es el producto?
Software that facilitates inter-business networking e-solutions.
Software que facilita las soluciones electrónicas de redes interempresariales.
I'm cold.
Tengo frío.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Guess who's a finalist for a huge research grant?
¿Adivina quién es finalista para una enorme subvención de investigación?
I'll give you a hint. He's looking right at you.
Te doy una pista. Te está mirando directamente a ti.
Huh, well, unless it's the creepy guy with his hand up his kilt...
Eh, bueno, a menos que sea el tipo espeluznante con la mano en su kilt...
...I'm gonna say, "Congratulations."
...voy a decir: "Felicitaciones".
Ha, ha. Uh, I'm so excited.
Ja, ja. Eh, estoy muy emocionado.
Apparently, I beat out hundreds of other applicants...
Aparentemente, superé a cientos de otros solicitantes...
...including five guys I went to graduate school with.
...incluyendo a cinco chicos con los que fui a la escuela de posgrado.
Not that I'm keeping score, or anything. Five.
No es que esté contando, ni nada. Cinco.
- Wow, that's great. - Yeah.
Vaya, eso es genial. Sí.
- So tell me about the grant. - Well, okay, it's for $25,000.
Entonces, háblame de la subvención. Bueno, está bien, es por $25,000.
And if I get it, I'll finally be able to complete my field research.
Y si la consigo, finalmente podré completar mi investigación de campo.
And there will be an article about me in the Paleontology Review.
Y habrá un artículo sobre mí en la Paleontology Review.
It'll be the first time my name is in there...
Será la primera vez que mi nombre esté ahí...
...without people raising serious questions about my work.
...sin que la gente plantee serias dudas sobre mi trabajo.
- Are you talking about the Dewer Grant? - Yeah. Why?
¿Estás hablando de la Beca Dewer? Sí. ¿Por qué?
Benjamin Hobart is administering that grant.
Benjamin Hobart está administrando esa subvención.
- Your ex-boyfriend? - Yeah.
¿Tu exnovio? Sí.
So your ex-boyfriend is gonna determine if your new boyfriend gets this grant?
Entonces, ¿tu exnovio va a determinar si tu nuevo novio obtiene esta subvención?
Wow, your new boyfriend is screwed.
Vaya, tu nuevo novio está frito.
No. No, we ended on great terms.
No. No, terminamos en buenos términos.
If anything, I think this could help you. You know what?
Si acaso, creo que esto podría ayudarte. ¿Sabes qué?
Why don't we all go out to dinner, and I can introduce you.
¿Por qué no salimos todos a cenar y te lo presento?
- If you think it'd help. - Yeah, absolutely. I'll call him.
Si crees que ayudaría. Sí, absolutamente. Lo llamaré.
Now, is there anything I could do to butter him up?
Ahora, ¿hay algo que pueda hacer para ganármelo?
- Anything he really likes? - Hmm.
¿Algo que le guste mucho? Mmm.
He does have a pretty serious latex fetish.
Tiene un fetiche bastante serio con el látex.
We'll see how dinner goes.
Veremos cómo va la cena.
- Hey. - Hey, you want to go see a movie?
Oye. Oye, ¿quieres ir a ver una película?
I told you I had to spend all day clearing out stuff so Mike could move in.
Te dije que tenía que pasar todo el día limpiando cosas para que Mike pudiera mudarse.
- Oh, right. - Yeah.
- Oh, claro. - Sí.
Now that I'm here, I might as well help with the cleaning and organizing.
Ahora que estoy aquí, bien podría ayudar con la limpieza y organización.
I just happen to have my label maker.
Justo tengo mi etiquetadora.
Oh, it's so hard to get rid of stuff.
Oh, es tan difícil deshacerse de las cosas.
Did you and Chandler make compromises when you moved in together?
¿Tú y Chandler hicieron concesiones cuando se mudaron juntos?
Huh, Chandler did.
Eh, Chandler sí.
- What does he want you to give up? - A bunch of stuff.
¿Qué quiere que renuncies? Un montón de cosas.
And the worst one...
Y la peor...
He wants me to get rid of Gladys.
Quiere que me deshaga de Gladys.
Who's Gladys?
¿Quién es Gladys?
- Oh, what a tragic loss. - Mm-hm.
Oh, qué pérdida tan trágica. Mm-hm.
Yeah, I really hate to give her up. Oh, I know. Oh, you should take her.
Sí, realmente odio renunciar a ella. Oh, lo sé. Oh, deberías tomarla.
Oh, I... I don't know.
Oh, yo... no lo sé.
- Oh, what, you don't like her? - Heh, of course I do. What's not to like?
- ¿Qué, no te cae bien? - Je, claro que sí. ¿Qué no te va a gustar?
I'd take her in a minute.
Me la quedaría en un minuto.
But I think that you're giving up too easy.
Pero creo que te estás rindiendo muy fácil.
I think that you need to fight for her.
Creo que tienes que luchar por ella.
- Really, you think? - Absolutely.
- ¿En serio, crees? - Absolutamente.
You say to him, "I'm sorry, Mike, I can't live without her.
Le dices: "Lo siento, Mike, no puedo vivir sin ella.
She means too much to me."
Significa demasiado para mí."
Okay, I'll fight for her. Okay.
Está bien, lucharé por ella. Está bien.
Oh, wait. Oh, I just realized, if I do that, that means you don't get her.
Oh, espera. Oh, acabo de darme cuenta, si hago eso, significa que tú no la consigues.
Damn it, I did not think this through.
Maldición, no pensé esto bien.
- Hey, guys. - Hi.
- Hola, chicos. - Hola.
Oh, any word on casting yet?
Oh, ¿alguna noticia sobre el casting?
- I told you, you're not right for the part. - What do you mean?
- Te dije que no eres adecuado para el papel. - ¿Qué quieres decir?
Rach, don't I seem like a professor you'd buy some kind of e-crap from?
Rach, ¿no parezco un profesor al que le comprarías alguna porquería electrónica?
I'm sorry, this sounds like something I'm never gonna be interested in.
Lo siento, esto suena a algo que nunca me va a interesar.
Look, come on, please? It's not like I'm asking you for some crazy favor.
Mira, vamos, ¿por favor? No es como si te pidiera un favor loco.
This is what I do for a living. I am a professional actor.
Esto es a lo que me dedico. Soy un actor profesional.
Oh, man, I'm two hours late for work.
Oh, hombre, llego dos horas tarde al trabajo.
Here's my reel. It's got all the commercials that I've been in.
Aquí está mi demo. Tiene todos los comerciales en los que he estado.
- Joe... - Uh, just watch it.
- Joe... - Uh, solo mírala.
If you don't like it, don't pass it on to your bosses.
Si no te gusta, no se la pases a tus jefes.
- Fine. - Thank you.
- Bien. - Gracias.
- Work, Joe. - Damn it.
- Trabajo, Joe. - Maldición.
- What am I gonna do now? - Just pass the tape along.
- ¿Qué voy a hacer ahora? - Solo pasa la cinta.
He's not right for the part.
Él no es adecuado para el papel.
If I suggest him, my bosses will think I'm an idiot.
Si lo sugiero, mis jefes pensarán que soy un idiota.
And that's something they should learn on their own.
Y eso es algo que deberían aprender por sí mismos.
Oh, just tell Joey that you watched the tape...
Oh, solo dile a Joey que viste la cinta...
...and you liked it, but your bosses didn't.
...y te gustó, pero a tus jefes no.
Then you're the good guy, and they're the bad guy.
Entonces tú eres el bueno, y ellos son los malos.
That's good. I liked it, they didn't.
Eso está bien. Me gustó, a ellos no.
Joey, for God's sake, go to work.
Joey, por el amor de Dios, ve a trabajar.
I can't believe I'm about to meet Benjamin Hobart.
No puedo creer que voy a conocer a Benjamin Hobart.
Um, I've always thought of him as someone I'd invite...
Um, siempre lo he considerado alguien a quien invitaría...
...to my fantasy dinner party, ha, ha.
...a mi cena de ensueño, ja, ja.
Do you think there's any chance he'll bring Christie Brinkley or C-3PO?
¿Crees que hay alguna posibilidad de que traiga a Christie Brinkley o a C-3PO?
Sorry, it looks like it's just him.
Lo siento, parece que solo estará él.
Charlie.
- My God, you look absolutely stunning. - Oh.
- Dios mío, te ves absolutamente deslumbrante. - Oh.
Well, I am having a good hair day.
Bueno, estoy teniendo un buen día de pelo.
- It's so good to see you. - Oh, you too.
- Qué bueno verte. - Oh, tú también.
BENJl: Mm.
Ahem, I'm okay.
Ejem, estoy bien.
Um, I'm sorry. Um, Ross Geller, Benjamin Hobart.
Um, lo siento. Um, Ross Geller, Benjamin Hobart.
Oh, it's an honor to meet you. I can't tell you how long...
Oh, es un honor conocerte. No te imaginas cuánto...
...I've been an admirer of your work. I mean, that Nobel Prize, uh, whoo!
...he sido admirador de tu trabajo. Quiero decir, ese Premio Nobel, ¡uh, guau!
- Ha, ha. - Oh.
- Ja, ja. - Oh.
I mean, I have to tell you that you're one of the reasons I got into the field.
Tengo que decirte que eres una de las razones por las que me metí en el campo.
Oh, well, uh, likewise.
Oh, bueno, uh, igualmente.
Uh, not likewise. I'd never heard of you until this morning.
Uh, no igualmente. Nunca había oído hablar de ti hasta esta mañana.
But it's nice to be nice.
Pero es bueno ser bueno.
- Uh, shall we? - Yeah, ahem. Thank you. Ahem.
- Uh, ¿vamos? - Sí, ejem. Gracias. Ejem.
I can't believe that you chose this restaurant.
No puedo creer que hayas elegido este restaurante.
- Do you remember the night? - Oh, my God. I completely forgot.
- ¿Recuerdas la noche? - Dios mío. Lo olvidé por completo.
BENJl: Ha-ha-ha. - Oh, my God.
BENJI: Ja-ja-ja. - Dios mío.
I can't believe they let us back in this place.
No puedo creer que nos dejaran volver a este lugar.
- You weren't there. - Ha, ha.
- Tú no estabas. - Ja, ja.
No, but, you know, it's just a funny image.
No, pero, ya sabes, es solo una imagen graciosa.
You know, the two of you in this restaurant with the hmm...
Sabes, ustedes dos en este restaurante con el mmm...
Why don't you tell Benji about your proposal while I go to the ladies' room.
¿Por qué no le cuentas a Benji sobre tu propuesta mientras voy al baño?
So tell me about it.
Entonces, cuéntame.
Okay. Well, I would like to do a dig in the Painted Desert.
Está bien. Bueno, me gustaría hacer una excavación en el Desierto Pintado.
Mm-hm.
There are still several areas that haven't been fully excavated.
Todavía hay varias áreas que no han sido completamente excavadas.
- Break up with Charlie. - What?
- Termina con Charlie. - ¿Qué?
What?
¿Qué?
Did you just say, "Break up with Charlie"?
¿Acabas de decir "Termina con Charlie"?
Well, yes and no. Yes, I did say it. And no, I didn't not say it.
Bueno, sí y no. Sí, lo dije. Y no, no lo dije.
Um, kind of inappropriate, don't you think?
Um, un poco inapropiado, ¿no crees?
Listen, I'm sorry.
Escucha, lo siento.
I just haven't seen her for so long, all these feelings are rushing back.
Simplemente no la he visto en tanto tiempo, todos estos sentimientos están volviendo.
I'm starting to realize how much I've missed her.
Estoy empezando a darme cuenta de cuánto la he extrañado.
And I'm gonna need you to break up with her.
Y voy a necesitar que termines con ella.
- Are you serious? - If you say, yes, then I'm serious.
- ¿Hablas en serio? - Si dices que sí, entonces hablo en serio.
If you say, no, then I'm joking.
Si dices que no, entonces estoy bromeando.
- No. - Joking it is.
- No. - Entonces es broma.
- Hi, sorry I'm late. - Hey, how'd it go with Mike?
- Hola, perdón por llegar tarde. - Hola, ¿cómo te fue con Mike?
- Is he gonna let you keep the painting? - Huh, no, he really hates it, ugh.
- ¿Te dejará quedarte con la pintura? - Eh, no, la odia de verdad, ugh.
But he's gonna let me keep my box of human hair.
Pero me dejará quedarme con mi caja de cabello humano.
So you gotta pick your battles. But the good news is, Gladys is yours.
Así que tienes que elegir tus batallas. Pero la buena noticia es que Gladys es tuya.
Wow, what's the bad news?
Vaya, ¿cuál es la mala noticia?
- Who's Gladys? - Oh, she's that work of art I made.
- ¿Quién es Gladys? - Oh, es esa obra de arte que hice.
You know, with the woman coming out of the frame.
Sabes, con la mujer saliendo del marco.
Ah, and Monica gets to keep her?
Ah, ¿y Monica se la queda?
In her house? I am so jealous.
¿En su casa? Muero de envidia.
- Oh, I didn't know you wanted her too. - Oh.
- Oh, no sabía que tú también la querías. - Oh.
Well, I mean, sure, of course.
Bueno, quiero decir, claro, por supuesto.
But you already gave that to Monica, so...
Pero ya se la diste a Monica, así que...
- You know, I would give her up for you. - No, I couldn't let you do that.
- Sabes, la dejaría por ti. - No, no podría permitir que lo hicieras.
- No, but I want to. - But I don't want you to.
- No, pero quiero. - Pero yo no quiero que lo hagas.
- But I insist. - But I insist harder.
- Pero insisto. - Pero insisto más.
Girls. Girls. Stop. Okay, we'll flip a coin.
Chicas. Chicas. Paren. Está bien, lanzaremos una moneda.
Heads, she's Rachel's. Tails, she's Monica's.
Cara, es de Rachel. Cruz, es de Monica.
- Tails. - Oh.
- Cruz. - Oh.
- Monica, she's yours. - No, that landed in your food.
- Monica, es tuya. - No, eso cayó en tu comida.
No, no, that's okay. You won fair and square. I'm so sad.
No, no, está bien. Ganaste limpiamente. Estoy tan triste.
- Hey, Joe? - What's up?
- Oye, ¿Joe? - ¿Qué pasa?
Bad news. I watched the tape and passed it along to my bosses...
Malas noticias. Vi la cinta y se la pasé a mis jefes...
...and they weren't interested. - Oh.
...y no estaban interesados. - Oh.
I'm sorry, man.
Lo siento, amigo.
- But, uh, you watched the tape? - Yeah, I... I liked it.
- Pero, eh, ¿viste la cinta? - Sí, me... me gustó.
But, uh, my bosses didn't go for it. Stupid sons of bitches.
Pero, eh, a mis jefes no les pareció. Estúpidos hijos de perra.
- You didn't watch the tape. - What? Of course I did.
- No viste la cinta. - ¿Qué? Claro que sí.
Look, it's one thing not to cast me, but to lie to me?
Mira, una cosa es que no me elijas, pero ¿que me mientas?
- I'm not lying to you. I watched it. - Ah, you lied again.
- No te miento. La vi. - Ah, mentiste de nuevo.
- I watched it. - Keep going, Pinocchio.
- La vi. - Sigue, Pinocho.
- I did. - No, you didn't!
- Sí. - ¡No, no lo hiciste!
I'm telling you, I watched the tape.
Te digo que vi la cinta.
- Did you watch the tape? - No.
- ¿Viste la cinta? - No.
The selection committee has chosen the three of you as our finalists.
El comité de selección los ha elegido a ustedes tres como finalistas.
The decision will be based on the answers you give to the questions I ask.
La decisión se basará en las respuestas que den a las preguntas que haga.
We'll start with Dr. Li. You claim the field is too reliant...
Empezaremos con la Dra. Li. Usted afirma que el campo depende demasiado...
...on the Linnaean taxonomic system. How do you propose to correct this?
...del sistema taxonómico linneano. ¿Cómo propone corregir esto?
I believe that the answers lie in the osteological evidence.
Creo que las respuestas están en la evidencia osteológica.
- I plan to begin there. - Interesting.
- Planeo empezar por ahí. - Interesante.
I guess.
Supongo.
Dr. Biely, your proposal includes some fieldwork. Where might that take place?
Dra. Biely, su propuesta incluye trabajo de campo. ¿Dónde podría ser?
Primarily in the Pierre Shale region of South Dakota.
Principalmente en la región de Pierre Shale en Dakota del Sur.
Certainly. Very well. And Dr. Geller, when is my birthday?
Claro. Muy bien. Y Dra. Geller, ¿cuándo es mi cumpleaños?
What? I... Uh.
¿Qué? Yo... Eh.
Care to venture a guess?
¿Alguna suposición?
- May 12? - That's not even kind of close.
- ¿El 12 de mayo? - Ni por asomo.
Dr. Li, how many graduate students will you need?
Dra. Li, ¿cuántos estudiantes de posgrado necesitará?
- Half a dozen. - I see. And Dr. Biely?
- Media docena. - Ya veo. ¿Y la Dra. Biely?
Three for excavation, and two for analysis.
Tres para excavación y dos para análisis.
Certainly. Dr. Geller, which 1965 Shirelles hit...
Claro. Dra. Geller, ¿cuál éxito de las Shirelles de 1965...
...was later covered by a popular British Invasion band?
...fue versionado después por una popular banda de la Invasión Británica?
What?
¿Qué?
What? I need six graduate students.
¿Qué? Necesito seis estudiantes de posgrado.
No, I'm sorry. We were looking for "Baby It's You."
No, lo siento. Buscábamos "Baby It's You."
"Baby It's You."
What? Wait just a minute.
¿Qué? Espera un minuto.
None of my questions have anything to do with paleontology.
Ninguna de mis preguntas tiene que ver con paleontología.
You're right, I apologize. Scratch the last question.
Tiene razón, me disculpo. Olvide la última pregunta.
Spell "Boscodictiasaur."
Escriba "Boscodictiasaur."
Um, I've never heard of a "Boscodictiasaur."
Mmm, nunca he oído hablar de un "Boscodictiasaur."
Yeah, I just made it up. Spell it.
Sí, me lo acabo de inventar. Escríbalo.
- Okay. B-O... - No, it starts with a silent M.
- Vale. B-O... - No, empieza con una M muda.
Oh, come on!
¡Ay, vamos!
I can't believe Joey. I hate being called a liar.
No puedo creer a Joey. Odio que me llamen mentiroso.
But you are a liar.
Pero eres un mentiroso.
What did I just say?
¿Qué acabo de decir?
- Are you still here? - Yes.
- ¿Sigues aquí? - Sí.
And I'm not just hurt, I'm insulted. When I tell somebody I did something...
Y no solo estoy dolido, estoy insultado. Cuando le digo a alguien que hice algo...
Okay, hold on, let me just stop you right there, okay? First, you lied. Right?
Vale, espera, déjame detenerte justo ahí, ¿vale? Primero, mentiste. ¿Correcto?
Then you lied about lying, okay?
Luego mentiste sobre mentir, ¿vale?
Then you lied about lying about lying, okay?
Luego mentiste sobre mentir sobre mentir, ¿vale?
So before you lie about lying about lying about lying about lying...
Así que antes de que mientas sobre mentir sobre mentir sobre mentir sobre mentir...
Stop lying.
Deja de mentir.
Why are you so sure I didn't watch this tape?
¿Por qué estás tan seguro de que no vi esta cinta?
You wanna know why? You wanna know why?
¿Quieres saber por qué? ¿Quieres saber por qué?
Well, this is going well.
Bueno, esto va bien.
Here's how I know.
Aquí es como lo sé.
If you had seen what was on this tape, believe me, you'd have some comments.
Si hubieras visto lo que había en esta cinta, créeme, tendrías comentarios.
All right, remember, I got paid a lot of money for this...
Muy bien, recuerda, me pagaron mucho dinero por esto...
...and it only aired in Japan.
...y solo se emitió en Japón.
Ichiban.
Ichiban, lipstick for men.
Ichiban, el lápiz labial para hombres.
And that's how I know you didn't watch the tape.
Y así es como sé que no viste la cinta.
He really is a chameleon.
Realmente es un camaleón.
Well, Gladys, say hello to your new home.
Bueno, Gladys, saluda a tu nuevo hogar.
- Oh, my. - Wow.
- Oh, Dios mío. - Guau.
Oh, she is so nice and big.
Oh, es tan bonita y grande.
Oh, Monica, where are you going to display Gladys, oh, so proudly?
Oh, Monica, ¿dónde vas a exhibir a Gladys, oh, tan orgullosamente?
I haven't really settled on a spot yet.
Todavía no he decidido un lugar.
How about right above the TV?
¿Qué tal justo encima de la televisión?
That way, it will be the first thing that you see when you walk in the door.
De esa manera, será lo primero que veas al entrar por la puerta.
Yeah, yeah, and you can get rid of that French poster.
Sí, sí, y puedes deshacerte de ese póster francés.
- I like that poster. - Really?
- Me gusta ese póster. - ¿En serio?
It doesn't have anything coming out of it.
No tiene nada saliendo de él.
Or maybe there's someplace for her in your bedroom?
¿O tal vez hay un lugar para ella en tu habitación?
- Oh, there's nothing above your bed. - Are you still here?
- Oh, no hay nada encima de tu cama. - ¿Sigues aquí?
Oh, hi. Hello.
Oh, hola. Hola.
Uh, have you come to ask me some more paleontology-related questions?
Uh, ¿has venido a hacerme más preguntas sobre paleontología?
Um, your grandmother's nickname, perhaps?
¿El apodo de tu abuela, quizás?
Ann-Margret's pant size?
¿La talla de pantalón de Ann-Margret?
I've come here to apologize. I think I may have let my feelings...
He venido aquí a disculparme. Creo que dejé que mis sentimientos...
...for Charlie interfere with the interview process.
...por Charlie interfirieran con el proceso de la entrevista.
No. Stop!
¡No! ¡Para!
Anyway, I decided to offer you the grant.
De todos modos, decidí ofrecerte la beca.
- Really? - There is just, uh, one small stipulation.
- ¿En serio? - Solo hay, eh, una pequeña estipulación.
- I have to break up with Charlie? - Hey, you got one right.
- ¿Tengo que romper con Charlie? - Oye, acertaste una.
- You're crazy. - Crazy or romantic?
- Estás loco. - ¿Loco o romántico?
Crazy.
Loco.
- Or? - Get out!
- ¿O? - ¡Fuera!
Oh, my God!
¡Oh, Dios mío!
- What? - Joey, what is this thing doing here?
- ¿Qué? - Joey, ¿qué hace esta cosa aquí?
I got her from Monica. She sold it to me for a very reasonable price.
La conseguí de Monica. Me la vendió a un precio muy razonable.
- Joey, we're not keeping this. - But it's an original Buffay.
- Joey, no nos vamos a quedar con esto. - Pero es una Buffay original.
All right, fine. You can keep it.
Muy bien, está bien. Puedes quedártela.
As long as you don't mind that she's haunted.
Siempre y cuando no te importe que esté embrujada.
Hey, what? Whoa. What?
Oye, ¿qué? Vaya. ¿Qué?
Well, legend has it, Joey, that she comes alive when you're asleep.
Bueno, la leyenda dice, Joey, que cobra vida cuando duermes.
She climbs out of the frame...
Se sale del marco...
...and then drags her half-a-body across the floor...
...y arrastra su medio cuerpo por el suelo...
...just looking for legs to steal.
...solo buscando piernas para robar.
And then with her one good hand...
Y luego, con su única mano buena...
...she slowly reaches up...
...lentamente alcanza...
...and turns your doorknob.
...y gira el pomo de tu puerta.
Get that legless witch out of here!
¡Saca a esa bruja sin piernas de aquí!
- Hey, I sold that to Joey. - Yeah, well, I told him it's haunted.
[ERROR API]
- Two can play at this game. - Too late. You can't give it back.
- Oh, yes, I can. - No, you can't, she's yours.
[ERROR API]
- She's yours. - She's yours.
- She's yours. - Hey.
[ERROR API]
- She's mine. - She's mine.
You guys, you don't have to fight over her anymore.
[ERROR API]
Whoever doesn't get Gladys, gets Glynnis.
- I want Gladys. - She's mine.
[ERROR API]
- She's mine. - She's mine.
Look, I'm sorry I didn't give them your tape.
[ERROR API]
And I promise next time to submit you, whether I think you're right or not.
That's not the point, Chandler. The point is that you lied.
[ERROR API]
I know. You're right.
Oh, what's it gonna take for you to forgive me?
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
Oh, excellent.
Oh, excelente.
Now what do you say?
[ERROR API]
Lying is wrong.
And? And?
[ERROR API]
I'm a pretty little girl.
I knew it. Ha, ha.
[ERROR API]
Your ex-boyfriend is insane.
- Did you get the grant? - No. And you wanna know why?
[ERROR API]
Because your ex-boyfriend is still in love with you.
What?
¿Qué?
He refused me because I wouldn't give you up.
[ERROR API]
Benji isn't in love with me. I mean, he broke up with me.
- And besides, he's a very ethical man. - Really?
[ERROR API]
Is it ethical to ask someone in a grant review:
"Who was the voice of Underdog?"
[ERROR API]
I'm sure he was just joking.
If you don't believe me, let's go talk to him.
[ERROR API]
I'm telling you, he didn't ask me one paleontological question.
- Seriously? - Oh, I'm sorry. No, he did ask me one:
[ERROR API]
Uh, "How do you spell Boscodictiasaur?"
Well, if it's like the Lake Mbosco in Congo, then M-B-O...
[ERROR API]
Damn it.
Maldición.
Dr. Geller. Charlie, what are you doing here?
[ERROR API]
I want you to tell her everything.
About the deal you tried to make with me, about the crazy questions you...
[ERROR API]
Wally Cox. That's the voice of Underdog.
Like I tried to tell you in the interview...
[ERROR API]
...this grant is not based on your knowledge of pretty useless trivia.
No, don't do that. I want you to look her in the eyes and tell her the truth.
[ERROR API]
Benji?
It's true. I behaved horribly, but it's only because I still love you.
[ERROR API]
And I would do anything to have you back in my life.
Too little, too late, Benji.
[ERROR API]
- I can't believe this. - I never should've broken up with you.
I think about you all the time. Do you ever still think about me?
Pienso en ti todo el tiempo. ¿Tú todavía piensas en mí?
No.
- Yes. - What?
- Sí. - ¿Qué?
I don't know what to say, Benji. This is all so...
No sé qué decir, Benji. Todo esto es tan...
...romantic.
...romántico.
Or?
¿O?
I know I may be way out of bounds here...
Sé que me estoy metiendo donde no me llaman...
...but is there any chance you would take me back?
...pero, ¿hay alguna posibilidad de que me perdones?
Maybe.
Quizás.
Sweetie, this conversation is starting to make me a little uncomfortable.
Cariño, esta conversación me está empezando a incomodar un poco.
Oh, God. I am so sorry, but...
Dios mío. Lo siento muchísimo, pero...
I mean, there's so much history between us, you know?
O sea, hay mucha historia entre nosotros, ¿sabes?
I'm sorry too.
Yo también lo siento.
- I love you. - Oh, I love you too.
- Te amo. - Oh, yo también te amo.
Okay, that's it, we are seeing other people.
Okay, eso es todo, vamos a ver a otras personas.
Gladys?
¿Gladys?
For the third time this week. Man, this does not get old.
Por tercera vez esta semana. Vaya, esto nunca cansa.
- You're mean! - Oh, don't be such a baby. Please.
- ¡Eres malo! - Oh, no seas un bebé. Por favor.