Hey, out of all of us, who do you think will get married next?
Oigan, de todos nosotros, ¿quién creen que se casará primero?
Probably Monica and Chandler.
Probablemente Monica y Chandler.
Hi, could I have a pack of Newport Lights?
Hola, ¿me podría dar un paquete de Newport Lights?
Oh, um, uh, we don't sell cigarettes, but they do across the street.
Oh, eh, eh, no vendemos cigarros, pero venden cruzando la calle.
That'd be great. Thanks.
Sería genial. Gracias.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
Melissa Worbert. I don't think I have the energy for this.
Melissa Worbert. No creo que tenga energía para esto.
Oh, my God! Ray-Ray Green?
¡Dios mío! ¿Ray-Ray Green?
Melissa. Hey.
Melissa. Hola.
You've been MIA for seven sorority newsletters.
Has estado desaparecida en siete boletines de la fraternidad.
What's up with you?
¿Qué hay de ti?
Why don't I tell you over here?
¿Por qué no te cuento aquí?
So last I heard you were gonna get married.
Entonces, lo último que supe es que te ibas a casar.
Oh.
Poor Ray-Ray.
Pobre Ray-Ray.
Oh, no, no. It's... It's good. It's all good.
Oh, no, no. Está... Está bien. Todo está bien.
- I actually work at Ralph Lauren. - Shut up!
- De hecho, trabajo en Ralph Lauren. - ¡Cállate!
I will not. Heh, heh. I'm the divisional head of men's sportswear.
No lo haré. Je, je. Soy el jefe divisional de ropa deportiva para hombres.
Oh, shut up more! Are you friends with Ralph?
¡Cállate más! ¿Eres amigo de Ralph?
- Oh, please. Ha. - Are you?
- Oh, por favor. Ja. - ¿Lo eres?
No.
Listen, we have to have dinner. What are you doing tomorrow?
Escucha, tenemos que cenar. ¿Qué haces mañana?
- Oh, tomorrow. I don't know. Um... - You're having dinner with me.
- Oh, mañana. No sé. Eh... - Vas a cenar conmigo.
Shut up.
Cállate.
I've gotta go. This has been so great, Ray-Ray.
Tengo que irme. Ha sido genial, Ray-Ray.
Oh, there you are.
Oh, aquí estás.
Um, so listen, just call me. Here's my card.
Eh, entonces escucha, solo llámame. Aquí está mi tarjeta.
Oh, wow, thanks.
Oh, wow, gracias.
- Oh, you're in real estate? - Oh, no, heh, that's an old card.
- Oh, ¿trabajas en bienes raíces? - Oh, no, je, esa es una tarjeta vieja.
Um, I got out of that to do something where I could...
Eh, dejé eso para hacer algo donde pudiera...
...help people and make a difference.
...ayudar a la gente y marcar la diferencia.
Wow. What do you do now?
Wow. ¿Qué haces ahora?
I'm a party planner.
Soy organizadora de fiestas.
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
- Te veo mañana. - Vale.
Hey guys, look who's back. It's Ray-Ray.
Hey chicos, miren quién volvió. Es Ray-Ray.
That was my friend, Melissa, from college.
Esa era mi amiga, Melissa, de la universidad.
She seems really, really fun!
¡Parece muy, muy divertida!
She's actually very sweet, and we used to be very close.
En realidad es muy dulce, y solíamos ser muy cercanas.
Wait a minute. She's not the one who you?
Espera un minuto. Ella no es la que tú...
Who you what? Who you what?
¿Tú qué? ¿Tú qué?
- Yes. - Wow!
- Sí. - ¡Wow!
Wow... Wow, what? Who you what?
Wow... ¿Wow, qué? ¿Tú qué?
Oh, it's not a big deal.
Oh, no es gran cosa.
They were lovers.
Eran amantes.
- What? - What?
- ¿Qué? - ¿Qué?
No, we weren't. It was nothing.
No, no lo fuimos. No fue nada.
It was one night, senior year, and we went to a party...
Fue una noche, el último año, y fuimos a una fiesta...
...had a lot of sangria, and you know, ended up...
...tomamos mucha sangría, y ya sabes, terminamos...
...kissing for a bit.
...besándonos un rato.
So that's two of my wives.
Entonces, esas son dos de mis esposas.
Okay, so this is where the band is. And here's the bar.
[ERROR API]
And all these pins have people's names on them. Rach, here you are.
Oh, wow!
[ERROR API]
Why don't we just put me with a Manhattan in my hand...
...talking to the cute bartender.
[ERROR API]
These pins aren't for playing, are they?
Okay, the red ones are my guests, and the blue are yours.
[ERROR API]
This is so sad. I only have like 10 pins.
Heh, Chandler, relax. It's not a contest.
[ERROR API]
Certainly not a close one.
- Hello. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Hey, Rach.
Hola, Rach.
Stop picturing it!
[ERROR API]
Okay, I think that's it. The seating chart is done. This is our wedding.
Wow. They all look like they're having fun.
[ERROR API]
So where are my parents gonna be?
Oh.
Well, if this is the wedding hall, then, um...
[ERROR API]
...your parents would be over here at home in Queens.
They're not invited? Oh, no, they're gonna be crushed!
[ERROR API]
Why would they think they're invited?
You got me. I don't...
[ERROR API]
- Joey! - Look, I thought parents were coming.
Your parents are coming. Chandler's parents are coming.
[ERROR API]
Ross' parents are coming.
Ross' parents are my parents.
[ERROR API]
Well, see, parents are coming.
- We should invite them. - You just want more blue pins.
[ERROR API]
Well, this is just sad.
All right. Maybe I can fit them in if I just do some rearranging.
[ERROR API]
Rachel may have to sit at the bar.
That is not a problem.
[ERROR API]
- Maybe you'll order a little sangria. - Oh, get out of here!
These are our tuxedos. If you like anything, we can make a deal.
[ERROR API]
Anything at all. But these are the three that Monica pre-approved.
Uh, well, thanks a lot for hooking me up.
[ERROR API]
And I want you to know that I want you to attend our wedding as my guest.
I'm Monica's maid of honor.
[ERROR API]
Okay, don't try to blue-pin me.
- Well, these look nice. - They are nice.
[ERROR API]
When celebrities are done with them, they send them back.
- You mean, like, for award shows? - Some of them.
[ERROR API]
They've been down the red carpet with people yelling, uh...
..."Who are you wearing? You look fabulous!"
[ERROR API]
Might I suggest watching a little more ESPN...
...and a little less E!
[ERROR API]
Okay. Who wore those?
Uh...
Eh...
- Well, uh, this one's Tom Brokaw. - Not bad.
[ERROR API]
This one is, uh, Paul O'Neil.
Who's that?
¿Quién es?
He plays for the Yankees. Seriously, ESPN.
Juega para los Yankees. En serio, ESPN.
Just once in a while. Have it on in the background.
Solo de vez en cuando. Lo tengo de fondo.
Ooh, this one was Pierce Brosnan.
Ooh, este era de Pierce Brosnan.
- Pierce Brosnan? - Uh-huh.
- ¿Pierce Brosnan? - Ajá.
Are you serious?
¿Hablas en serio?
007?
¿007?
This is James Bond's tux? Oh, I have to get married in James Bond's tux.
¿Este es el esmoquin de James Bond? Oh, me tengo que casar con el esmoquin de James Bond.
Ha, ha. It's a pretty cool tux.
Ja, ja. Es un esmoquin bastante genial.
Ah, it's not just that. I would be England's most powerful weapon.
Ah, no es solo eso. Sería el arma más poderosa de Inglaterra.
A jet-setting heartbreaker on Her Majesty's secret service.
Un rompecorazones jet-setter al servicio secreto de Su Majestad.
A man who fears no one, with a license to kill.
Un hombre que no teme a nadie, con licencia para matar.
Would Monica let me wear this?
¿Mónica me dejaría ponerme esto?
We should really learn how to play the real way.
Deberíamos aprender a jugar de verdad.
I like our way.
Me gusta nuestra forma.
- Ah! - Hey, hey!
- ¡Ah! - ¡Oye, oye!
Chess!
¡Ajedrez!
- Nice move. - Yeah.
- Buena jugada. - Sí.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
I hooked Ross and Chandler up with tuxedos. Do you need one?
Les conseguí esmóquines a Ross y Chandler. ¿Necesitas uno?
No, I'm not wearing a tux.
No, no voy a usar esmoquin.
- What are you gonna wear? - Multi-colored robes.
- ¿Qué vas a usar? - Túnicas multicolores.
Ooh, and maybe a hat.
Ooh, y quizás un sombrero.
- Huh. Does Monica know about this? - No.
- ¿Eh? ¿Mónica sabe de esto? - No.
Can I please be there when you tell her?
¿Puedo estar ahí cuando se lo digas?
Hey, Rach, you want to go to a movie tonight?
Oye, Rach, ¿quieres ir al cine esta noche?
Oh, I can't. I'm having dinner with Melissa.
Oh, no puedo. Ceno con Melissa.
Can I come?
¿Puedo ir?
I won't talk. You'll just hear my video camera.
No hablaré. Solo oirás mi cámara de video.
- What? What's going on? - Can I tell her?
- ¿Qué? ¿Qué está pasando? - ¿Puedo decirle?
Do you want what happened, or Joey's lewd version?
¿Quieres lo que pasó, o la versión lasciva de Joey?
- Joey's. - Okay.
- La de Joey. - Vale.
Okay, come on.
Vale, vamos.
I had this college friend...
Tenía esta amiga de la universidad...
...and I made the mistake of telling Joey that one time...
...y cometí el error de decirle a Joey que una vez...
...she and I, you know, kissed a little bit.
...ella y yo, ya sabes, nos besamos un poco.
Yeah, I'm sure that happened.
Sí, seguro que eso pasó.
- It did. - Sure.
- Pasó. - Seguro.
Hey, heh. It happened.
Oye, je. Pasó.
Yeah, it was senior year. It was after the Sigma Chi luau...
Sí, era el último año. Fue después del luau de Sigma Chi...
...and Melissa and I got very drunk.
...y Melissa y yo nos emborrachamos mucho.
And we ended up kissing. For several minutes.
Y terminamos besándonos. Durante varios minutos.
Which means she had a couple spritzers and a peck on the cheek.
Lo que significa que ella tomó un par de copitas y un beso en la mejilla.
- Why are you taking this away from me? - Ugh.
- ¿Por qué me quitas esto? - Ugh.
Why is it so hard for you to believe?
¿Por qué te cuesta tanto creerlo?
Okay. I just didn't know that you were a lesbian.
Está bien. Simplemente no sabía que eras lesbiana.
I'm not saying that I'm a lesbian. I'm just saying that this happened.
No digo que sea lesbiana. Solo digo que esto pasó.
It just seems pretty wild. And you're... You know, so...
Parece bastante salvaje. Y tú eres... ya sabes, tan...
...vanilla.
...normal.
Vanilla? I'm not vanilla. I do lots of crazy things.
¿Normal? No soy normal. Hago muchas cosas locas.
I mean, I got drunk and married in Vegas.
O sea, me emborraché y me casé en Las Vegas.
To Ross.
Por Ross.
If you don't believe me...
Si no me crees...
...just come with me to dinner tonight and she'll tell you.
...solo ven conmigo a cenar esta noche y ella te lo dirá.
Okay. Because I can't picture it.
Está bien. Porque no me lo imagino.
You should get inside my head.
Deberías meterte en mi cabeza.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Guess what I got for your wedding?
¿Adivina qué conseguí para tu boda?
A freakishly thin date with a hanger for a head?
¿Una cita freakishly delgada con una percha por cabeza?
Rachel hooked me up with a tux. But not just any tux.
Rachel me consiguió un esmoquin. Pero no uno cualquiera.
Batman's tux!
¡El esmoquin de Batman!
- What? - That's right.
- ¿Qué? - Así es.
Made expressly for Val Kilmer, and worn by him in the hit film...
Hecho expresamente para Val Kilmer, y usado por él en la exitosa película...
...that Batman film he was in.
...esa película de Batman en la que estuvo.
You can't wear that. I'm wearing the famous tux.
No puedes usar eso. Yo llevo el famoso esmoquin.
- James Bond's tux. - So?
- El esmoquin de James Bond. - ¿Y qué?
If you wear that, it'll make mine less special.
Si usas eso, el mío será menos especial.
You need something to to make it special?
¿Necesitas algo para hacerlo especial?
Hello! You have the most special thing of all.
¡Hola! Tienes lo más especial de todo.
You are marrying the woman you love.
Te vas a casar con la mujer que amas.
Don't take away my cool thing. Pretty please?
No me quites mi cosa genial. ¿Porfis?
"Pretty please?" Not very, uh, 007.
¿"Porfis"? No muy, eh, 007.
If you were getting married, I'd never do anything to upset you.
Si te fueras a casar, yo nunca haría nada para molestarte.
- You slept with my sister. - That was pretty 007.
- Te acostaste con mi hermana. - Eso sí que fue muy 007.
- Hey. - Hey. Okay, good. You're here.
- Hola. - Hola. Bien. Estás aquí.
All right, I figured it out.
Muy bien, lo he resuelto.
I'm gonna take 2 tables of 8, add your parents...
Voy a tomar 2 mesas de 8, añadir a tus padres...
...and make them into 3 tables of 6.
...y hacerlas en 3 mesas de 6.
And I called the caterer. We are good to go!
Y llamé al catering. ¡Estamos listos!
Yeah. They're not coming.
Sí. No vienen.
What?
¿Qué?
They think that you only invited them because of me.
Creen que solo los invitaste por mi culpa.
They feel unwanted.
Se sienten no deseados.
That's too bad. It's true. But too bad.
Qué lástima. Es verdad. Pero qué lástima.
- If you could just call my mom. - Oh, Joey.
- Si pudieras llamar a mi mamá. - Oh, Joey.
Come on. Just let her know you want them there.
Vamos. Solo hazle saber que los quieres allí.
Let's not forget this is a woman who has sent you many lasagnas.
No olvidemos que es una mujer que te ha enviado muchas lasañas.
No, she hasn't.
No, no lo ha hecho.
Is it her fault if some didn't make it to you?
¿Es culpa suya si algunas no te llegaron?
What am I gonna say?
¿Qué voy a decir?
Just tell them you mixed up invitations. No, no, no, blame it on the post office.
Solo diles que mezclaste las invitaciones. No, no, no, échale la culpa al cartero.
They hate the post office. And the Irish.
Odia al cartero. Y a los irlandeses.
But I don't think you could blame it on them.
Pero no creo que puedas culparlos a ellos.
Hello? Yeah, hi. Uh, Mrs. Tribbiani? Hi, this is Monica Geller.
¿Hola? Sí, hola. Eh, ¿Sra. Tribbiani? Hola, soy Monica Geller.
I'm just calling to say that I really hope you can make the wedding.
Solo llamo para decir que realmente espero que pueda venir a la boda.
Apparently some of our invitations weren't delivered.
Aparentemente, algunas de nuestras invitaciones no fueron entregadas.
Um, I guess there was some screw-up at the damn post office.
Eh, supongo que hubo algún error en la maldita oficina de correos.
Tell me about it.
Ni me digas.
Yeah, the U.S. Post Office? No. More like U.S. Lost Office.
Sí, ¿la Oficina de Correos de EE. UU.? No. Más bien la Oficina Perdida de EE. UU.
What are they, Irish?
¿Qué son, irlandeses?
Anyway, his name's Allen. And we've been going out for three years.
Bueno, él se llama Allen. Y llevamos saliendo tres años.
He was my first client when I became a party planner.
Fue mi primer cliente cuando me convertí en organizadora de fiestas.
He was actually planning a party for his girlfriend at the time.
En realidad, él estaba planeando una fiesta para su novia en ese momento.
- Oh, well. - No.
- Oh, bueno. - No.
- Ah. He was Theta Beta Pi at Syracuse. - Oh! Oh, that's great.
- Ah. Él era de Theta Beta Pi en Syracuse. - ¡Oh! Oh, eso es genial.
Mm-hm.
- Phoebe, were you ever in a sorority? - Of course.
- Phoebe, ¿tú estuviste en alguna hermandad? - Claro.
Yes. I was a, um, Thigh Mega Tampon.
Sí. Yo era, eh, Thigh Mega Tampon.
What one?
¿En cuál?
Yeah, we were huge too. But they had to shut us down...
Sí, nosotras también éramos enormes. Pero tuvieron que cerrarnos...
...when Regina Phalangie died of alcohol poisoning.
...cuando Regina Phalangie murió por intoxicación etílica.
Ugh.
Isn't it a shame when one girl ruins it for the whole bunch?
¿No es una pena cuando una chica arruina todo el grupo?
Hmm. Mm-hm. Ugh.
Anyway...
De todos modos...
Speaking of drinking too much, I was, uh, telling Phoebe...
Hablando de beber demasiado, le estaba, eh, contando a Phoebe...
...about that crazy night after the Sigma Chi luau where we made out.
...sobre esa noche loca después del luau de Sigma Chi donde nos besamos.
What?
¿Qué?
Remember we... Come on, we had sarongs on and the coconut bikini tops.
Recuerdas que... Vamos, llevábamos pareos y tops de bikini de coco.
We went back to the house and got really silly...
Volvimos a la casa y nos pusimos muy tontas...
...and we made out.
...y nos besamos.
Wow, Ray-Ray, I have no idea what you're talking about.
Vaya, Ray-Ray, no tengo ni idea de qué estás hablando.
Really?
¿En serio?
Ross is Batman.
Ross es Batman.
Well, he did manage to keep his identity secret for a long time.
Bueno, logró mantener su identidad en secreto durante mucho tiempo.
Rachel got Ross the tuxedo that Val Kilmer wore in Batman.
Rachel le consiguió a Ross el esmoquin que Val Kilmer usó en Batman.
Batman is so much cooler than James Bond.
Batman es mucho más genial que James Bond.
- What? 007 has all those gadgets. - Batman has a utility belt.
- ¿Qué? 007 tiene todos esos gadgets. - Batman tiene un cinturón de utilidades.
- 007 has a fancy car. - Batman has the Batmobile.
- 007 tiene un coche elegante. - Batman tiene el Batmobile.
- 007 gets all the ladies. - Heh. Batman has Robin.
- 007 se liga a todas las chicas. - Je. Batman tiene a Robin.
We get ESPN, right?
Tenemos ESPN, ¿verdad?
How about you go put on your 007 tuxedo, and I'll make you a nice martini?
¿Qué tal si vas a ponerte tu esmoquin de 007 y te preparo un buen martini?
Actually I don't like martinis.
En realidad no me gustan los martinis.
- A Yoo-Hoo with a funny straw? - Ooh, yum.
- ¿Un Yoo-Hoo con una pajita divertida? - Ooh, qué rico.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
I know the invitation says 6:00...
Sé que la invitación dice las 6:00...
...but does that mean get there at 6, or the show starts at 6?
...pero ¿eso significa llegar a las 6, o que el espectáculo empieza a las 6?
The show?
¿El espectáculo?
Right, the wedding. Gotcha.
Correcto, la boda. Entendido.
But weddings start a little late, right?
Pero las bodas empiezan un poco tarde, ¿verdad?
Have you ever been to one of my weddings?
¿Has estado alguna vez en una de mis bodas?
Ah, well, it's the same day as my niece's christening...
Ah, bueno, es el mismo día que el bautizo de mi sobrina...
...and I want my parents to see me.
...y quiero que mis padres me vean.
My part's in the beginning. I'm not in the rest of the show... Wedding.
Mi parte es al principio. No estoy en el resto del espectáculo... Boda.
The wedding starts at 6.
La boda empieza a las 6.
Okay. I totally hear you.
Okay. Te entiendo perfectamente.
Ooh! How about this? I vamp till they get there.
¡Ooh! ¿Qué tal esto? Yo amenizo hasta que lleguen.
Heh. You'll "vamp"?
¿Je. Vas a "amenizar"?
Yeah, yeah, like warm up the crowd. Ask where they're from.
Sí, sí, como calentar al público. Preguntar de dónde son.
In Joey Tribbiani, you get a minister and an entertainer.
Con Joey Tribbiani, tienes un ministro y un animador.
I'm a "ministainer."
Soy una "mini estrella de cine".
All right?
¿De acuerdo?
There's no one better. There's no one greater.
No hay nadie mejor. No hay nadie más grande.
Huh?
¿Eh?
How can you not remember us kissing?
¿Cómo puedes no recordar que nos besamos?
I don't know. I don't remember a lot of things that never happened.
No sé. No recuerdo muchas cosas que nunca sucedieron.
Wha...
¿Qúe...
Remember, we were on the sleeping porch? We couldn't stop giggling.
Recuerda, estábamos en el porche para dormir. No podíamos parar de reír.
Our coconuts kept knocking together.
Nuestras cabezas chocaban.
Somewhere Joey's head is exploding.
En algún lugar, la cabeza de Joey está explotando.
I don't want to make you uncomfortable...
No quiero incomodarte...
...but I told Phoebe it happened, and she doesn't believe me.
...pero le dije a Phoebe que sucedió, y ella no me cree.
I'm sorry. I mean, if I thought it happened, I would say it.
Lo siento. Digo, si creyera que sucedió, lo diría.
Maybe I passed out and you did stuff to me while I was sleeping.
Quizás me desmayé y tú hiciste cosas conmigo mientras dormía.
No.
It's okay, you don't have to do this. I believe you.
Está bien, no tienes que hacer esto. Te creo.
If you say you kissed Melissa, then you kissed Melissa.
Si dices que besaste a Melissa, entonces besaste a Melissa.
- Thank you, Phoebe. - Okay.
- Gracias, Phoebe. - De acuerdo.
- But she didn't. - I know.
- Pero no lo hizo. - Lo sé.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
You carry that around?
¿Llevas eso contigo?
Yes.
Sí.
I find it to be something of a conversation piece.
Lo encuentro una especie de tema de conversación.
- Between you and? - Gunther.
- ¿Entre tú y? - Gunther.
Hey, hey. Why don't we put them on?
Oye, oye. ¿Por qué no nos los ponemos?
Get a picture of Batman and James Bond, together.
Toma una foto de Batman y James Bond, juntos.
I would, but my pants are a little tight.
Lo haría, pero mis pantalones están un poco apretados.
A little tight? I could see 00 and 7 in those things.
¿Un poco apretados? Podría ver el 00 y el 7 en esos pantalones.
I was looking forward to wearing our celebrity tuxes together.
Tenía ganas de usar nuestros esmóquines de celebridad juntos.
- So you're not gonna be wearing yours? - Are you kidding? It's Batman's tux!
- ¿Entonces no vas a usar el tuyo? - ¿Estás bromeando? ¡Es el esmoquin de Batman!
Let me try it on.
Déjame probarlo.
Okay. But just the jacket. 00 and 7 are not getting in there.
De acuerdo. Pero solo la chaqueta. El 00 y el 7 no entrarán ahí.
Okay.
Holy double-vented comfort, Batman!
¡Santo confort de doble ventilación, Batman!
- What's this? - Huh?
- ¿Qué es esto? - ¿Eh?
An invitation to the At First Sight premiere?
¿Una invitación al estreno de 'At First Sight'?
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
Val Kilmer didn't wear this in Batman.
Val Kilmer no usó esto en Batman.
He wore it to the premiere of a fruity love story where he was a blind guy.
Lo usó para el estreno de una historia de amor cursi donde él era un ciego.
Let me see that.
Déjame ver eso.
Oh, man.
Oh, Dios.
The only super power you have is the slightly heightened sense of smell.
El único superpoder que tienes es el sentido del olfato ligeramente agudizado.
Hey.
Oye.
Uh, can I talk to you guys for a second?
Uh, ¿puedo hablar con ustedes un segundo?
I give up. Whatever you want, you can have it.
Me rindo. Lo que quieras, lo tendrás.
You want to sing a song or do a dance?
¿Quieres cantar una canción o bailar?
You want your mom at the altar screaming racial slurs? I don't care.
¿Quieres a tu mamá en el altar gritando insultos raciales? No me importa.
No. I just want to thank you guys for what you did for my parents.
No. Solo quiero agradecerles por lo que hicieron por mis padres.
They're so happy to get to be a part of your special day.
Están tan felices de poder ser parte de tu día especial.
Oh.
Well, your welcome. Tell them we're glad they're coming.
De nada. Diles que estamos contentos de que vengan.
I will. Oh, check out what they got me to wear for the ceremony!
Lo haré. ¡Oh, mira lo que me hicieron usar para la ceremonia!
Huh?
¿Eh?
I wear it like this when I marry you guys. And then this...
Me lo pongo así cuando me caso con ustedes. Y luego esto...
...is for party time.
...es para la fiesta.
It happened. I am telling you it happened.
Pasó. Te digo que pasó.
Hey, it was great meeting you.
Oye, fue genial conocerlos.
And, uh, Rachel? I don't think I'll be calling you because, uh...
Y, eh, ¿Rachel? No creo que te llame porque, eh...
...you know, you've gotten weird.
...sabes, te has vuelto rara.
Take care, you guys.
Cuídense, chicos.
Wha... Wait a minute. Okay, look.
¿Q-? Espera un minuto. Está bien, mira.
That night was the one wild thing I've ever done in my life.
Esa noche fue lo único salvaje que he hecho en mi vida.
I won't let you take it away from me.
No te dejaré quitármelo.
So if you don't remember that, maybe you'll remember this...
Así que si no recuerdas eso, quizás recuerdes esto...
Oh, my God. You love me.
Dios mío. Me amas.
- What? - Of course I remember our kiss.
- ¿Qué? - Claro que recuerdo nuestro beso.
I think about it all the time.
Pienso en ello todo el tiempo.
I can still hear the coconuts knocking together, I...
Todavía puedo oír los cocos chocando, yo...
I didn't want to tell you, because I didn't think you'd return my love.
No quería decírtelo, porque no pensé que devolverías mi amor.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Aw! Look who's being suddenly shy.
¡Ay! Mira quién se pone tímido de repente.
You have to feel what I feel.
Tienes que sentir lo que yo siento.
Nobody can kiss that good and not mean it.
Nadie puede besar tan bien y no sentirlo.
I'm just a good kisser.
Solo soy un buen besador.
Shut up.
Cállate.
I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
Oh.
Oh, you don't have to be sorry.
Oh, no tienes que disculparte.
I'm obviously kidding.
Obviamente estoy bromeando.
I'm not in love with you. I'm not in love with her.
No estoy enamorado de ti. No estoy enamorado de ella.
I don't hear coconuts banging together.
No oigo cocos chocando.
I don't picture your face when I make love to my boyfriend.
No imagino tu cara cuando hago el amor con mi novio.
Anyway, I gotta go.
En fin, tengo que irme.
A kiss goodbye?
¿Un beso de despedida?
No? Okay.
¿No? Ok.
Wow!
¡Vaya!
I mean, I had no idea that that would...
Quiero decir, no tenía idea de que eso...
What the hell was that?
¿Qué demonios fue eso?
Just wanted to see what all the fuss was about.
Solo quería ver de qué se trataba todo el alboroto.
- And? - I've had better.
- ¿Y? - He tenido mejores.
I found one that fits.
Encontré uno que me queda.
Well, you know what they say? 23rd time's a charm.
Bueno, ¿sabes qué dicen? A la vigésimo tercera va la vencida.
Aw! Look at you, all handsome.
¡Ay! Mírate, todo guapo.
- Whose is it? - Oh, does it matter?
- ¿De quién es? - Oh, ¿importa?
All that matters is that you look so handsome.
Lo único que importa es que te ves muy guapo.
- Whose is it? - I don't want to say.
- ¿De quién es? - No quiero decirlo.
Come on, I don't care. Whose is it?
Vamos, no me importa. ¿De quién es?
Diane Keaton.