- Hey. Who wants French toast? - Oh, I'll have some.
- Hola. ¿Quién quiere tostadas francesas? - Oh, yo quiero un poco.
Me too. Eggs and milk in the fridge. Thanks.
Yo también. Huevos y leche en el refrigerador. Gracias.
Ow.
Ay.
- Oh, what's the matter, honey? - My hand feels weird.
- Oh, ¿qué pasa, cariño? - Me siento rara de la mano.
I guess it's because I'm engaged.
Supongo que es porque estoy comprometida.
- When will that start getting annoying? - Start?
- ¿Cuándo va a empezar a molestar eso? - ¿Empezar?
So let's actually get started on the wedding plans.
Entonces, empecemos de verdad con los planes de la boda.
- Okay. - Already?
- Está bien. - ¿Ya?
Yeah, we got a lot to do. We gotta think about the flowers...
Sí, tenemos mucho que hacer. Tenemos que pensar en las flores...
...the caterers, the music...
...los servicios de catering, la música...
- Oh, I got some thoughts on the music... - Chandler, too many cooks...
- Oh, tengo algunas ideas sobre la música... - Chandler, demasiados cocineros...
Take it from me. All you have to do is show up and try to say the right name.
Créeme. Lo único que tienes que hacer es aparecer e intentar decir el nombre correcto.
Okay.
- What in God's name is that? - Oh, my God, the wedding book?
- ¿Qué demonios es eso? - Oh, Dios mío, ¿el libro de bodas?
I haven't seen that since the 4th grade.
No he visto eso desde cuarto grado.
This baby has everything. Take, you know, locations for instance:
Este bebé lo tiene todo. Mira, por ejemplo, las ubicaciones:
First organized alphabetically, then geographically...
Primero organizadas alfabéticamente, luego geográficamente...
...then by square footage.
...luego por metraje cuadrado.
That is so smart. Ha.
Eso es muy inteligente. Ja.
Break it off. Ahem. Break it off, now.
Termínalo. Ejem. Termínalo, ahora.
And that should conclusively prove...
Y eso debería probar concluyentemente...
...that I had the idea for Jurassic Park first.
...que yo tuve la idea de Jurassic Park primero.
- Now, let's take a look... - Hey, Ross.
- Ahora, veamos... - Oye, Ross.
Phoebe, oh, my God, what are you doing here?
Phoebe, oh, Dios mío, ¿qué haces aquí?
I need to talk to you. It's pretty urgent. It's about Monica and Chandler.
Necesito hablar contigo. Es bastante urgente. Es sobre Monica y Chandler.
Oh, my God. Um, of course.
Oh, Dios mío. Eh, por supuesto.
Uh, would you please excuse me for a moment?
Eh, ¿me disculpas un momento?
Um, heh, do you know each other's hometowns? Why don't you?
Eh, je, ¿se conocen las ciudades de origen del otro? ¿Por qué no lo hacen?
What's going on?
¿Qué está pasando?
Well, um, not much. I was just thinking that since those guys just got engaged...
Bueno, eh, no mucho. Solo estaba pensando que, ya que esos chicos acaban de comprometerse...
...that maybe it'd be nice if they had some privacy.
...que tal vez sería bueno que tuvieran algo de privacidad.
So could I just move in with you for a couple days?
Así que, ¿puedo mudarme contigo un par de días?
Um...
Okay, yeah, sure. But what's wrong with Monica and Chandler?
Está bien, sí, claro. Pero, ¿qué pasa con Monica y Chandler?
Nothing. Why?
Nada. ¿Por qué?
Phoebe, you said it was urgent.
Phoebe, dijiste que era urgente.
Oh, yeah, it is. I'm going to the movies and it starts in like five minutes.
Oh, sí, lo es. Voy al cine y empieza en como cinco minutos.
Do you realize I have a classroom full of students?
¿Te das cuenta de que tengo un aula llena de estudiantes?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so rude. Does anyone want to come to the movies?
Oh, lo siento. Soy muy grosera. ¿Alguien quiere ir al cine?
I haven't cleared the budget with my parents yet...
Todavía no he aprobado el presupuesto con mis padres...
...but tell me how this is for music.
...pero dime, ¿cómo es esto para la música?
All right, um, a string quartet for the processional, a jazz trio for cocktails...
Está bien, eh, un cuarteto de cuerdas para la procesión, un trío de jazz para los cócteles...
...the Bay City Rollers for dancing...
...los Bay City Rollers para bailar...
Wait, that was for my 6th grade wedding.
Espera, eso fue para mi boda de sexto grado.
Well, you couldn't get them anyway. Ian doesn't play anymore, and Derek...
Bueno, de todos modos no podrías conseguirlos. Ian ya no toca, y Derek...
Well, Derek is a name I shouldn't know.
Bueno, Derek es un nombre que no debería saber.
Hey, Mon, do you have another pillow, you know, something a little snugglier?
Oye, Mon, ¿tienes otra almohada, sabes, algo un poco más acogedor?
Why are you napping over here instead of over at your place?
¿Por qué estás durmiendo la siesta aquí en lugar de en tu casa?
- The duck. - What, the duck?
- El pato. - ¿Qué, el pato?
What the hell did the damn duck do now?
¿Qué demonios hizo el maldito pato ahora?
Uh, well, he did not get sick somewhere in there...
Eh, bueno, no se enfermó en algún lado por ahí...
...and it was immediately found and properly cleaned up.
...y fue encontrado inmediatamente y limpiado adecuadamente.
Now, do I get to look at this book...
Ahora, ¿puedo ver este libro...
...or is it just for people who are actually involved in the wedding?
...o es solo para gente que está realmente involucrada en la boda?
Of course you can look at it. Yeah, I want your opinion too.
Claro que puedes verlo. Sí, también quiero tu opinión.
- Okay. - Here you go.
- Está bien. - Aquí tienes.
- What do you think about centerpieces? - Centerpieces.
- ¿Qué opinas de los centros de mesa? - ¿Centros de mesa?
- Roses or lilies? - Definitely roses.
- ¿Rosas o lirios? - Definitivamente rosas.
Well, I just think they're a bit more wedding-y, you know.
Bueno, creo que son un poco más de "boda", ¿sabes?
- But lilies are the clear choice. - Oh, my God, it's like one mind.
- Pero los lirios son la elección obvia. - Dios mío, es como si pensáramos igual.
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
Guys, guys, you gotta let me nap.
Chicos, chicos, déjenme dormir la siesta.
I'm gonna get cranky.
Me voy a poner de mal humor.
Joey, there is a perfectly good couch across the hall.
Joey, hay un sofá perfectamente bueno al otro lado del pasillo.
Yes, it is perfectly good...
Sí, está perfectamente bien...
...and it is not one of the places the duck got sick.
...y no es uno de los lugares donde el pato se enfermó.
What?
¿Qué?
- All right, I'm gonna go. - Joey, what did the duck do?
- Está bien, me voy. - Joey, ¿qué hizo el pato?
I don't know, but he did not eat your face cream.
No lo sé, pero no se comió tu crema facial.
Hey, little buddy.
Hola, amiguito.
How you feeling? Aah.
¿Cómo te sientes? Aah.
What the hell is in that face cream?
¿Qué demonios hay en esa crema facial?
That's so soft.
Está tan suave.
Pillowcases.
Fundas de almohada.
Oh, ah.
"Zelda looked at the chimney sweep. Her father, the vicar..."
"Zelda miró al deshollinador. Su padre, el vicario..."
Vicar?
¿Vicario?
"...wouldn't be home for hours.
"...no estaría en casa por horas."
Her loins were burning.
Sus lomos ardían.
She threw caution to the wind and reached out and grabbed his..."
Echó la prudencia al viento y extendió la mano y agarró su..."
Whoa.
This is a dirty book.
Este es un libro sucio.
Uh, Phoebe?
Eh, ¿Phoebe?
Oh, Ross, hi.
Oh, Ross, hola.
- Phoebe, what are you doing? - I'm sorry, I'm with a client right now.
- Phoebe, ¿qué estás haciendo? - Lo siento, estoy con un cliente ahora mismo.
- Phoebe. - Okay, let's talk outside.
- Phoebe. - Está bien, hablemos afuera.
Phoebe, you can't massage people in my apartment.
Phoebe, no puedes masajear gente en mi apartamento.
What's the big deal? I did it at Monica and Chandler's.
¿Cuál es el problema? Lo hice en el de Monica y Chandler.
And they knew about it?
¿Y ellos lo sabían?
Okay, look, Ross, what is this really about?
Está bien, mira, Ross, ¿de qué se trata realmente?
Look, this is my home, and I want to be able to come and go whenever I want.
Mira, este es mi hogar, y quiero poder entrar y salir cuando quiera.
Okay. I will find someplace else to do the rest of my appointments.
Está bien. Encontraré otro lugar para hacer el resto de mis citas.
I just don't know what the big deal is.
Simplemente no entiendo cuál es el gran problema.
The big deal is I don't want naked, greasy strangers in my apartment...
El gran problema es que no quiero extraños desnudos y grasientos en mi apartamento...
...when I want to kick back with a puzzle... Beer, cold beer.
...cuando quiero relajarme con un rompecabezas... Cerveza, cerveza fría.
Hey, Joey. What are you doing?
Hola, Joey. ¿Qué haces?
Sweeping. Why? Does it turn you on?
Barriendo. ¿Por qué? ¿Te excita?
No.
Hmm.
Mmm.
What if I was, uh, sweeping a chimney?
¿Y si estuviera, eh, barriendo una chimenea?
Joey, did you eat my face cream?
Joey, ¿te comiste mi crema facial?
Where are you going? The vicar won't be home for hours.
¿A dónde vas? El vicario no volverá hasta dentro de horas.
Joey...
...where did you learn that word?
...¿dónde aprendiste esa palabra?
Where do you think...
¿A dónde crees que...
...Zelda?
...¿Zelda?
- You found my book? - Yeah, I did.
- ¿Encontraste mi libro? - Sí, lo encontré.
Joey, what are you doing going into my bedroom?
Joey, ¿qué haces entrando en mi habitación?
Okay, I'm sorry. I went in there to take a nap.
Está bien, lo siento. Entré ahí para echar una siesta.
And I know I shouldn't have, but you got porn.
Y sé que no debí, pero tienes pornografía.
Ugh.
You know what? I don't care. I'm not ashamed of my book.
¿Sabes qué? No me importa. No me avergüenzo de mi libro.
There's nothing wrong with a woman enjoying a little erotica.
No hay nada de malo en que una mujer disfrute de un poco de erotismo.
It's just a healthy expression of female sexuality...
Es solo una expresión saludable de la sexualidad femenina...
...which, by the way, is something that you will never understand.
...que, por cierto, es algo que tú nunca entenderás.
You got porn.
Tienes pornografía.
- Hello. - Hi, is, uh, Phoebe here?
- Hola. - Hola, ¿está, eh, Phoebe aquí?
- Uh, no, no, she's out for the night. - Oh, great.
- Eh, no, no, salió por la noche. - Oh, genial.
Heh. Can I help you with something?
Je. ¿Puedo ayudarte en algo?
I don't know. Are you a masseur?
No sé. ¿Eres masajista?
Yes, I am.
Sí, lo estoy.
Great. Dad?
Genial. ¿Papá?
Thank you so much. I'll be back to pick him up in an hour.
Muchas gracias. Volveré a recogerlo en una hora.
So, Chandler, your parents must've been thrilled...
Entonces, Chandler, tus padres deben haber estado encantados...
...when you told them you were engaged.
...cuando les dijiste que estabas comprometido.
Oh, yeah. I should probably call them.
Oh, sí. Probablemente debería llamarles.
I remember when we first got engaged.
Recuerdo cuando nos comprometimos.
- I don't think I've heard that story. - Dad, you don't...
- Creo que no he oído esa historia. - Papá, tú no...
Well, I'd gotten Judy pregnant.
Bueno, había dejado a Judy embarazada.
I still don't know how.
Todavía no sé cómo.
You don't know how? Your dog thought my diaphragm was a chew toy.
¿No sabes cómo? Tu perro pensó que mi diafragma era un juguete para morder.
What a sweet story.
Qué historia tan tierna.
At least you're not hearing it at your 5th grade Halloween party.
Al menos no la oyes en tu fiesta de Halloween de quinto grado.
What? They wanted a scary story.
¿Qué? Querían una historia de miedo.
Anyway, we're really excited about our wedding plans.
De todos modos, estamos muy emocionados con los planes de nuestra boda.
Pretty soon we'll be making a big withdrawal from the Monica wedding fund.
Pronto haremos un gran retiro del fondo de bodas de Monica.
- What? - You tell her, Jack. I can't do it.
- ¿Qué? - Tú dile, Jack. Yo no puedo hacerlo.
What happened? You still have the wedding fund, don't you?
¿Qué pasó? Todavía tienes el fondo de bodas, ¿verdad?
We have it. Only now we call it "the beach house."
Lo tenemos. Solo que ahora lo llamamos "la casa de la playa".
I can't believe you spent my wedding fund on the beach house.
No puedo creer que gastaras mi fondo de bodas en la casa de la playa.
We're sorry. We assumed...
Lo sentimos. Asumimos...
...if you got married after you turned 30 you'd pay for it yourself.
...que si te casabas después de los 30, lo pagarías tú misma.
You bought the beach house when I was 23.
Compraste la casa de la playa cuando yo tenía 23.
Which means you had seven years of beach fun...
Lo que significa que tuviste siete años de diversión en la playa...
...and you can't put a price on that, sweetie.
...y no se le puede poner precio a eso, cariño.
We really do feel bad about this though.
De verdad que nos sentimos mal por esto.
We started saving again when you dated Richard.
Empezamos a ahorrar de nuevo cuando salías con Richard.
But then that went to hell, so we redid the kitchen.
Pero luego eso se fue al infierno, así que rehicimos la cocina.
What about when I started dating Chandler?
¿Y cuando empecé a salir con Chandler?
It was Chandler. We didn't think he'd ever propose.
Era Chandler. No pensamos que alguna vez propondría matrimonio.
Clearly I did not start drinking enough at the start of the meal. Heh.
Claramente no empecé a beber lo suficiente al inicio de la comida. Je.
I can't believe there is no money for my wedding.
No puedo creer que no haya dinero para mi boda.
We might still have some if your father hadn't thought...
Quizás todavía tendríamos algo si tu padre no hubiera pensado...
...to sell ice over the Internet.
...en vender hielo por internet.
- It seemed like such a simple idea. - Stupid, Jack. The word is stupid.
- Parecía una idea tan simple. - Estúpida, Jack. La palabra es estúpida.
All right, enough. I don't want to hear about it anymore.
Muy bien, suficiente. No quiero oír hablar más de esto.
Good luck, Chandler.
Buena suerte, Chandler.
Okay, now I'm going to...
Okay, ahora voy a...
...touch you.
...tocarte.
Oh, that's soft.
Oh, qué suave.
I can't believe this. Do you think your parents could help pay for it?
No puedo creer esto. ¿Crees que tus padres podrían ayudar a pagarlo?
I don't know.
No sé.
My mother spent most of her money on her fourth wedding.
Mi madre gastó la mayor parte de su dinero en su cuarta boda.
She's saving the rest for her divorce.
Ella está guardando el resto para su divorcio.
And any extra cash my father has, he saves for his yearly trips to...
Y cualquier dinero extra que mi padre tenga, lo guarda para sus viajes anuales a...
...Dollywood.
What happened at dinner?
¿Qué pasó en la cena?
My parents spent the money for our wedding.
Mis padres gastaron el dinero de nuestra boda.
My God, what did you order?
Dios mío, ¿qué pediste?
Wait, there's no money? Well, this is terrible.
Espera, ¿no hay dinero? Bueno, esto es terrible.
You guys are gonna have to get married in, like, a rec center.
Van a tener que casarse en, como, un centro comunitario.
- Honey, it's gonna be okay. - No, it's not gonna be okay. It sucks.
- Cariño, todo va a estar bien. - No, no va a estar bien. Es horrible.
- No swing band, no lilies. - No, you know what? It's gonna be okay.
- Sin banda de swing, sin lirios. - No, ¿sabes qué? Va a estar bien.
I mean, you don't need to have this...
O sea, no necesitas tener este...
...rustic Italian feast, you know?
...banquete rústico italiano, ¿sabes?
And you don't need this custom-made empire-waisted, duchess satin gown.
Y no necesitas este vestido hecho a medida de satén duquesa con corte imperio.
You can wear off-the-rack.
Puedes usar uno de rebajas.
Look, it really is gonna be okay.
Mira, de verdad va a estar bien.
The important thing is that we love each other and we're gonna get married.
Lo importante es que nos amamos y nos vamos a casar.
Do you even understand what "off-the-rack" means?
¿Entiendes siquiera lo que significa "de rebajas"?
Why don't you just pay for it yourself?
¿Por qué no lo pagas tú misma?
How? I don't have any money.
¿Cómo? No tengo dinero.
- Well, I have some. - How much?
- Bueno, yo tengo algo. - ¿Cuánto?
Well, close to...
Bueno, cerca de...
- Whoa! Are you kidding me? - What? How much?
- ¡Whoa! ¿Me estás bromeando? - ¿Qué? ¿Cuánto?
- It's enough for wedding scenario A. - Really?
- Es suficiente para el escenario A de la boda. - ¿En serio?
How great are you, you little saver? Heh.
Qué genial eres, pequeña ahorradora. Je.
The amount you have is exactly the budget of my dream wedding.
La cantidad que tienes es exactamente el presupuesto de la boda de mis sueños.
Oh, you guys are so made for each other.
Oh, ustedes dos están hechos el uno para el otro.
Well, you're not suggesting we spend all of the money on the wedding?
Bueno, ¿no sugieres que gastemos todo el dinero en la boda?
Uh, yeah.
Eh, sí.
Look, Mon, I've been saving this money for six years...
Mira, Mon, he estado ahorrando este dinero por seis años...
...and I kind of have some of it earmarked for the future, not just for a party.
...y tengo algo reservado para el futuro, no solo para una fiesta.
Wow. Hello, Mr. Chandler.
Vaya. Hola, Sr. Chandler.
Sweetie, this is the most special day of our lives.
Cariño, este es el día más especial de nuestras vidas.
I realize that, honey, but I'm not gonna spend all the money on one party.
Lo entiendo, cariño, pero no voy a gastar todo el dinero en una sola fiesta.
Honey, um, I love you. Heh.
Cariño, um, te amo. Je.
But, um, if you call our wedding a party one more time...
Pero, um, si llamas a nuestra boda una fiesta una vez más...
...you may not get invited.
...puede que no te inviten.
We can always earn more money, okay? But we're only gonna get married once.
Siempre podemos ganar más dinero, ¿okay? Pero solo nos vamos a casar una vez.
Look, I understand, but I have to put my foot down, okay? The answer is no.
Mira, entiendo, pero tengo que poner límites, ¿de acuerdo? La respuesta es no.
You're gonna have to put your foot down?
¿Vas a tener que poner límites?
Yes, I am.
Sí, lo estoy.
Wow. Money and a firm hand.
Vaya. Dinero y mano firme.
Finally a Chandler I can get on board with.
Por fin un Chandler con el que puedo estar de acuerdo.
- Hey, Rach. - Joey.
- Hola, Rach. - Joey.
Hey, Rach, do you smell smoke?
Oye, Rach, ¿hueles humo?
Uh-huh. I get it. Smoke, chimney, chimney sweep. Very funny. Ha, ha.
Ajá. Lo entiendo. Humo, chimenea, deshollinador. Muy gracioso. Ja, ja.
No, no, no, I'm serious. You don't smell it?
No, no, no, en serio. ¿No lo hueles?
Something's on fire.
Algo se está quemando.
No, I don't smell anything.
No, no huelo nada.
Oh, you know what? It's probably just your burning loins.
Oh, ¿sabes qué? Probablemente solo sean tus lomos ardientes.
- Hey, what are you guys talking about? - Nothing.
- Oye, ¿de qué están hablando? - De nada.
Mm, damn, this coffee's cold.
Mmm, maldita sea, este café está frío.
Hey, Rach, do you mind if I heat this up on your loins?
Oye, Rach, ¿te importa si lo caliento en tus lomos?
You know, I cannot believe you told him. Joey...
Sabes, no puedo creer que se lo dijeras. Joey...
So I guess you bought that book after we broke up, huh?
Así que supongo que compraste ese libro después de que rompimos, ¿eh?
Uh-huh, I did, because I wore out my first copy when I was with you.
Ajá, lo hice, porque desgasté mi primera copia cuando estaba contigo.
Oh, yeah? Yeah?
¿Ah, sí? ¿Sí?
Well, uh, when we were going out, I read tons of porno magazines.
Bueno, eh, cuando salíamos, leí un montón de revistas porno.
'Sup?
¿Qué onda?
Ross, how could you do that to an old man?
Ross, ¿cómo pudiste hacer eso a un anciano?
Excuse me, ladies.
Disculpen, señoras.
I'm sorry?
¿Perdón?
My massage client, Arthur.
Mi cliente de masajes, Arthur.
His daughter called and said some guy that worked for me...
Su hija llamó y dijo que un tipo que trabajaba para mí...
...gave him a really weird massage this afternoon.
...le dio un masaje muy raro esta tarde.
I gave him an extremely professional massage.
Le di un masaje extremadamente profesional.
He said you poked at him with wooden spoons.
Dijo que lo pinchaste con cucharas de madera.
Okay, so it wasn't a traditional massage.
Está bien, no fue un masaje tradicional.
But I did give him acupressure with a pair of chopsticks...
Pero sí le di acupresión con un par de palillos...
...and I gently exfoliated him with a mop.
...y lo exfolié suavemente con una mopa.
Well, he's never coming back, okay? You just cost me $80 a week.
Bueno, él nunca volverá, ¿de acuerdo? Me costaste $80 a la semana.
You know what? This is your fault. You didn't move his appointment.
¿Sabes qué? Esto es tu culpa. No moviste su cita.
Oh, it's my fault? You didn't have to massage him.
¿Ah, es mi culpa? No tenías que darle masajes.
You could've sent him away.
Podrías haberlo despedido.
You could've not rolled Tonka trucks up and down his back.
Podrías no haber rodado camiones Tonka por su espalda.
He said he liked that.
Dijo que le gustó eso.
You're right, you're right. I'm sorry.
Tienes razón, tienes razón. Lo siento.
Dude, what are you massaging an old man for?
Tío, ¿por qué le das masajes a un anciano?
- His daughter was hot. - Gotcha.
- Su hija estaba buena. - Ya veo.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Listen, um...
Escucha, um...
...I've been thinking.
...he estado pensando.
And it's not fair for me to ask you to spend all your money on our wedding.
Y no es justo que te pida que gastes todo tu dinero en nuestra boda.
I mean, you work really hard for that.
Quiero decir, trabajas muy duro para eso.
- Well. - Well, you work for that.
- Bueno. - Bueno, tú trabajas para eso.
Look, I thought about it too.
Mira, yo también lo pensé.
And I'm sorry. I think we should spend all of the money on the wedding.
Y lo siento. Creo que deberíamos gastar todo el dinero en la boda.
- You do? - Yeah, I'm putting my foot down.
- ¿De verdad? - Sí, voy a poner límites.
Yeah, look, when I proposed, I told you...
[ERROR API]
...that I would do anything to make you happy.
And if having the perfect wedding makes you happy...
[ERROR API]
...then that's what we're gonna do.
You are so sweet.
Eres tan dulce.
Oh, but wait.
[ERROR API]
What about our...? What about the future and stuff?
Ah, forget about the future and stuff.
[ERROR API]
So we only have two kids.
You know, we'll pick our favorite and that one will get to go to college.
[ERROR API]
- Have you thought about that? - Yeah.
How many kids were we gonna have?
[ERROR API]
Uh, four. A boy, twin girls and another boy.
What else did you think about?
[ERROR API]
Well, heh, stuff like where we'd live, you know.
Like a small place outside the city...
[ERROR API]
...where our kids could learn to ride their bikes and stuff.
We could have a cat that had a bell on its collar...
[ERROR API]
...and we could hear it every time it ran through the little kitty door.
Of course we'd have an apartment over the garage where Joey could grow old.
[ERROR API]
You know what?
¿Sabes qué?
I don't want a big, fancy wedding.
[ERROR API]
- Sure you do. - No.
I want everything that you've just said. I want a marriage.
[ERROR API]
- You sure? - Mm-hm.
- I love you so much. - I love you.
[ERROR API]
Hey, listen, when you were talking about our future, you said cat.
But you meant dog, right? Ha, ha.
[ERROR API]
- Ha, yeah, totally. - Oh, good.
Hello, Zelda.
[ERROR API]
- Who are you supposed to be? - The vicar.
- Do you even know what a vicar is? - Like a goalie, right?
[ERROR API]
Yeah.
Sí.
Look, Joey, it's enough, all right?
[ERROR API]
You keep making these stupid jokes and these sleazy innuendoes...
...and it's just not funny anymore.
[ERROR API]
All right, I'm sorry. Rach, I'm sorry. Okay? I'm sorry.
Maybe I could make it up to you by taking you roughly in the barn.
[ERROR API]
Ugh.
All right, you know what? That's it. You want to do it? Let's do it.
[ERROR API]
Huh?
¿Eh?
That's right. I want to do it with you.
[ERROR API]
Been trying to fight it, but you just said all the right things.
Uh, I did?
[ERROR API]
Yeah, oh, I've been waiting so long to get on that body.
- This body? - Yeah, that's right.
[ERROR API]
Come on, Joey, sex me up.
Hey, you're starting to sound like the butcher's wife there in chapter seven.
[ERROR API]
Oh, come on, now. Don't keep me waiting. Get those clothes off.
But I would keep that helmet on, because you're in for a rough ride.
[ERROR API]
I don't want to. I'm scared.
No quiero. Tengo miedo.