Oh. Mm.
Oh. Mmm.
- Hi. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
You have got to try this cheesecake.
Tienes que probar este pastel de queso.
Oh, you know, I'm not that much of a sweet tooth...
Oh, sabes, no soy muy de dulces...
- Oh, my God, it's so creamy. - Oh.
- ¡Dios mío, está tan cremoso! - Oh.
Oh, my God. That's the best cheesecake I've ever had.
Dios mío. Es el mejor pastel de queso que he probado.
Where did you get this?
¿De dónde lo sacaste?
It was at the front door when I got home. Somebody sent it to us.
Estaba en la puerta cuando llegué a casa. Alguien nos lo envió.
Chandler, this isn't addressed to you.
Chandler, esto no es para ti.
This is addressed to Mrs. Braverman downstairs.
Esto es para la Sra. Braverman de abajo.
Thief.
Ladrón.
I didn't read the box before I opened it...
No leí la caja antes de abrirla...
...and you can't return a box after you opened it.
...y no puedes devolver una caja después de abrirla.
- Why not? - Because it's too delicious.
- ¿Por qué no? - Porque está demasiado delicioso.
Chandler, you stole this cheesecake. That is wrong.
Chandler, robaste este pastel de queso. Eso está mal.
No, no, no, it is going to be okay...
No, no, no, todo va a estar bien...
...because Mrs. Braverman is gonna send away for a free one.
...porque la Sra. Braverman va a pedir uno gratis.
And that way, we all win.
Y de esa manera, todos ganamos.
The only losers are the big cheesecake conglomerate:
Los únicos perdedores son el gran conglomerado de pasteles de queso:
"Mama's Little Bakery."
"La Pequeña Panadería de Mamá."
I feel terrible.
Me siento terrible.
I'm a horrible, horrible, horrible person.
Soy una persona horrible, horrible, horrible.
Well, I'm sorry, what?
Bueno, lo siento, ¿qué?
I should get going. Big day at work.
Debería irme. Gran día en el trabajo.
You know how I'm in a coma?
¿Sabes que estoy en coma?
Today they do a test on me and it turns out I'm not brain-dead.
Hoy me hacen una prueba y resulta que no estoy muerta cerebralmente.
So...
Así que...
Ah-ah, Mr. Smarty-Pants.
Ajá, señor sabelotodo.
It's just my character that's not brain-dead.
Es solo mi personaje el que no está muerto cerebralmente.
Pheebs, still on for tonight?
Pheebs, ¿sigues en pie para esta noche?
- Absolutely. Okay. - All right, I'll see you at 8.
- Absolutamente. De acuerdo. - Muy bien, te veo a las 8.
Oh, what's at 8?
Oh, ¿qué hay a las 8?
Oh, I have dinner plans with Joey.
Oh, tengo planes para cenar con Joey.
We get together about once a month to discuss the rest of you guys.
Nos reunimos aproximadamente una vez al mes para hablar del resto de ustedes.
Wow. Did not know that.
Vaya. No sabía eso.
May I say how lovely you look today?
¿Puedo decir lo encantadora que te ves hoy?
Duly noted.
Tomado en cuenta.
Oh, so for tomorrow...
Oh, entonces para mañana...
...do you want to rent a car and drive down together or what?
...¿quieres alquilar un coche y conducir juntas o qué?
What are you talking about?
¿De qué estás hablando?
Cousin Frannie's wedding. It's tomorrow night.
La boda de la prima Frannie. Es mañana por la noche.
You were invited?
¿Estuviste invitada?
No.
Oh, my God, I can't believe this.
Dios mío, no puedo creerlo.
I knew Mom and Dad were invited. I thought that was it.
Sabía que mamá y papá estaban invitados. Pensé que eso era todo.
I mean, from the ages of 7 to 9, Frannie and I were inseparable.
Quiero decir, de los 7 a los 9 años, Frannie y yo éramos inseparables.
Well, maybe since the age of 9, Frannie's made some new friends.
Bueno, tal vez desde los 9 años, Frannie ha hecho algunos amigos nuevos.
Look, it's probably just a mistake. Let me call Aunt Cheryl, okay?
Mira, probablemente sea solo un error. Déjame llamar a la tía Cheryl, ¿de acuerdo?
Maybe you are invited and the invitation just got lost in the mail.
Tal vez sí estás invitada y la invitación se perdió en el correo.
Yeah, well, you call her and tell her that, you know, when we were kids...
Sí, bueno, llámala y dile que, ya sabes, cuando éramos niños...
...her precious little Frannie tried to undress me several times, okay?
...mi pequeña y preciosa Frannie intentó desvestirme varias veces, ¿vale?
If I hadn't stopped her, there probably wouldn't be a wedding to go to.
Si no la hubiera detenido, probablemente no habría boda a la que ir.
She tried to undress me too.
Ella también intentó desvestirme a mí.
I used to undress my cousin Glenn.
Yo solía desvestir a mi primo Glenn.
Joseph Francis Tribbiani, are you home yet?
Joseph Francis Tribbiani, ¿ya llegaste a casa?
Um, I think he's still out. What's wrong?
Mmm, creo que todavía no ha salido. ¿Qué pasa?
Well, I'll tell you, Rachel Karen Green.
Bueno, te lo diré, Rachel Karen Green.
I had plans with Joey tonight, and he left me this note.
Tenía planes con Joey esta noche y me dejó esta nota.
"Pheebs, can't make it. Got a date. Talk to you later.
"Pheebs, no puedo ir. Tengo una cita. Hablamos luego.
Big Daddy."
Papá Grande."
- "Big Daddy"? - Oh, that's a nickname we were trying out.
- ¿"Papá Grande"? - Oh, es un apodo que estábamos probando.
Hey, you know what nickname never caught on? "The Ross-a-tron."
Oye, ¿sabes qué apodo nunca pegó? "El Ross-a-tron".
- Hey. - Oh, here's Joseph Francis.
- Hola. - Oh, aquí está Joseph Francis.
Whoa, what are you middle-naming me for?
¿Por qué me pones nombres de pila y segundo nombre?
I left you a note.
Te dejé una nota.
So what? That doesn't give you the right to ditch me.
¿Y qué? Eso no te da derecho a dejarme plantada.
Hey, you can cancel plans with friends if there's a possibility for sex.
Oye, puedes cancelar planes con amigos si hay posibilidad de sexo.
Phoebe, he's right. That is the rule.
Phoebe, tiene razón. Esa es la regla.
I don't accept this rule.
Yo no acepto esta regla.
When we make plans, I expect you to show up.
Cuando hacemos planes, espero que aparezcas.
Okay, I can't just be a way to kill time till you meet someone better.
Vale, no puedo ser solo una forma de matar el tiempo hasta que conozcas a alguien mejor.
You know, boyfriends and girlfriends are gonna come and go, but this is for life.
Sabes, novios y novias vendrán y se irán, pero esto es para toda la vida.
Wow. I'm so sorry. I had no idea it would bother you this much.
Vaya. Lo siento mucho. No tenía idea de que te molestaría tanto.
Well, it does.
Pues sí, me molesta.
Okay, can I make it up to you? Huh?
Vale, ¿puedo compensártelo? ¿Eh?
I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
How about dinner tomorrow night? I'll pay for myself.
¿Qué tal una cena mañana por la noche? Yo pago lo mío.
Okay, you wore me down.
Vale, me has convencido.
Joe, while you're over there, how about another beer for "The Ross-a-tron"?
Joe, ya que estás ahí, ¿otra cerveza para "El Ross-a-tron"?
"Ross..." Is that back?
¿"Ross..." ¿Eso ha vuelto?
- Hi. - The other cheesecake came.
- Hola. - Llegó la otra tarta de queso.
They delivered it to the wrong address again.
La entregaron en la dirección equivocada otra vez.
So just bring it back downstairs. What's the problem?
Entonces solo tráela aquí abajo. ¿Cuál es el problema?
I can't seem to say goodbye.
No puedo decir adiós.
Are you serious? Chandler, we ate an entire cheesecake two days ago...
¿Hablas en serio? Chandler, nos comimos una tarta de queso entera hace dos días...
...and you want more?
...¿y quieres más?
Well, I've forgotten what it tastes like, okay?
Bueno, he olvidado a qué sabe, ¿vale?
It was cheesecake. It was fine.
Era tarta de queso. Estaba bien.
It had a buttery, crumbly, graham-cracker crust...
Tenía una base de galleta de graham, mantecosa y desmenuzable...
...with a very rich...
...con un relleno de queso crema muy rico...
...yet light cream-cheese filling.
...pero ligero.
Wow, my whole mouth just filled with saliva. Ahem.
Vaya, se me hizo agua la boca. Ejem.
Know what? Forget it. We are just hungry.
¿Sabes qué? Olvídalo. Solo tenemos hambre.
We have not had lunch. We are just lightheaded.
No hemos almorzado. Estamos mareados.
So let us go out and have lunch and forget about the cheesecake.
Así que salgamos a almorzar y olvidémonos de la tarta de queso.
We'll drop it off downstairs so we're not tempted.
La dejaremos abajo para no caer en la tentación.
Where do you wanna go to lunch?
¿A dónde quieres ir a almorzar?
Mama's Little Bakery, Chicago, Illinois.
Aw.
Ay.
Mel Tormé died.
Murió Mel Tormé.
Joey, that paper's like a year old.
Joey, ese papel tiene como un año.
Oh, does that mean the Sam Goody's sale is over?
Oh, ¿eso significa que la oferta de Sam Goody's ya terminó?
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
So I finally heard back from Aunt Cheryl...
Bueno, finalmente me respondió la tía Cheryl...
...and apparently it wasn't a mistake.
...y aparentemente no fue un error.
Uh, there's limited seating in the hall...
Uh, hay asientos limitados en el salón...
Limited seating? I am just one tiny person.
¿Asientos limitados? Soy solo una personita.
Yeah, but she doesn't know that.
Sí, pero ella no lo sabe.
I mean, the last time she saw you...
O sea, la última vez que te vio...
...you would've turned one of those little wedding chairs into kindling.
...habrías convertido una de esas sillitas de boda en leña.
"Limited seating." That's such a lame excuse.
"Asientos limitados". Qué excusa tan tonta.
That's not the reason why she's not inviting me.
Esa no es la razón por la que no me está invitando.
What's the big deal? I wasn't even invited to the ceremony, just the reception.
¿Cuál es el problema? Ni siquiera me invitaron a la ceremonia, solo a la recepción.
And you know what? If it makes you feel any better...
Y sabes qué, si eso te hace sentir mejor...
...Joan and I will just make an appearance...
...Joan y yo solo haremos una aparición...
...and then we'll leave early as a sign of protest.
...y luego nos iremos temprano como señal de protesta.
- Joan? - Yeah, Joan Tedeschi, my date.
- ¿Joan? - Sí, Joan Tedeschi, mi cita.
She's an assistant professor in the Linguistics Department.
Es profesora asistente en el Departamento de Lingüística.
Tall, very beautiful.
Alta, muy guapa.
And despite what some people say, not broad-backed.
Y a pesar de lo que algunos dicen, no es de espalda ancha.
Wait a minute. You got "Ross Geller and guest"?
Espera un minuto. ¿Te pusieron "Ross Geller y acompañante"?
I wasn't invited, and you got "and guest"?
A mí no me invitaron, ¿y a ti te pusieron "y acompañante"?
Uh, excuse me, I do have to interrupt on Ross' behalf.
Uh, disculpen, tengo que interrumpir en nombre de Ross.
I think the rule applies here.
Creo que la regla aplica aquí.
Since he has a chance to get on broad-back...
Como tiene la oportunidad de ser de espalda ancha...
Not broad-back!
¡No de espalda ancha!
Wait a minute. You're bringing me.
Espera un minuto. ¿Me llevas a mí?
What? I can't cancel on Joan.
¿Qué? No puedo cancelar con Joan.
- Why not? - Did you not hear me?
- ¿Por qué no? - ¿No me oíste?
She's an assistant professor in the Linguistics Department, okay?
Es profesora asistente en el Departamento de Lingüística, ¿ok?
They're wild.
Son salvajes.
- Why do you want to come anyway? - Because...
- ¿Por qué quieres venir de todos modos? - Porque...
...she's my cousin.
...es mi prima.
I mean, we grew up together.
O sea, crecimos juntas.
Family, you know? And all that's important to me.
Familia, ¿sabes? Y todo eso es importante para mí.
Okay, all right. I'll take you.
Ok, está bien. Te llevo.
I'll go call Joan.
Voy a llamar a Joan.
Oh, that's nice.
Oh, qué bien.
Family should be there.
La familia debería estar ahí.
This is her wedding. Happiest day of her life.
Esta es su boda. El día más feliz de su vida.
We'll see. Ha, ha.
Ya veremos. Ja, ja.
Well, thank you for lunch.
Bueno, gracias por el almuerzo.
Wait a minute, I didn't pay. I thought you paid.
Espera un minuto, yo no pagué. Pensé que pagaste tú.
So apparently, we just don't pay for food anymore.
Así que aparentemente, ya no pagamos por la comida.
- Do you see what I see? - Huh! It's still there.
- ¿Ves lo que yo veo? - ¡Huh! Sigue ahí.
Mrs. Braverman must be out.
La señora Braverman debe estar fuera.
She could be out of town. Maybe she'll be gone for months.
Podría estar fuera de la ciudad. Quizás se vaya por meses.
By then, the cheesecake may have gone bad.
Para entonces, el pastel de queso podría haberse echado a perder.
We don't want her to come back to bad cheesecake.
No queremos que regrese a un pastel de queso echado a perder.
- That could kill her. - Wouldn't want that.
- Eso podría matarla. - No querríamos eso.
No, we're protecting her.
No, la estamos protegiendo.
- We should take it. - But move quick.
- Deberíamos llevarlo. - Pero muévete rápido.
- Why? - I heard her moving around in there.
- ¿Por qué? - La oí moverse ahí dentro.
Go, go, go.
Vamos, vamos, vamos.
Oh, my God, that's David.
Oh, Dios mío, es David.
- Who? - David, the scientist guy.
- ¿Quién? - David, el científico.
David that I was in love with.
David, de quien estuve enamorada.
David who went to Russia and broke my heart, David.
David, que se fue a Rusia y me rompió el corazón, David.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
Oh, you say someone's name enough, they turn around.
Ay, si dices el nombre de alguien lo suficiente, se da la vuelta.
- Phoebe. - David.
What are you doing here? Aren't you supposed to be in Russia?
¿Qué haces aquí? ¿No se suponía que estabas en Rusia?
Yeah, I'm just in town for a conference.
Sí, solo estoy de paso por una conferencia.
Um, God, you look phenomenal.
Um, Dios, te ves fenomenal.
Well, ha, ha...
Bueno, ja, ja...
Yeah.
Sí.
You look great too. Did you get a haircut?
Tú también te ves genial. ¿Te cortaste el pelo?
Yeah. Well, I got like 30 of them.
Sí. Bueno, me hice como 30 cortes.
Yeah.
Sí.
- Um, look, I got a confession to make. - Uh-huh.
- Um, mira, tengo que confesar algo. - Ajá.
Um, I was hoping to run into you here.
Um, esperaba encontrarte aquí.
I didn't know that I should call or not. You know, I was only in town a few days...
No sabía si llamarte o no. Sabes, solo estuve unos días...
...and, you know, I didn't want to intrude on your life or anything.
...y, sabes, no quería entrometerme en tu vida ni nada.
But I really wanted to see you...
Pero de verdad quería verte...
...but I didn't know if you wanted to see me.
...pero no sabía si tú querías verme.
Of course I would want to see you. I think about you all the time.
Claro que querría verte. Pienso en ti todo el tiempo.
Really? Because I think about you all the time.
¿En serio? Porque yo pienso en ti todo el tiempo.
- Really? - There's a statue in Minsk...
- ¿En serio? - Hay una estatua en Minsk...
...that reminds me of you so much.
...que me recuerda tanto a ti.
I mean, um, it's actually of Lenin...
Quiero decir, um, en realidad es de Lenin...
- ...but, you know, at certain angles... - Yeah.
- ...pero, sabes, desde ciertos ángulos... - Sí.
Anyway, do you want to have dinner tonight?
En fin, ¿quieres cenar esta noche?
Yes.
Sí.
- Oh, no. - Oh.
- Uh, what? - I can't.
- Eh, ¿qué? - No puedo.
I can't believe I have plans. I can't. Can you do it tomorrow?
No puedo creer que tenga planes. No puedo. ¿Puedes mañana?
Uh, no, I have to go in a few hours. I have to be on the redeye.
Eh, no, me voy en unas horas. Tengo que tomar el vuelo nocturno.
Well, listen, you know, next time you're in Minsk, uh...
Bueno, escucha, sabes, la próxima vez que estés en Minsk, eh...
- Phoebe? Can I talk to you for a second? - Uh-huh.
- ¿Phoebe? ¿Podemos hablar un segundo? - Ajá.
What are you doing?
¿Qué estás haciendo?
- Well, I have plans with Joey tonight. - So? He'll understand.
- Bueno, tengo planes con Joey esta noche. - ¿Y qué? Él entenderá.
No, he won't. And that's not even the point.
No, no lo hará. Y ese ni siquiera es el punto.
Monica, I made a whole speech about how you do not cancel plans with friends.
Monica, di todo un discurso sobre cómo no cancelas planes con amigos.
And now, you know, what? Just because, potentially, the love of my life...
Y ahora, ¿qué? ¿Solo porque, potencialmente, el amor de mi vida...
...comes back from Russia just for one night, I should change my beliefs?
...vuelve de Rusia solo por una noche, debo cambiar mis creencias?
I should change my beliefs.
Debo cambiar mis creencias.
No. No, no. If I don't have my principles, I don't have anything.
No. No, no. Si no tengo mis principios, no tengo nada.
God, you are so strong.
Dios, eres tan fuerte.
Or I should rush through dinner with Joey and I could meet David at 9.
O debería apurarme en la cena con Joey y podría ver a David a las 9.
Oh, my God, that is so good.
Oh, Dios mío, eso es genial.
I'm full. And yet I know if I stop eating this...
Estoy lleno. Y aun así sé que si dejo de comer esto...
...I'll regret it.
...me arrepentiré.
Hey, what have you got there?
Oye, ¿qué tienes ahí?
Oh, it's, um...
Oh, es, eh...
- It's tofu cake. Do you want some? - Aah.
- Es pastel de tofu. ¿Quieres un poco? - Aah.
- What are you doing tonight? - Huh?
- ¿Qué haces esta noche? - ¿Eh?
- Uh. - Dude. Dude.
- Uh. - Tío. Tío.
Sorry. Uh, I got those plans with Phoebe. Why?
Perdona. Uh, tengo esos planes con Phoebe. ¿Por qué?
Oh, really? Uh, Monica said she had a date at 9.
Oh, ¿en serio? Uh, Monica dijo que tenía una cita a las 9.
- What? Tonight? - That's what Monica said.
- ¿Qué? ¿Esta noche? - Eso dijo Monica.
After she gave me that big speech...
Después de que me diera todo ese discurso...
...she goes and makes a date on the same night she has plans with me?
...¿se va y hace una cita la misma noche que tiene planes conmigo?
I think she's trying to pull a fast one on Big Daddy.
Creo que le está intentando hacer una jugarreta a Big Daddy.
Here, I think this is us. Yeah.
Aquí, creo que somos nosotros. Sí.
Limited seating, my ass.
Asientos limitados, mis narices.
Let's just see who made the cut.
Veamos quién pasó el corte.
Hi. Hi. I'm Monica Geller.
Hola. Hola. Soy Monica Geller.
- How do you know the bride and groom? - I worked with Frannie.
- ¿Cómo conoces a los novios? - Trabajé con Frannie.
Used to work with her. Used to.
Solía trabajar con ella. Solía.
I'm a relative and I didn't get invited, okay?
Soy un pariente y no me invitaron, ¿vale?
A blood relative. Blood.
Un pariente de sangre. Sangre.
Stop saying "blood" to strangers.
Deja de decir "sangre" a desconocidos.
So how about you? How do you know the happy couple?
Entonces, ¿y tú? ¿Cómo conoces a la feliz pareja?
We went to college with both of them. And now we live next door.
Fuimos a la universidad con ambos. Y ahora vivimos al lado.
Okay, you're fine.
Vale, estás bien.
- Hey. Are you guys ready? - Hey. Yes.
- Oye. ¿Están listos? - Oye. Sí.
I will have a green salad, um, house dressing and water's fine.
Tomaré una ensalada verde, uh, aderezo de la casa y agua está bien.
- Okay. - And for you, sir?
- Vale. - ¿Y para usted, señor?
Yeah. This slow-roasted salmon...
Sí. Este salmón asado lentamente...
...just how slow are we talking?
...¿qué tan lento estamos hablando?
It's already been roasted.
Ya ha sido asado.
Oh, then no. Maybe I should hear those specials again.
Oh, entonces no. Quizás debería escuchar las especialidades de nuevo.
Oh, Joey, we've heard the specials three times, okay?
Oh, Joey, hemos escuchado las especialidades tres veces, ¿vale?
There's prime rib, mahi-mahi and a very special lobster ravioli.
Hay costilla de res, mahi-mahi y unos raviolis de langosta muy especiales.
- Actually, we're out of the lobster ravioli. - Oh, well, that changes everything.
- En realidad, ya no nos quedan los raviolis de langosta. - Oh, bueno, eso lo cambia todo.
- You know what, Pheebs? - Uh-huh.
- ¿Sabes qué, Pheebs? - Ajá.
You were right before. Friends are so important.
Tenías razón antes. Los amigos son muy importantes.
Yeah, I'm very wise. I know.
Sí, soy muy sabia. Lo sé.
You know what I really want?
¿Sabes qué quiero realmente?
- What? - Is to have a long, long talk.
- ¿Qué? - Es tener una larga, larga charla.
You know? Get Joey out on the open road and really open him up.
¿Sabes? Sacar a Joey a la carretera y realmente abrirlo.
- Any progress? - Yes.
- ¿Algún progreso? - Sí.
I will have the lobster ravioli.
Tomaré los raviolis de langosta.
God, Joey, this is taking forever.
Dios, Joey, esto está tardando una eternidad.
- What's the rush? - Well...
- ¿Cuál es la prisa? - Bueno...
...I just have, you know, an appointment.
...solo tengo, ya sabes, una cita.
And it's very important.
Y es muy importante.
What is it?
¿Qué es?
Well...
Bueno...
...it's a date.
...es una cita.
A date? No, no, Pheebs, you must be mistaken...
[ERROR API]
...because you wouldn't schedule a date...
...on the night you have plans with a friend.
[ERROR API]
Come on. Don't make me feel badly about this.
No, I'm gonna.
[ERROR API]
That's right. Yeah, you made me feel really guilty...
...about going out with that girl.
[ERROR API]
Like I did something terrible to you. Now, Pheebs, you're doing the same thing.
That's not the same thing. This is totally different.
[ERROR API]
This is with David. Remember David, the scientist guy?
Okay, he's very special to me.
[ERROR API]
Okay, well, my girl from the other night was special.
She was a scientist too.
[ERROR API]
- She was? - Well, she graduated high school.
Okay, whatever. Know what?
[ERROR API]
I don't have time to convince you.
He's only here for four hours and I'm gonna go see him.
[ERROR API]
- Fine. Fine! - Yeah. Yeah.
What are you still doing here? I told you, lobster ravioli.
[ERROR API]
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Oh, I was just about to leave. I didn't think you were coming.
[ERROR API]
Oh, I wouldn't have missed this. Ha, ha.
Well, I'm very glad you're here.
[ERROR API]
Oh, you're such a gentleman.
Come on, we're going to my place.
[ERROR API]
Are you eating the cheesecake without me?
Mm-mm.
I will give you $100 to whistle right now.
[ERROR API]
How can you eat the cheesecake without me?
What are you gonna do?
¿Qué vas a hacer?
Gonna run and tell Monica or Joey? No, you'd have to tell them what we did.
[ERROR API]
We are dessert stealers. We are living outside the law.
You know what? I don't trust you with this cake.
[ERROR API]
- And I got it first, and I'm taking it back. - What?
- What? Oh, no, you don't. - Oh, yes.
[ERROR API]
You think I trust you with it?
We're gonna split it. You take half, I take half.
[ERROR API]
That's not fair. You had some.
Oh, you know what? I think Monica would be very interested to know...
[ERROR API]
...that you called her cheesecake dry and mealy.
- What do we use to split it? - Okay.
[ERROR API]
- All right, pick a half. - Okay.
- Well, this side looks bigger. - Mm-hm.
[ERROR API]
Uh, but there's more crust on this side.
Yeah. So maybe if I measure it...
[ERROR API]
For God's sake, pick a piece.
- All right, I pick that one. - So the smaller piece.
[ERROR API]
Okay. There you go.
Enjoy your half, my friend. But that is it.
[ERROR API]
No sharing, no switching, and don't come crying to me...
...if you eat your piece too fast.
...si te comes tu pedazo demasiado rápido.
Oh!
¡Oh!
- You gonna give me some of your piece? - Oh, no.
- ¿Me vas a dar un poco de tu pedazo? - Oh, no.
No switching, no sharing. And don't come crying to me.
Nada de cambiar, nada de compartir. Y no vengas llorando.
Ha, ha. I may just sit here and have my cake all day.
Ja, ja. Me quedaré aquí sentada comiendo mi pastel todo el día.
Just sit here in the hallway and eat my...
Solo me sentaré aquí en el pasillo a comerme mi...
Never met a girl that could me feel...
Nunca conocí a una chica que pudiera hacerme sentir...
Ross, sweetheart.
Ross, cariño.
Oh, hey, Aunt Millie.
Oh, hola, tía Millie.
- Isn't it a beautiful wedding? - Yes. Yes, it is.
- ¿No es una boda preciosa? - Sí. Sí que lo es.
Every time, on the lips.
Cada vez, en los labios.
Why? Why on the lips?
¿Por qué? ¿Por qué en los labios?
There's Frannie. Won't she be happy to see me?
Ahí está Frannie. ¿No se alegrará de verme?
Now, wait a minute. You be nice, all right?
Ahora, espera un minuto. Pórtate bien, ¿de acuerdo?
I didn't bring you here so you could ambush her.
No te traje aquí para que la emboscaras.
Frannie was the one who found your Playboys and showed them to Mom.
Frannie fue la que encontró tus Playboys y se los enseñó a mamá.
That bitch.
Esa perra.
Monica. What...?
Monica. ¿Qué...?
Am I doing here? Surprised to see me?
¿Qué hago aquí? ¿Sorprendida de verme?
Ross brought me. How do you like that?
Me trajo Ross. ¿Qué te parece?
Hi, Frannie. Congratulations.
Hola, Frannie. Felicidades.
You invite my brother, you invite my whole family, and not me? Why?
¿Invitas a mi hermano, invitas a toda mi familia, y a mí no? ¿Por qué?
Why wouldn't you want me at your wedding?
¿Por qué no querrías que estuviera en tu boda?
What could I have possibly done?
¿Qué podría haber hecho yo?
Stuart.
I believe you know my husband.
Creo que conoce a mi esposo.
So it's really a question of "who" could you have possibly done.
Así que la pregunta es más bien "a quién" pudiste haberle hecho algo.
- I hate this, but I have to go. - Mm-hm.
- Odio esto, pero tengo que irme. - Mm-hm.
I can't miss my flight.
No puedo perder mi vuelo.
Are you sure? I bet there's another flight to Minsk in...
¿Estás segura? Apuesto a que hay otro vuelo a Minsk en...
July.
Julio.
That's really beautiful. What does it mean?
Eso es realmente hermoso. ¿Qué significa?
"Please clean my beakers."
"Por favor, limpie mis vasos de precipitados."
I don't get out of the lab much.
No salgo mucho del laboratorio.
I thought it meant something else.
Pensé que significaba otra cosa.
Yeah, well, I really actually wanted to say, um...
Sí, bueno, en realidad quería decir, um...
...that.
...eso.
But, um, I figured I probably shouldn't because...
Pero, um, pensé que probablemente no debería porque...
...you know, I have to leave.
...sabes, tengo que irme.
Hmm. No, you're right. Don't say it.
Hmm. No, tienes razón. No lo digas.
I do, though.
Sí que lo hago.
I do too.
Yo también.
Well, bye, Phoebe.
Bueno, adiós, Phoebe.
Okay, now's not the time, Joey, all right? You can yell at me tomorrow.
Está bien, ahora no es el momento, Joey, ¿de acuerdo? Puedes gritarme mañana.
No, no. No, Pheebs. I'm not gonna yell at you.
No, no. No, Pheebs. No te voy a gritar.
I just started thinking about you and David...
Solo empecé a pensar en ti y David...
...and I remember how bummed you were the first time he left.
...y recuerdo lo deprimida que estabas la primera vez que se fue.
Oh, Pheebs, come here.
Oh, Pheebs, ven aquí.
- Are you okay? - No, I'm not okay.
- ¿Estás bien? - No, no estoy bien.
The only guy I've ever been crazy about is going to Minsk...
El único chico que me ha vuelto loca se va a Minsk...
...and I may never see him again.
...y quizás no lo vuelva a ver.
Hey, you could always visit him.
Oye, siempre puedes ir a visitarlo.
Oh, right. Like they're gonna let me have a passport.
Ah, claro. Como si me fueran a dar un pasaporte.
Anything I can do? Whatever you need.
¿Hay algo que pueda hacer? Lo que necesites.
Well, now...
Bueno, ahora...
...if you achieve positronic distillation of subatomic particles before he does...
...si logras la destilación positrónica de partículas subatómicas antes que él...
...then he could come back.
...entonces él podría regresar.
I could give it a shot.
Podría intentarlo.
Oh, look. There's a piece that doesn't have floor on it.
Oh, mira. Hay una pieza que no tiene piso.
- Stick to your side. - Come on, now.
- Quédate de tu lado. - Vamos, vamos.
All right, what are we having?
Muy bien, ¿qué vamos a comer?
Oh, wait, I forgot my wrap.
Oh, espera, olvidé mi chal.
Oh, okay, wait here.
Oh, está bien, espera aquí.
Hi, sweetie. Are you leaving?
Hola, cariño. ¿Te vas?
- Well... - Give us a kiss. Come on.
- Bueno... - Dame un beso. Anda.
Why? Why on the lips?
¿Por qué? ¿Por qué en los labios?