- Oh, hey! How was your audition? - Hey.
- ¡Oh, hola! ¿Cómo te fue en la audición? - Hola.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
Perdona, ¿te conozco?
What are you doing?
¿Qué estás haciendo?
Practicing blowing you off. I'm gonna be a big movie star!
Practicando cómo ignorarte. ¡Voy a ser una gran estrella de cine!
Oh, you got it?
Oh, ¿te lo dieron?
- Not yet, but the audition went great! - What's it for?
- Todavía no, ¡pero la audición fue genial! - ¿Para qué?
A big-budget period movie about three Italian brothers...
Una película de época de gran presupuesto sobre tres hermanos italianos...
...who come to America at the turn of the century. It's classy.
...que vienen a América a principios de siglo. Es elegante.
The director's supposed to be the next-next Martin Scorsese.
Se supone que el director es el próximo, próximo Martin Scorsese.
The "next-next"?
¿El "próximo, próximo"?
A guy from Chicago's supposed to be the next Martin Scorsese.
Se supone que un tipo de Chicago es el próximo Martin Scorsese.
This guy's right after him.
Este tipo viene justo después de él.
Hello?
¿Hola?
Joey, it's Estelle. I just talked to the casting people. They loved you!
Joey, soy Estelle. Acabo de hablar con la gente de casting. ¡Les encantaste!
They loved me!
¡Les encanté!
They want to see you again tomorrow.
Quieren verte de nuevo mañana.
- Oh, my God. - Just one thing.
- Oh, Dios mío. - Solo una cosa.
Do you have a problem with full-frontal nudity?
¿Tienes algún problema con la desnudez frontal completa?
Are you kidding me? I never rent a movie without it!
¿Me estás bromeando? ¡Nunca alquilo una película sin eso!
Oh.
Uh, okay, let me call you back.
Uh, está bien, te devuelvo la llamada.
- What's the matter? - They want me naked in the movie.
- ¿Qué pasa? - Quieren que esté desnudo en la película.
- Wow. - I know.
- Vaya. - Lo sé.
- My grandmother's gonna see this. - Grandma's gonna have to get in line.
- Mi abuela va a ver esto. - La abuela tendrá que hacer fila.
The wedding's so close. Are you nervous?
La boda está muy cerca. ¿Estás nerviosa?
Yeah, but I also can't wait till it's over.
Sí, pero también estoy deseando que termine.
We have a pact not to have sex again until the wedding.
Tenemos un pacto de no volver a tener sexo hasta la boda.
A "no sex" pact, huh?
Un pacto de "nada de sexo", ¿eh?
I have one of those with every woman in America.
Tengo uno de esos con todas las mujeres de América.
Will you give me a hand making up the guest bedroom?
¿Me echas una mano para arreglar el dormitorio de invitados?
Cousin Cassie's staying with us for a few days.
La prima Cassie se quedará con nosotros unos días.
Cassie? I haven't seen her in, like, forever.
¿Cassie? No la he visto en, como, ¡mil años!
I wonder if she still carries a Barbie everywhere?
Me pregunto si todavía lleva una Barbie a todas partes.
- She's 25 years old. - So? I still...
- Tiene 25 años. - ¿Y qué? Yo todavía...
You're probably right.
Probablemente tengas razón.
- Hi. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Pheebs, can I talk to you over here for a second?
Pheebs, ¿puedo hablar contigo aquí un segundo?
Yeah.
Sí.
Subtle, guys.
Sutil, chicos.
What?
¿Qué?
I know you're planning my surprise bridal shower.
Sé que están planeando mi despedida de soltera sorpresa.
Ha, okay, well, don't ruin it. Just play along, at least.
Ja, está bien, bueno, no lo arruines. Solo sigue la corriente, al menos.
- Okay. Sorry. - Okay.
- Está bien. Lo siento. - Está bien.
Oh, my God. We have to throw her a shower?
Dios mío. ¿Tenemos que hacerle una fiesta?
What'd you decide to do about the movie?
¿Qué decidiste hacer sobre la película?
I don't know.
No sé.
It's not like it's porn. This is a serious, legitimate movie.
No es como si fuera porno. Es una película seria y legítima.
Nudity's really important to the story.
La desnudez es realmente importante para la historia.
That's what you say about porn.
Eso es lo que dices del porno.
Maybe I shouldn't go on the callback.
Quizás no debería ir a la segunda audición.
No, you should. A lot of major actors do nude scenes.
No, deberías. Muchos actores famosos hacen escenas de desnudos.
The chance to star in a movie? Come on!
¿La oportunidad de protagonizar una película? ¡Vamos!
That's true. And I'm only naked in one scene. It sounds really great.
Es verdad. Y solo estoy desnuda en una escena. Suena muy bien.
My character's Catholic. He falls in love with a Jewish girl.
Mi personaje es católico. Se enamora de una chica judía.
We run away and get caught in a big rainstorm.
Salimos corriendo y nos quedamos atrapados en una gran tormenta.
We go into a barn, undress each other and hold each other.
Entramos en un granero, nos desvestimos mutuamente y nos abrazamos.
It's really sweet and tender.
Es muy dulce y tierno.
Plus, everyone is gonna see your thing.
Además, todos van a ver tu cosa.
When can we have this shower?
¿Cuándo podemos tener esta ducha?
She has so much going on, we have only two options.
Ella tiene tantas cosas, solo tenemos dos opciones.
- We have Friday. - That's just two days away.
- Tenemos el viernes. - Eso es en solo dos días.
- What is the other option? - Yesterday.
- ¿Cuál es la otra opción? - Ayer.
Well, if we make it yesterday, woo-hoo, we're done.
Bueno, si lo hacemos ayer, ¡hurra, terminamos!
It's impossible. We can't do this by Friday.
Es imposible. No podemos hacer esto para el viernes.
We have to find a place, invite people, get food.
Tenemos que encontrar un lugar, invitar gente, conseguir comida.
There's too much to do.
Hay demasiado que hacer.
- We cannot do it! - Calm down!
- ¡No podemos hacerlo! - ¡Cálmate!
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right. I'm sorry.
Está bien. Lo siento, tienes razón. Lo siento.
Just calm down, woman!
¡Solo cálmate, mujer!
Phoebe, I already did.
Phoebe, yo ya lo hice.
- All right, then I need to calm down. - Okay.
- Está bien, entonces necesito calmarme. - De acuerdo.
I think we can do this if we just get organized.
Creo que podemos hacerlo si nos organizamos.
- Uh-huh. - We have two days to plan this party.
- Ajá. - Tenemos dos días para planear esta fiesta.
- We just need to make fast decisions. - Mm-hm.
- Solo necesitamos tomar decisiones rápidas. - Mm-hm.
Where will we have it?
¿Dónde la haremos?
- Um, here. What time? - Four o'clock. Food?
- Mmm, aquí. ¿A qué hora? - A las cuatro. ¿Comida?
- Finger sandwiches and tea. - Ooh, great. Very Monica.
- Sándwiches pequeños y té. - Ooh, genial. Muy Monica.
- And chili. - Ah, you went one too far.
- Y chili. - Ah, te pasaste un poco.
- Uh, flowers or balloons? - Both.
- Mmm, ¿flores o globos? - Ambos.
- We're paying for this. Okay. - Neither.
- Pagamos por esto. De acuerdo. - Ninguno.
- Um, what should we do for the theme? - "Lusts of the Flesh."
- Mmm, ¿qué deberíamos hacer para el tema? - "Lujurias de la Carne".
- What? - I don't know. Cowboy theme?
- ¿Qué? - No sé. ¿Tema de vaqueros?
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
I'm glad we decided not to sleep together before the wedding.
Me alegro de que decidimos no dormir juntos antes de la boda.
Oh, boy. Me too.
Oh, vaya. Yo también.
You know, I was thinking, if we had a big fight...
Sabes, estaba pensando, si tuviéramos una gran pelea...
- Mm-hm. ...and, uh, we broke up for a few hours.
- Mm-hm. ...y, eh, rompiéramos por unas horas.
- Yeah. - Technically, we could have sex again.
- Sí. - Técnicamente, podríamos tener sexo de nuevo.
What do you think, bossy and domineering?
¿Qué piensas, mandona y dominante?
The wedding's off, sloppy and immature.
La boda se cancela, descuidada e inmadura.
- That's me. Come on. - Okay.
- Esa soy yo. Vamos. - De acuerdo.
Wait. Cassie's in the guest room. We're going to lunch.
Espera. Cassie está en la habitación de invitados. Vamos a almorzar.
Get rid of her, obsessive and shrill!
¡Deshazte de ella, obsesiva y chillona!
Shrill? The wedding is back on.
¿Chillona? La boda está de vuelta.
I thought I heard voices. You must be Chandler.
Creí oír voces. Debes ser Chandler.
- Hi. Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you too.
- Hola. Encantado de conocerte. - Encantado de conocerte también.
- So, ready to go? - Yeah.
- Entonces, ¿listos para ir? - Sí.
- Chandler? - I'll be right with you.
- ¿Chandler? - Ahora voy.
- Cassie needs to stay at your place. - Why?
- Cassie necesita quedarse en tu casa. - ¿Por qué?
Because "Pervie Perverson" here can't stop staring at her.
Porque "Pervertido Pervertón" aquí no deja de mirarla.
Chandler, she's our cousin!
[ERROR API]
I wasn't staring. I was listening intently.
It's called being a good conversationalist. Watch.
[ERROR API]
Say something.
You were staring about eight inches south of there.
[ERROR API]
Fine. She can stay at my place.
What does Cassie look like now?
[ERROR API]
- She looks exactly like Aunt Marilyn. - Huh.
So this Aunt Marilyn, is she coming to the wedding?
[ERROR API]
Wafer-thin ice.
Hey, I'm back.
[ERROR API]
Hi, Joey.
Hola, Joey.
Uh, so, will I be reading the same scene again?
[ERROR API]
I tried to call you. You didn't need to come today.
Oh, great.
Oh, genial.
I'd have been perfect for this part.
[ERROR API]
You made a bad decision and ruined your movie. Good day!
You didn't need to come, because the director saw your tape and loved it.
[ERROR API]
And scene.
Huh? Wasn't that fun?
[ERROR API]
We did a little improv there. Yeah!
So, you... You were saying?
[ERROR API]
The director wants to meet you tomorrow.
Wow. Sure. That's great.
[ERROR API]
Your agent said you're okay with nudity.
Yeah, sure. As long as it's handled tastefully.
[ERROR API]
And that barn is not too cold.
Terrific. Well, uh, there's one more thing.
[ERROR API]
Uh... Uh, it's important to the director that everything in the movie is authentic.
In your love scene with Sarah...
[ERROR API]
...she talks about how she's never seen a naked man who wasn't Jewish.
So...
Así que...
So, what?
[ERROR API]
So, uh, well, the director is insisting that whoever play that part...
...be authentically, uh, anatomically...
[ERROR API]
...not Jewish. You know what I'm saying?
Yes!
¡Sí!
No. What?
[ERROR API]
An Italian Catholic immigrant at this time would not be...
Bar mitzvah-ed?
[ERROR API]
- To get this part, you can't be... - No.
- But you are? - Yep.
[ERROR API]
- You told them you weren't? - That's right.
Wow. Wow.
[ERROR API]
It's definitely all gone? There's nothing there to work with?
- What were you thinking? - I don't know. I just want this part.
[ERROR API]
They say no matter what you're asked during an audition, say yes.
They want you to ride a horse, say you can.
[ERROR API]
You figure out how to do it later.
This is not like learning to ride a horse. This is like learning to...
[ERROR API]
...grow a turtleneck.
...ponerme un cuello alto.
I know, okay? Tomorrow, when I go meet the director...
Ya sé, ¿vale? Mañana, cuando vaya a ver al director...
...I have to take my clothes off so they can see what my body looks like.
...tengo que quitarme la ropa para que vean cómo es mi cuerpo.
Oh, my God. What are you gonna do?
Dios mío. ¿Qué vas a hacer?
I have to call my agent and tell her I can't do the part.
Tengo que llamar a mi agente y decirle que no puedo hacer el papel.
Unless...
A menos que...
Unless what?
¿A menos que qué?
This may sound crazy, but there may be something we could...
Esto puede sonar una locura, pero quizás haya algo que podríamos...
...fashion.
...moda.
- Like what? - Well, I'm not sure yet, but, um...
- ¿Cómo qué? - Bueno, no estoy segura todavía, pero, eh...
...off the top of my head, I'm thinking...
...así de repente, estoy pensando...
...double-sided tape and some sort of luncheon meat.
...cinta de doble cara y algún tipo de embutido.
I've got a great idea for party favors for the shower.
Tengo una gran idea para los regalitos de la fiesta.
We get mahogany boxes and carve everyone's names in them.
Compramos cajas de caoba y tallamos los nombres de todos.
Then inside is each person's individual birthstone.
Luego, dentro, está la piedra de nacimiento de cada persona.
Okay. Okay.
- All right, you take care of that. - Okay.
- Muy bien, tú encárgate de eso. - Vale.
Meanwhile, the party's tomorrow and we don't have a guest list.
Mientras tanto, la fiesta es mañana y no tenemos lista de invitados.
Okay. Who do we know that's coming? Me. Are you?
Vale. ¿A quién conocemos que vaya a venir? Yo. ¿Tú?
- Hey. - Hey, what's up?
- Hola. - Hola, ¿qué pasa?
I'm making something for Joey. Can I raid your fridge?
Estoy haciendo algo para Joey. ¿Puedo saquear tu nevera?
Have at it.
Adelante.
All right. Turkey? Mm, that won't work.
Vale. ¿Pavo? Mm, eso no servirá.
Cheese? That won't work.
¿Queso? Eso no servirá.
Olive loaf? I hope that won't work.
¿Salchichón en rodajas? Espero que eso no sirva.
Are you making him a sandwich?
¿Le estás haciendo un sándwich?
No, it's, um, more like a wrap.
No, es, eh, más bien un wrap.
Okay, so, um, I'm gonna go, guys.
Vale, entonces, eh, me voy, chicos.
So you can get back to deciding on what to get me for a present!
¡Así podéis volver a decidir qué regalarme!
We have to get her a present?
¿Tenemos que comprarle un regalo?
Okay, but look. Look at what I got.
Vale, pero mirad. Mirad lo que conseguí.
It's her address book. We have a guest list.
Es su agenda. Tenemos una lista de invitados.
Ah.
You're amazing. Did you pull that out of her purse?
Eres increíble. ¿Lo sacaste de su bolso?
Uh-huh. And a little seed money for the party.
Ajá. Y un poco de dinero inicial para la fiesta.
Oh, nice.
Oh, qué bien.
Cassie?
¿Cassie?
- Hey, Ross. - Hi. Ha, ha.
- Hola, Ross. - Hola. Ja, ja.
It's been so long!
¡Ha pasado tanto tiempo!
Last time I saw you...
La última vez que te vi...
...you were setting up your tent in line for Return of the Jedi.
...estabas montando tu tienda de campaña en la cola para 'El Retorno del Jedi'.
Oh, uh, that's right.
Oh, eh, es verdad.
So you did see me that day. Because it seemed like you didn't.
Así que sí me viste ese día. Porque parecía que no.
- Yeah, sorry about that. - It's okay. Come on in.
- Sí, lo siento por eso. - No pasa nada. Pasa.
Thanks for letting me stay here. Monica's place was nice.
Gracias por dejarme quedarme aquí. El sitio de Monica estaba bien.
But her fiancé sure stares a lot.
Pero su prometido mira mucho.
Oh.
Oh, my God! You do a great Chandler!
¡Dios mío! ¡Haces un Chandler genial!
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
Yeah, I have a knack for impressions.
Sí, tengo facilidad para las imitaciones.
Well, maybe after we get re-acquainted, uh, you could do me.
Bueno, quizás después de que nos pongamos al día, eh, podrías hacerme un favor.
Yeah. No!
Sí. ¡No!
Cassie, how you...? How you doing on that...
Cassie, ¿cómo...? ¿Cómo vas con eso...
...hot dog?
...¿perrito caliente?
- I'm all done. - Thank God.
- Ya terminé. - Gracias a Dios.
The last time we hung out was when our parents rented that beach house.
La última vez que salimos fue cuando nuestros padres alquilaron esa casa en la playa.
Oh, right, right. Ooh, remember the time...
Oh, claro, claro. Ooh, ¿te acuerdas de la vez...
...l, uh, pinned you down and tickled you until you cried?
...¿que te inmovilicé y te hice cosquillas hasta que lloraste?
We're probably too old to do that now.
Probablemente ya seamos demasiado viejos para eso.
I'll always remember that summer. It's when I got all these freckles.
Siempre recordaré ese verano. Fue cuando me salieron todas estas pecas.
Uh-huh, Uh-huh.
Ajá, ajá.
And... And I'll always remember that summer...
Y... Y yo siempre recordaré ese verano...
...because that's when I realized that we are related.
...porque fue cuando me di cuenta de que somos parientes.
It took you that long to figure it out, huh?
¿Te tomó tanto tiempo darte cuenta, eh?
Um, I'm a little slow.
Um, soy un poco lenta.
Just as our children would be.
Igual que lo serían nuestros hijos.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
How are you? Good. Hi. Thanks for coming.
¿Cómo estás? Bien. Hola. Gracias por venir.
- Oh, thank you. - Thank you. So nice to see you.
- Oh, gracias. - Gracias. Qué gusto verte.
- No, thanks. - Okay. Hey, Rach?
- No, gracias. - Vale. Oye, ¿Rach?
- Yeah? - Who the hell are all these people?
- ¿Sí? - ¿Quién demonios es toda esta gente?
I don't know. I called everybody in her book.
No sé. Llamé a todo el mundo de su agenda.
These are the ones that could show up on 24 hours' notice.
Estos son los que pudieron venir con 24 horas de aviso.
There's a word for people like that: Losers.
Hay una palabra para gente así: Perdedores.
Hi, I'm Rachel. This is Phoebe. I'm the maid of honor.
Hola, soy Rachel. Esta es Phoebe. Soy la dama de honor.
How do you know Monica?
¿Cómo conoces a Monica?
- I was her accountant four years ago. - Oh...
- Fui su contadora hace cuatro años. - Oh...
I'm interested to find out who's been doing her taxes the last four years.
Me interesa saber quién ha estado haciendo sus impuestos los últimos cuatro años.
That's great.
Eso es genial.
- When is Monica supposed to get here? - I don't know.
- ¿Cuándo se supone que llega Monica? - No sé.
Excuse us.
Disculpen.
- You didn't tell her? - You were supposed to.
- ¿No le dijiste? - Se suponía que tú lo hacías.
You were supposed to tell her to come! I was bringing the cake!
¡Se suponía que tú le decías que viniera! ¡Yo traía el pastel!
- Fine, I'll go call her. - And please tell her to bring a cake!
- Bien, iré a llamarla. - ¡Y por favor dile que traiga un pastel!
We have a lot of options. A number of prototypes for you to try on.
Tenemos muchas opciones. Varios prototipos para que te pruebes.
Wow, those look great.
Vaya, se ven geniales.
Okay, this one's a mushroom cap. Uh, this one is made of bologna.
Vale, este es un sombrero de hongo. Eh, este está hecho de mortadela.
- And... And the toothpicks? - Just until the glue dries.
- ¿Y... Y los palillos? - Solo hasta que se seque el pegamento.
Thank God.
Gracias a Dios.
These are more realistic, but perishable.
Estos son más realistas, pero perecederos.
Over here, we have pink suede, which is nice.
Por aquí, tenemos gamuza rosa, que es bonita.
But if it gets wet, it'll shrink.
Pero si se moja, se encogerá.
Maybe we'll just take that one away.
Quizás deberíamos llevarnos ese.
I also did a little something in fur, but, uh, that's really just for me.
También hice algo en piel, pero, eh, eso es más para mí.
Why don't you try these on? We'll get a better idea of what works.
¿Por qué no te pruebas estos? Tendremos una mejor idea de lo que funciona.
Thanks, you are such a good friend. And this is so weird.
Gracias, eres una gran amiga. Y esto es muy raro.
Ow.
Ay.
- Toothpick? - Yeah.
- ¿Palillo? - Sí.
- What are you trying now? - The Fruit Roll-up.
- ¿Qué te pruebas ahora? - El Fruit Roll-up.
- And? - Delicious.
- ¿Y? - Delicioso.
Joey.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. We have a winner!
Espera un minuto. Espera un minuto. ¡Tenemos un ganador!
What? Which one?
¿Qué? ¿Cuál?
The Silly Putty. Not so silly anymore!
El Silly Putty. ¡Ya no es tan tonto!
She's your cousin. She's your cousin.
Ella es tu prima. Ella es tu prima.
If she knew what was going on in your head, she'd think you were sick.
Si supiera lo que pasa por tu cabeza, pensaría que estás enfermo.
Or would she? Let's back up for a second.
¿O no? Retrocedamos un segundo.
She was the one who suggested opening a bottle of wine.
Ella fue la que sugirió abrir una botella de vino.
She was the one who turned down the lights.
Ella fue la que bajó las luces.
She was the one that wanted to rent Logan's Run...
Ella fue la que quiso alquilar "Logan's Run"...
...the sexiest movie ever.
...la película más sexy de la historia.
I know that look.
Conozco esa mirada.
Forget it. I want it. She wants it.
Olvídalo. Lo quiero. Ella lo quiere.
I'm going in.
Voy a entrar.
What the hell are you doing?
¿Qué demonios estás haciendo?
Say something clever.
Di algo ingenioso.
Okay, doesn't have to be clever.
Está bien, no tiene que ser ingenioso.
Just has to be words. Say some words.
Solo tienen que ser palabras. Di algunas palabras.
Any words will do.
Cualquier palabra sirve.
Oh, my God, this is the longest...
¡Dios mío, este es el más largo...
...that anyone has not talked ever!
...que alguien no ha hablado jamás!
There is nothing you could say to make this worse...
No hay nada que puedas decir para empeorar esto...
...so just say something!
...¡así que solo di algo!
I haven't had sex in a very long time.
Hace mucho tiempo que no tengo sexo.
Yeah, you really shouldn't have said anything.
Sí, realmente no debiste haber dicho nada.
Phoebe? Rachel? It's Monica.
¿Phoebe? ¿Rachel? Soy Monica.
I wonder what you could possibly need me for on such short notice?
Me pregunto para qué podrías necesitarme con tan poca antelación.
Oh.
- Oh, Monica. We are so sorry. - For what?
- Oh, Monica. Lo sentimos mucho. - ¿Por qué?
First, for forgetting to throw you a bridal shower.
Primero, por olvidar tirarte una fiesta de despedida de soltera.
Then, forgetting to invite you to it.
Luego, por olvidar invitarte a ella.
You already had it?
¿Ya la tuviste?
We called everyone in your phone book. A bunch of people came.
Llamamos a todos en tu agenda. Vinieron un montón de gente.
It took us so long to get you here that they had to leave.
Nos tomó tanto tiempo traerte aquí que tuvieron que irse.
We wanted to throw you a big surprise and a great shower.
Queríamos darte una gran sorpresa y una gran fiesta.
Now you don't have either.
Ahora no tienes ninguna.
- We ruined everything. - Ugh.
- Arruinamos todo. - Ugh.
No, wait a minute, that's not true. What you did was really sweet.
No, espera un minuto, eso no es verdad. Lo que hiciste fue muy dulce.
- It kind of works out for the best, heh. - What do you mean?
- De alguna manera funciona para lo mejor, je. - ¿Qué quieres decir?
Now I get to spend my shower with the only people I really love.
Ahora puedo pasar mi fiesta con las únicas personas que realmente amo.
I get all those presents without talking to people I don't even like!
¡Recibo todos esos regalos sin hablar con gente que ni siquiera me gusta!
- Surprise. - Surprise, Monica.
- Sorpresa. - Sorpresa, Monica.
What's cool is, the character is from Naples, right?
Lo genial es que el personaje es de Nápoles, ¿verdad?
- Yeah. - My whole family's from Naples.
- Sí. - Toda mi familia es de Nápoles.
That's great. Okay. I've heard everything I need to hear...
Eso es genial. Está bien. He oído todo lo que necesito oír...
We just need to, uh...
Solo necesitamos, eh...
Leslie?
¿Leslie?
- Uh, Joey, this is the awkward part. - Oh, hey, right. Not a problem.
- Eh, Joey, esta es la parte incómoda. - Oh, hola, claro. No hay problema.
I totally understand you need to...
Entiendo perfectamente que necesites...
...make sure I don't have any horrible scars or tattoos.
...asegurarte de que no tenga ninguna cicatriz o tatuaje horrible.
Don't you worry.
No te preocupes.
I have nothing to hide.
No tengo nada que ocultar.
So, there you go. That's me.
Así que, ahí lo tienes. Ese soy yo.
One hundred-percent natural.
Cien por cien natural.
I tell you, that has never happened before.
Te digo que eso nunca había pasado antes.
Cassie, are you finding everything okay?
Cassie, ¿estás encontrando todo bien?
Yeah. Thank you so much for letting me stay here.
Sí. Muchas gracias por dejarme quedarme aquí.
Oh, it's no problem. I've...
Oh, no es problema. Yo...
What?
¿Qué?
Say something. Say anything.
Di algo. Di cualquier cosa.
Ask her out! She's not your cousin!
¡Invítala a salir! ¡No es tu prima!