- She totally winked at me! - She did not wink at you.
- ¡Me guiñó el ojo! - No te guiñó el ojo.
You always think somebody's winking at you.
Siempre crees que alguien te guiña el ojo.
Huh.
Vaya.
I say "Tupelo Honey" by Van Morrison.
Yo digo "Tupelo Honey" de Van Morrison.
No way!
¡De ninguna manera!
The most romantic song ever was "The Way We Were. "
La canción más romántica de la historia fue "The Way We Were".
Ah, I think the one that Elton John wrote for, um, that guy on Who's the Boss?
Ah, creo que la que Elton John escribió para, eh, ¿ese tipo de "Who's the Boss"?
- What song was that? - Um.
- ¿Qué canción era? - Eh.
Hold me close, young Tony Danza
Abrázame fuerte, joven Tony Danza
Hi, Monica. Hi, Mon.
Hola, Monica. Hola, Mon.
Hey, Mon.
Oye, Mon.
Oh, my God!
¡Oh, Dios mío!
- Has she slept at all? Nope.
- ¿Ha dormido algo? No.
It's been three nights in a row.
Han sido tres noches seguidas.
She finally stopped crying yesterday.
Finalmente dejó de llorar ayer.
But then she found one of Richard's cigar butts on the terrace...
Pero entonces encontró una colilla de cigarro de Richard en la terraza...
Oh. Okay, that explains it. I got a call at 2 in the morning...
Oh. Vale, eso lo explica. Recibí una llamada a las 2 de la mañana...
...and all I could hear was this squeaky sound.
...y lo único que oía era un chirrido.
So I thought, "Oh, it's a mouse or a possum. "
Así que pensé: "Oh, es un ratón o un zarigüeya".
Then I realized, like, okay...
Entonces me di cuenta, como, vale...
...where would a mouse or a possum get the money to make the phone call?
...¿dónde conseguiría un ratón o una zarigüeya el dinero para hacer la llamada?
Morning. - Morning. Hey.
Buenos días. - Buenos días. Hola.
You made pancakes?
¿Hiciste panqueques?
Yeah, like there's any way I could ever do that.
Sí, como si yo pudiera hacer eso.
Monica and Rachel had syrup
Monica y Rachel tenían sirope
Uh, uh Now I can get my man to cheer up
Uh, uh Ahora puedo hacer que mi hombre se anime
Good morning, Joey.
Buenos días, Joey.
Good morning.
Buenos días.
Here's a thought.
Aquí tienes una idea.
Why don't you stay home from work and just hang out with me?
¿Por qué no te quedas en casa y pasas el rato conmigo?
Oh, I wish.
Oh, ojalá.
You have that report to finish, and I've got to see my lawyer.
Tienes que terminar ese informe, y yo tengo que ver a mi abogado.
I can't believe I date a girl who's getting divorced.
No puedo creer que salga con una chica que se está divorciando.
- I'm such a grownup. - Ha-ha-ha.
- Soy tan adulta. - Ja-ja-ja.
I gotta go, I gotta go.
Tengo que irme, tengo que irme.
Not without a kiss.
No sin un beso.
Maybe I won't kiss you so you'll stay.
Quizás no te bese para que te quedes.
Kiss her. Kiss her!
¡Bésala! ¡Bésala!
I'll see you later, sweetie. Bye, Joey.
Te veo luego, cariño. Adiós, Joey.
Bye-bye, Janice.
Adiós, Janice.
So when are you dumping her?
Entonces, ¿cuándo la vas a dejar?
Nope.
No.
Not this time.
No esta vez.
Heh. Come on, quit yanking me.
Je. Vamos, deja de tomarme el pelo.
I'm not yanking you.
No te estoy tomando el pelo.
- This is Janice. - Yeah, I know.
- Esta es Janice. - Sí, lo sé.
She makes me happy.
Me hace feliz.
Okay. All right.
Está bien. De acuerdo.
You look me in the eye and tell me, without blinking...
Mírame a los ojos y dime, sin parpadear...
...that you're not breaking up with her. No blinking.
...que no vas a romper con ella. Sin parpadear.
I'm not breaking up with her!
¡No voy a romper con ella!
Ah!
¡Ah!
What's that?
¿Qué es eso?
God, look what I found in the drain!
¡Dios, mira lo que encontré en el desagüe!
What?
¿Qué?
It's some of Richard's hair!
¡Es pelo de Richard!
What do I do with this?
¿Qué hago con esto?
Getting it away from me would be job one.
Quitarlo de mi vista sería lo primero.
It's weird, but I don't want to throw this away.
Es raro, pero no quiero tirar esto.
This is all I have left of him.
Esto es todo lo que me queda de él.
Gross...
Qué asco...
...drain hair.
...pelo del desagüe.
Ew!
¡Ew!
Cool! Oh, it looks like a tiny little person drowning in your cereal.
¡Genial! Oh, parece una personita ahogándose en tu cereal.
- God, what is wrong with me? - You need to get some sleep.
- Dios, ¿qué me pasa? - Necesitas dormir un poco.
I need to get some Richard.
Necesito un poco de Richard.
You broke up with him for a reason.
Terminaste con él por algo.
I know. I know. I'm just so tired of missing him.
Lo sé. Lo sé. Solo estoy cansada de extrañarlo.
Tired of wondering why he hasn't called. Why hasn't he?
Cansada de preguntarme por qué no ha llamado. ¿Por qué no lo ha hecho?
Maybe because you told him not to?
¿Quizás porque le dijiste que no lo hiciera?
What are you, the Memory Woman?
¿Qué eres, la Mujer de la Memoria?
They're not breaking up! Chandler and Janice?
¡No van a romper! ¿Chandler y Janice?
They're not breaking up! He didn't blink!
¡No van a romper! ¡No parpadeó!
I'm not surprised. Have you seen them together?
No me sorprende. ¿Los has visto juntos?
They're really cute.
Son muy lindos.
"Cute"? This is Janice!
¿"Lindos"? ¡Es Janice!
You remember Janice?
¿Recuerdas a Janice?
Yes, I remember. She's annoying. But you know what?
Sí, recuerdo. Es molesta. ¿Pero sabes qué?
She's his girlfriend now. I mean, what can we do?
Ahora es su novia. O sea, ¿qué podemos hacer?
There you go! That's the spirit I'm looking for! "What can we do?"
¡Ahí está! ¡Ese es el espíritu que busco! ¿"Qué podemos hacer?"
Huh?
¿Eh?
All right, who's first, huh? Ross?
Muy bien, ¿quién es el primero, eh? ¿Ross?
Chandler's our friend, and Janice makes him happy.
Chandler es nuestro amigo, y Janice lo hace feliz.
So I say we be adult about it and accept her.
Así que digo que seamos adultos al respecto y la aceptemos.
We'll call that Plan B.
Llamaremos a eso Plan B.
Honey...
Cariño...
...I was wondering... - Mm.
...me preguntaba... - Mm.
...do you still have that, um, Navy uniform?
...¿todavía tienes ese, eh, uniforme de la Marina?
No, I had to return it to the costume place.
No, tuve que devolverlo a la tienda de disfraces.
Oh.
I think I have an old band uniform from high school.
Creo que tengo un uniforme viejo de banda de la secundaria.
You remember not having sex in high school, right?
Recuerdas no haber tenido sexo en la secundaria, ¿verdad?
Yeah.
Sí.
Well, honey, what about you?
Bueno, cariño, ¿y tú?
- What? - I mean...
- ¿Qué? - O sea...
Do you have any fun, you know, fantasy-type things?
¿Tienes alguna fantasía divertida, ya sabes, de ese tipo?
No.
Come on. You gotta have one.
Vamos. Tienes que tener una.
Nope.
No.
- Ross, you know what? - What?
- Ross, ¿sabes qué? - ¿Qué?
If you tell me, I might do it.
[ERROR API]
Okay.
- Ahem. - Um.
[ERROR API]
Did you ever see, um, Return of the Jedi?
Yeah.
Sí.
Do you remember the scene...
[ERROR API]
...with, um, Jabba the Hutt?
Jabba had as his prisoner...
[ERROR API]
...Princess Leia.
Oh.
Princess Leia was wearing...
[ERROR API]
...this, um, gold bikini thing.
It was pretty cool.
[ERROR API]
Yeah, Princess Leia and the gold bikini? Oh, every guy our age loved that.
- Really? - Mm-hm. Mm.
[ERROR API]
It's huge! That's the moment when she stopped being a princess...
...and she became, like, you know, a woman.
[ERROR API]
Did you ever do the Leia thing?
Oh, yeah. Mm-hm.
[ERROR API]
Really? That great, huh?
No, it's just that I got this new pager, and I have it on "vibrate. "
[ERROR API]
See you.
Nos vemos.
Hey.
Oye.
Hi, you guys!
[ERROR API]
Look who I found standing outside the Szechuan Dragon...
...staring at a parking meter.
[ERROR API]
- Ahem. Mon. Hi. - Hi.
- Why aren't you at work? - Oh, they sent me home.
[ERROR API]
Why?
¿Por qué?
Because I don't work at the Szechuan Dragon.
[ERROR API]
You really need to get some sleep.
I know I do.
Yo lo hago.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
Guess what? They published my paper.
[ERROR API]
- Oh! Really? Let me see, let me see. - Uh-huh.
Rach, look!
[ERROR API]
No. - Ooh.
Hi. Ha, ha.
[ERROR API]
Ha, ha! Oh.
Where is my strong Ross Skywalker to come rescue me?
[ERROR API]
There he is!
- Hey. - Wheel!
[ERROR API]
- Of! - Fortune!
This guy's so stupid.
[ERROR API]
It's Count Rushmore!
You should really go on this show.
[ERROR API]
I got three tickets to the Rangers tonight. What do you say?
I say I am there!
[ERROR API]
Cool! Oh.
Is Ross going too?
[ERROR API]
No. Janice.
Janice?
¿Janice?
Because I just feel bad for Ross, you know?
Porque me da pena Ross, ¿sabes?
We always go together. We're like The Three Hockey-teers, you know?
Siempre vamos juntos. Somos como Los Tres Mosqueteros, ¿sabes?
I may be way out on a limb here, but do you have a problem with Janice?
Quizás estoy arriesgando mucho, pero ¿tienes un problema con Janice?
No!
¡No!
Yes...
Sí...
Oh, God, how do I say this? Uh...
Oh, Dios, ¿cómo digo esto? Uh...
Oh! Ah!
¡Oh! ¡Ah!
You know that girl from the restaurant with the hair?
¿Conoces a esa chica del restaurante con el pelo?
Ooh! That girl that I hate? Ugh! She drives me crazy. Ew.
¡Ooh! ¿Esa chica que odio? Ugh. Me saca de quicio. Ew.
Oh.
Look, I don't hate Janice. She's just a lot to take, you know?
Mira, no odio a Janice. Es solo que es mucho, ¿sabes?
- Well, there you go. - Oh.
- Bueno, ahí lo tienes. - Oh.
Don't look at me like that.
No me mires así.
She drove you nuts before too, remember?
Ella también te sacó de quicio antes, ¿recuerdas?
I'm crazy about her now. This could be the real thing.
Ahora estoy loco por ella. Esto podría ser lo de verdad.
Capital R, capital T!
¡Con R mayúscula, T mayúscula!
Don't worry, those are the right letters.
No te preocupes, esas son las letras correctas.
Look, what do you want me to say?
Mira, ¿qué quieres que diga?
I want you to say that you like her!
¡Quiero que digas que te gusta!
I can't. It's like this chemical thing, you know?
No puedo. Es como algo químico, ¿sabes?
Every time she starts laughing, I just wanna...
Cada vez que empieza a reír, solo quiero...
...pull my arm off so I have something to throw at her.
...arrancarme el brazo para tener algo que tirarle.
Thanks for trying.
Gracias por intentarlo.
Oh, and by the way, there is no Count Rushmore!
Ah, y por cierto, ¡no existe el Conde Rushmore!
Then who's the guy that painted the faces on the mountain?
Entonces, ¿quién es el tipo que pintó las caras en la montaña?
- Ugh. - How could you tell her?
- Ugh. - ¿Cómo pudiste decírselo?
I didn't think it would be that big a deal!
¡No pensé que sería tan importante!
Oh. She didn't think it would be a big deal!
¡Oh! ¡Ella no pensó que sería importante!
Who are you talking to when you do that?
¿Con quién hablas cuando haces eso?
Look, that was supposed to be a private, personal thing between us.
Mira, eso se suponía que era algo privado, personal entre nosotros.
Phoebe is my girlfriend, okay? We tell each other everything.
Phoebe es mi novia, ¿vale? Nos contamos todo.
Guys do the same thing.
Los chicos hacen lo mismo.
I mean, what about all that locker-room stuff?
Quiero decir, ¿qué pasa con todas esas cosas de vestuario?
That's different. That's like, uh, who dated a stripper?
Eso es diferente. Eso es como, eh, quién salió con una stripper.
Or who did it on the back of the Staten Island ferry?
¿O quién lo hizo en la parte trasera del ferry de Staten Island?
- Both of those Joey? - Yeah.
- ¿Ambos, Joey? - Sí.
But you don't talk about your girlfriend...
Pero tú no hablas de tu novia...
...and the intimate stuff you do with her.
...y de las cosas íntimas que haces con ella.
- Not even with your best friend? - No.
- ¿Ni siquiera con tu mejor amigo? - No.
That is so sad.
Eso es muy triste.
You're missing out on so much.
Te estás perdiendo mucho.
I mean, the bonding and the sharing...
Quiero decir, la conexión y el compartir...
...and knowing they're going through the same thing you are.
...y saber que están pasando por lo mismo que tú.
Oh. So, what, you tell each other everything?
Oh. Entonces, ¿qué, se lo cuentan todo?
Pretty much.
Prácticamente.
Did you talk about the Night of Five Times?
¿Hablaste de la Noche de las Cinco Veces?
Do you tell people about the Night of Five Times?
¿Le cuentas a la gente sobre la Noche de las Cinco Veces?
Uh, honey, that was with Carol.
Uh, cariño, eso fue con Carol.
I know, but it's still worth mentioning, I think.
Lo sé, pero creo que aún así vale la pena mencionarlo.
Relax every muscle in your body.
Relaja cada músculo de tu cuerpo.
Listen to the plinky-plunky music.
Escucha la música esa tan pegadiza.
Okay, now close your eyes...
Okay, ahora cierra los ojos...
...and think of a happy place.
...y piensa en un lugar feliz.
Tell me your happy place.
Dime tu lugar feliz.
Richard's living room, drinking wine.
La sala de Richard, tomando vino.
No, no, no. Not a Richard thing. Just put down the glass and get out.
No, no, no. Nada de Richard. Solo deja el vaso y vete.
I'm sorry, but that's my happy place.
Lo siento, pero ese es mi lugar feliz.
Okay, fine. Use my happy place. Just don't move anything in there.
Okay, está bien. Usa mi lugar feliz. Solo no muevas nada ahí.
I'll try not to.
Intentaré no hacerlo.
Okay. All right, so, you're in a meadow...
Okay. Muy bien, entonces, estás en un prado...
...millions of stars in the sky...
...millones de estrellas en el cielo...
You think breaking up was a mistake?
¿Crees que terminar la relación fue un error?
There are no questions in the happy place.
No hay preguntas en el lugar feliz.
Just the warm breeze and the moonlight flowing through the trees.
Solo la brisa cálida y la luz de la luna fluyendo entre los árboles.
I'll bet he's over me. I'll bet he's fine.
Apuesto a que ya me superó. Apuesto a que está bien.
Betting and wagering of any kind are not permitted in the happy place.
Las apuestas y cualquier tipo de juego no están permitidos en el lugar feliz.
Okay?
¿Okay?
There's just, you know, the lovely waterfalls...
Solo están, ya sabes, las hermosas cascadas...
...and the trickling fountains...
...y las fuentes que gotean...
...and the calming sounds of the babbling brook.
...y los sonidos relajantes del arroyo.
- Okay, this isn't working. - Oh.
- Okay, esto no está funcionando. - Oh.
I'm still awake, and now I have to pee.
Todavía estoy despierta y ahora necesito ir al baño.
Oh.
So I hear...
Así que escucho...
...you hate me!
...¡me odias!
I, uh, never said hate. I was very careful about that.
Yo, eh, nunca dije odiar. Fui muy cuidadosa con eso.
A little birdie told me you wanting to rip your arm off and throw it at me.
Un pajarito me dijo que querías arrancarte un brazo y tirármelo.
And you got "hate" from that? You're taking a big leap there, I, uh...
¿Y de eso sacaste "odiar"? Estás dando un gran salto ahí, yo, eh...
All right, fine, fine, fine!
¡Muy bien, bien, bien!
We have got to do something about our little situation here.
Tenemos que hacer algo con nuestra pequeña situación aquí.
So this is my idea.
Así que esta es mi idea.
You and me spending some quality time together.
Tú y yo pasando tiempo de calidad juntos.
But what does that...?
¿Pero qué significa eso...?
For Chandler!
¡Por Chandler!
Okay. I'm in.
Okay. Me apunto.
Okay! This is what we'll call it: Joey and Janice's Day of Fun!
¡Okay! Esto es lo que llamaremos: ¡El Día de Diversión de Joey y Janice!
Does it have to be a day?
¿Tiene que ser un día?
Yes, because that's how long it takes to love me.
Sí, porque así es como se tarda en amarme.
Yeah, I know. Ha. I sleep in the next room.
Sí, lo sé. Ja. Duermo en la habitación de al lado.
I went down to the post office...
Fui a la oficina de correos...
...and it turns out it was those videos that I ordered...
...y resulta que eran esos videos que pedí...
...for Richard about the Civil War.
...para Richard sobre la Guerra Civil.
He loved the Civil War.
Le encantaba la Guerra Civil.
Do you want us to take you home?
¿Quieren que las llevemos a casa?
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
Or maybe to a galaxy far, far away.
O tal vez a una galaxia muy, muy lejana.
Women tell each other everything. Did you know that?
Las mujeres se cuentan todo. ¿Sabías eso?
Ha, ha. Yeah.
Ja, ja. Sí.
No, Chandler, everything.
No, Chandler, todo.
Like stuff you like. Stuff she likes.
Como cosas que te gustan. Cosas que le gustan a ella.
Technique. Stamina. Girth.
Técnica. Resistencia. Grosor.
Girth?
¿Grosor?
Why? Why? Why?
¿Por qué? ¿Por qué? ¿Por qué?
Why would they do this?
¿Por qué harían esto?
Rachel says sharing's great and supposedly...
Rachel dice que compartir es genial y supuestamente...
...we ought to be doing it.
...deberíamos hacerlo.
Uh, do you want to?
Uh, ¿quieres hacerlo?
- We're not gonna talk about girth? - No.
- ¿No vamos a hablar de grosor? - No.
- Yeah. Okay. Yeah. - Yeah?
- Sí. Vale. Sí. - ¿Sí?
All right, you go first.
Muy bien, tú primero.
- Okay. Okay, I'll go first. - Okay.
- Vale. Vale, yo primero. - Vale.
So, uh, the other night...
Entonces, uh, la otra noche...
...Rachel and I are in bed talking about fantasies...
...Rachel y yo estábamos en la cama hablando de fantasías...
...and I happened to describe a particular...
...y describí una particular...
...Star Wars thing...
...cosa de Star Wars...
- Princess Leia and the gold bikini. - Yes.
- La Princesa Leia y el bikini dorado. - Sí.
- I know! - Yes.
- ¡Lo sé! - Sí.
Whoa. Wow.
Vaya. Guau.
- Well, that was easy. Ha, ha. - Ha, ha.
- Bueno, eso fue fácil. Ja, ja. - Ja, ja.
Okay, you go.
Vale, tú.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Vale. - Vale.
Okay, you know when you're in bed with a woman...
Vale, ¿sabes cuando estás en la cama con una mujer...
Uh.
...and, uh, ahem, you know, you're fooling around...
...y, eh, ejem, ya sabes, estáis jugando...
...and you get all these mental images in your brain?
...y te vienen todas estas imágenes a la cabeza?
Like Elle MacPherson or the girl at the Xerox place?
¿Como Elle MacPherson o la chica de la fotocopiadora?
- With the bellybutton ring? Oh. - Oh! I know.
- ¿Con el piercing en el ombligo? Oh. - ¡Oh! Lo sé.
And then all of a sudden, your mom pops into your head.
Y de repente, tu madre aparece en tu cabeza.
And you're, like, "Mom, get out of here!"
Y dices: "¡Mamá, sal de aquí!"
But after that, you can't think of anything else.
Pero después de eso, no puedes pensar en nada más.
And you can't stop what you're doing. So it's kind of like you're...
Y no puedes parar lo que estás haciendo. Así que es como si estuvieras...
...you know, you know...
...ya sabes, ya sabes...
You don't know!
¡No lo sabes!
Your mom?
¿Tu mamá?
You're telling me about your mom? What's the matter with you?
¿Me estás contando lo de tu mamá? ¿Qué te pasa?
- You said... - I said "share," not "scare"!
- Dijiste... - ¡Dije "compartir", no "asustar"!
Go sit over there!
Ve a sentarte allí.
- We're back! Hey.
- ¡Volvimos! Hola.
What are you guys doing together?
¿Qué hacen juntos?
Joey and Janice's Day of Fun!
¡El Día Divertido de Joey y Janice!
- Really? Yeah, yeah.
- ¿En serio? Sí, sí.
We went to a Mets game. We got Chinese food.
Fuimos a un partido de los Mets. Comimos comida china.
And, uh, you know, I love this woman. Ha-ha-ha.
Y, eh, ya sabes, amo a esta mujer. Ja-ja-ja.
You have got competition, buddy.
Tienes competencia, amigo.
Well, I just came by to give you a kiss.
Bueno, solo vine a darte un beso.
Mwah.
I have to go pick up the baby. So I'll see you later, sweetheart.
Tengo que ir a recoger al bebé. Así que te veo luego, cariño.
You too, Chandler.
Tú también, Chandler.
- You still can't stand her, can you? - I'm sorry, man. I tried! I really did!
- Todavía no la soportas, ¿verdad? - ¡Lo siento, amigo! ¡Lo intenté! ¡De verdad lo hice!
I appreciate you giving it a shot.
Aprecio que lo hayas intentado.
But you know, the good thing...
Pero sabes, lo bueno...
...is that we spent the whole day together and I survived.
...es que pasamos todo el día juntos y sobreviví.
And what's even more amazing, so did she. Ha, ha.
Y lo que es aún más asombroso, ella también. Ja, ja.
It was Bat Day at Shea Stadium.
Era el Día de Batman en el Shea Stadium.
I guess that's something.
Supongo que eso es algo.
Oh, man, that's huge!
¡Oh, hombre, eso es enorme!
Now I know I can stand to be around her. Which means...
Ahora sé que puedo soportar estar cerca de ella. Lo que significa...
...I get to hang out with you.
...que puedo pasar tiempo contigo.
Which is kind of the whole point anyway. Ha, ha.
Que es como el propósito de todo de todos modos. Ja, ja.
Okay.
Oh, hey! We, uh, stopped by the coffee shop and, uh, ran into Ross.
¡Oh, hola! Eh, pasamos por la cafetería y, eh, nos encontramos con Ross.
Oh, God.
Ay, Dios.
If it makes you feel any better, I do it too.
Si te consuela, yo también lo hago.
Oh.
- Really? - Oh, yeah!
- ¿En serio? - ¡Oh, sí!
I always picture your mom when I'm having sex.
Siempre me imagino a tu mamá cuando estoy teniendo sexo.
April 12, 1861.
12 de abril de 1861.
The United States garrison at Fort Sumter was fired upon.
La guarnición de los Estados Unidos en Fort Sumter fue atacada.
It is now under bombardment by...
Está ahora bajo bombardeo por...
Dad, what are you doing here?
Papá, ¿qué haces aquí?
It's your mother's bridge night, so I came into the city for a Moni-cuddle.
Es la noche de puente de tu madre, así que vine a la ciudad para un "Moni-abrazo".
Oh.
Since when did you start smoking cigars?
¿Desde cuándo fumas puros?
I don't. I just like the smell of them.
No lo hago. Solo me gusta su olor.
So, uh, what are you really doing here?
Entonces, eh, ¿qué haces realmente aquí?
I just wanted to make sure you're okay.
Solo quería asegurarme de que estás bien.
Why wouldn't I be okay?
¿Por qué no iba a estar bien?
I saw Richard.
Vi a Richard.
Oh?
¿Ah sí?
So how you doing?
Entonces, ¿cómo estás?
I'm fine.
Estoy bien.
I'm just a little tired, but I'm okay.
Solo estoy un poco cansada, pero estoy bien.
- Ahem. How's Richard doing? - You don't want to know.
- Ejem. ¿Cómo está Richard? - No quieres saber.
No, I really, really do.
No, de verdad, de verdad quiero.
Well, he's doing terrible!
¡Bueno, él está fatal!
Really?
¿En serio?
Worse than when he broke up with Barbara.
Peor que cuando rompió con Barbara.
- You're not just saying that, are you? - No, the man is a mess!
- No solo lo dices, ¿verdad? - ¡No, el hombre es un desastre!
- Was he crying? - No.
- ¿Estaba llorando? - No.
Do you think he was waiting till after you left, so he could cry?
¿Crees que estaba esperando a que te fueras para poder llorar?
Maybe.
Quizás.
I think so.
Creo que sí.
Honey, relationships are hard. Like with your mom and me.
Cariño, las relaciones son difíciles. Como con tu mamá y yo.
You know, after we graduated from college, we broke up for a while.
Sabes, después de que nos graduamos de la universidad, rompimos por un tiempo.
It seems her father, your grandfather...
Parece que su padre, tu abuelo...
...wanted her to travel around Europe like he did.
...quería que ella viajara por Europa como él lo hizo.
Of course, he got to do it on Uncle Sam's nickel...
Claro, él pudo hacerlo con dinero del Tío Sam...
...because he was also strafing German troop trains at the time.
...porque también estaba ametrallando trenes de tropas alemanas en ese momento.
However...
Sin embargo...
Okay, here we go.
Okay, allá vamos.
I am Jabba's prisoner. And you...
Soy prisionero de Jabba. Y tú...
...have a really weird look on your face.
tienes una cara muy rara.
What? Honey, what is it?
¿Qué? Cariño, ¿qué pasa?
Did I get the hair wrong?
¿Me equivoqué con el pelo?
Or what? Did you just picture it differently? What?
¿O qué? ¿Te lo imaginaste diferente? ¿Qué?
No, no. It's, um... It's not you. It's, um...
No, no. Es, eh... No eres tú. Es, eh...
What is it? Come on, sweetie. You're, like, freaking me out here.
¿Qué es? Vamos, cielo. Me estás asustando.
I hate Chandler. The bastard ruined my life!
Odio a Chandler. ¡El bastardo arruinó mi vida!