So whose idea was it to put everybody in the diner on skates?
[ERROR API]
Some idiot customer put a suggestion in the suggestion box.
- Oh, my God. They took my idea. - That was you?
[ERROR API]
Yeah.
Sí.
Okay, there you go.
[ERROR API]
Rachel, I made you a cocoa.
Oh, that's so... Aah!
[ERROR API]
Ow!
¡Ay!
- Oh, my God. Are you guys okay? - You all right?
[ERROR API]
Oh, my.
Oh, vaya.
Hey.
Oye.
You know, with that goatee, you kind of look like Satan.
[ERROR API]
Oh, so that's why the priest threw holy water on me.
Okay, listen, you have to cheer up.
[ERROR API]
Okay? You should come out with Ross and me.
I mean, anything is better than sitting around here crying all day about Kate.
[ERROR API]
Hey, I was crying because...
Because nobody believed Quincy's theory, okay?
[ERROR API]
- Hey. I'm gonna be on TV. Hey.
- No way. Yeah.
[ERROR API]
They're putting together this panel to talk about these fossils they found in Peru.
The Discovery Channel's gonna film it.
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God. Heh. Who's gonna watch that?
- Thanks. You ready to go? Yeah.
[ERROR API]
Ahem, I saw a girl with that vest.
Thanks.
Gracias.
- Most of us think of chocolate bunnies and baskets as traditional Easter gifts.
[ERROR API]
Some people insist on giving live chicks as presents.
Unfortunately, the sad fact remains...
[ERROR API]
...that most of these little guys won't live to see the Fourth of July.
Because as a result of improper care, they will be dead.
[ERROR API]
You guys got any of those baby chicks?
Because I was watching this, uh, commercial on TV...
[ERROR API]
...and, man, those things are cute.
- Hi. Hi.
- Hola. Hola.
Oh, Pete, you're back. Hey, check this out.
[ERROR API]
Wow. Skates. Ha, ha.
Whoa.
Wow. You're a lot sturdier than Chandler. He crumbled like a piece of paper.
[ERROR API]
So how was your trip?
- Well... - Oh, what did you bring me?
[ERROR API]
Aw, hotel toiletries from Japan. Oh.
These are gonna go in my permanent collection.
[ERROR API]
- You want some coffee? - Sure, that'd be great.
Okay.
- Regular or decaf? Ha, ha.
[ERROR API]
- Uh, whichever's closest. All right.
- Okay. - So ask me what I did today.
[ERROR API]
So, what did you do today, Pete?
I bought a restaurant, and I would like you to be the chef.
[ERROR API]
What? Oh.
“¿Qué? Ay.
Can you believe he just offered me a restaurant?
¿Puedes creer que me ofreció un restaurante?
What a jerk. You want me to kick his ass?
Qué imbécil. ¿Quieres que lo noquee?
I mean, this has been my dream since I got my first Easy-Bake Oven...
O sea, este ha sido mi sueño desde que tuve mi primera cocina de juguete...
...and opened Easy-Monica's Bakery.
...y abrí la pastelería "Fácil-Mónica".
I mean, I would kill for this job. I mean, I can totally do this job...
O sea, mataría por este trabajo. O sea, puedo hacer este trabajo totalmente...
...and God knows I've paid my dues. Ugh.
...y Dios sabe que ya cumplí mi cuota. Uf.
But Pete's just doing this because he has a crush on me.
Pero Pete solo hace esto porque le gusto.
- And you're still not attracted to him at all? - Mm. No.
- ¿Y sigues sin sentir nada por él? - Mmm. No.
I mean, how could I accept a restaurant from him? I can't.
O sea, ¿cómo podría aceptar un restaurante de él? No puedo.
I couldn't even accept a necklace from Stu Vincent in the seventh grade.
Ni siquiera pude aceptar un collar de Stu Vincent en séptimo grado.
Yeah, Mon, that was totally different. He was your health teacher.
Sí, Mon, eso fue totalmente diferente. Él era tu profesor de salud.
- Ow. - What, honey?
- Ay. - ¿Qué, cariño?
Ow, my side still hurts from when you crashed into me yesterday.
Ay, todavía me duele el costado de cuando chocaste contra mí ayer.
- Oh, God, I'm so sorry. - I know. Ow.
- Oh, Dios, lo siento muchísimo. - Lo sé. Ay.
Oh, God.
Ay, Dios.
- Hey, you guys. Guess what. Hey.
- Hola, chicos. Adivinen qué. Hola.
Got a job on a riverboat?
¿Conseguiste trabajo en un barco de río?
You know what? I didn't wear this suit for a year because you hated it.
¿Sabes qué? No usé este traje en un año porque lo odiabas.
Guess what. You're not my girlfriend anymore, so...
Adivina qué. Ya no eres mi novia, así que...
- Oh, I see. So this suit is making a point. Mm.
- Oh, ya veo. Así que este traje está mandando un mensaje. Mmm.
Now that you're on your own, you're free to look as stupid as you'd like.
Ahora que estás sola, eres libre de verte tan estúpida como quieras.
You like it, right?
Te gusta, ¿verdad?
Absolutely. I like it even more on you than I did on Colonel Sanders.
Absolutamente. Me gusta incluso más en ti que en el Coronel Sanders.
Huh. Ross, Ross, I'm kidding. Come here.
¿Eh? Ross, Ross, es broma. Ven aquí.
- What were you gonna tell us? - Was it how you invented the cotton gin?
- ¿Qué nos ibas a decir? - ¿Fue cómo inventaste la desmotadora de algodón?
Okay, goodbye.
Okay, adiós.
So, um, after you put the suggestion in the box...
Entonces, eh, después de que pusiste la sugerencia en el buzón...
...how long did it take for the roller-skating thing to happen?
...¿cuánto tiempo tardó en suceder lo de los patines?
Um, about three months.
Eh, como tres meses.
Okay, so I guess that's about, uh, two weeks...
Okay, entonces supongo que eso es como, eh, dos semanas...
...before the topless thing kicks in.
...antes de que empiece lo de los topless.
- Hey. Hey.
- Oye. Oye.
I got you something. Open it. Open it.
Te traje algo. Ábrelo. Ábrelo.
Okay.
It's a chicken.
Es un pollito.
It's cute, huh?
Es lindo, ¿eh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You guys, do you know anything about chicks?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Chicos, ¿saben algo sobre pollitos?
Fowl? No.
¿Aves? No.
Women? No.
¿Mujeres? No.
Okay, well, they are a huge responsibility.
Okay, bueno, son una gran responsabilidad.
Especially at this age. They require constant care.
Especialmente a esta edad. Requieren cuidado constante.
They need just the right food and lots and lots of love.
Necesitan la comida justa y mucho, mucho amor.
Oh, well, no problem there.
Oh, bueno, no hay problema con eso.
Easy, Lenny.
Tranquilo, Lenny.
So, I mean, have you thought about it?
Entonces, o sea, ¿lo has pensado?
Okay, here's the thing.
Okay, aquí está el asunto.
Oh, no. Not "the thing. " I hate "the thing. "
Oh, no. No "el asunto". Odio "el asunto".
What's "the thing"?
¿Qué es "el asunto"?
I can't do it.
No puedo hacerlo.
I'm sorry. I wish I could...
Lo siento. Desearía poder...
...but, um, see, you have these feelings for me.
...pero, eh, mira, tú tienes estos sentimientos por mí.
Wait, wait, wait. That's what you're worried about?
Espera, espera, espera. ¿Eso es lo que te preocupa?
If that's the problem, we've got no problem.
Si ese es el problema, no tenemos ningún problema.
- Huh? - No.
- ¿Eh? - No.
I was gonna tell you this over dinner, but I met somebody else, on my trip.
Te iba a decir esto en la cena, pero conocí a alguien más, en mi viaje.
Oh?
¿Ah sí?
Her name's Ann. She's a journalist. Uh, we met on the plane.
Se llama Ann. Es periodista. Eh, nos conocimos en el avión.
She asked me if she could finish off my peanuts.
Me preguntó si podía terminar mis cacahuates.
I thought she said something else. We had a big laugh.
Pensé que dijo otra cosa. Nos reímos mucho.
Yeah, I just... I mean, I got tired of waiting.
Sí, yo solo... quiero decir, me cansé de esperar.
Oh, that's great. I mean, I'm sorry, but I'm so happy for you.
Oh, eso es genial. Quiero decir, lo siento, pero estoy muy feliz por ti.
- And now I can work for you. - I guess you can.
- Y ahora puedo trabajar para ti. - Supongo que sí.
Oh, my God. Oh, this is incredible. Oh.
Oh, Dios mío. Oh, esto es increíble. Oh.
All right. You know what? I'm just gonna roll right into that office and quit.
Está bien. ¿Sabes qué? Voy a ir directo a esa oficina y renunciar.
- All right. - Okay.
- Está bien. - Okay.
- Could you give me a little push? - Yeah, sure.
- ¿Me das un empujoncito? - Sí, claro.
- Good luck. I'm quitting. Woo-hoo!
- ¡Buena suerte! ¡Renuncio! ¡Woo-hoo!
I'm okay. I'm all right.
Estoy bien. Estoy bien.
Wow. That's exciting. You went to Japan, made up a woman.
Vaya. Eso es emocionante. Fuiste a Japón, inventaste una mujer.
What?
¿Qué?
I'm just saying, this woman, I mean, she's fictitious, no?
Solo digo, esta mujer, quiero decir, es ficticia, ¿no?
- Why would you say that? - You're still into Monica.
- ¿Por qué dirías eso? - Todavía te gusta Monica.
So you told her there's somebody else so she'd agree to work with you.
Así que le dijiste que hay alguien más para que aceptara trabajar contigo.
Because you figure, if you spend time together, maybe something might happen.
Porque piensas que, si pasan tiempo juntos, tal vez algo suceda.
You're good. You're good.
Eres bueno. Eres bueno.
Yeah. No, I'm fairly intuitive. And psychic.
Sí. No, soy bastante intuitivo. Y psíquico.
It's a substantial gift.
Es un don sustancial.
Listen, can you promise me that you won't tell her, though?
Escucha, ¿puedes prometerme que no le dirás, sin embargo?
Absolutely. Oh, I promise. Tell her what?
Absolutamente. Oh, lo prometo. ¿Decirle qué?
Thanks a lot.
Muchas gracias.
No, I'm serious. I mean, I'm intuitive, but my memory sucks.
No, en serio. Quiero decir, soy intuitivo, pero mi memoria es terrible.
Okay, but this is the last time.
Está bien, pero esta es la última vez.
With a chick-chick here And a chick-chick there
Con un chick-chick aquí Y un chick-chick allá
Here a chick, there a chick Everywhere a chick-chick
Aquí un pollito, allá un pollito Por todas partes un pollito-pollito
Chicken
Pollo
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
How's she doing?
¿Cómo está ella?
She?
¿Ella?
Well, yeah. Don't you think it's a she?
Bueno, sí. ¿No crees que es una ella?
I don't know.
No sé.
I can't tell. Whatever it was, went back in too quickly.
No puedo decirlo. Lo que sea que fuera, volvió a entrar demasiado rápido.
Anyway, I gotta change. I'm meeting some of the cast for drinks.
En fin, tengo que cambiarme. Me reuniré con algunos del elenco para tomar algo.
Excuse me?
¿Perdón?
What?
¿Qué?
I stayed home from work while you were at rehearsal...
Me quedé en casa del trabajo mientras tú estabas en el ensayo...
...so somebody could be here with our chick.
...así que alguien podía estar aquí con nuestra pollita.
Hey. Who was up from 2:00 this morning until 5:00 this morning...
Oye. ¿Quién estuvo despierto desde las 2:00 de esta mañana hasta las 5:00 de esta mañana...
...trying to get her back to sleep?
...intentando que volviera a dormir?
You don't think I get up when you get up?
¿No crees que me levanto cuando tú te levantas?
Oh, here it comes.
Aquí viene.
Yes. Here it comes. I'm stuck here all day.
Sí. Aquí viene. Me quedaré aquí todo el día.
And then you come in and spend two seconds with us...
Y luego vienes tú y pasas dos segundos con nosotros...
...and then expect to go off gallivanting with your friends?
...¿y luego esperas irte de parranda con tus amigos?
Well, I don't think so, mister.
Pues, no lo creo, señor.
Hey. I need to relax, okay? I was working all day.
Oye. Necesito relajarme, ¿vale? Estuve trabajando todo el día.
And you don't think taking care of our chick is work?
¿Y tú no crees que cuidar a nuestra polluela es trabajo?
That's not what I said. Okay, I just meant...
Eso no fue lo que dije. Vale, solo quise decir...
I know what you meant.
Sé lo que quisiste decir.
Did you notice that ever since we got this chick...
¿Te diste cuenta de que desde que tenemos esta polluela...
...we've been fighting a lot more than we used to?
...hemos estado peleando mucho más de lo que solíamos?
I don't know, maybe we weren't ready to have a chick.
No sé, quizás no estábamos listos para tener una polluela.
I'll take her back tomorrow.
La llevaré de vuelta mañana.
You think we'll get our 3 bucks back?
¿Crees que nos devolverán los 3 dólares?
- Hey. Hey.
- Oye. Oye.
Oh. Hey.
Oh. Hola.
Listen, I have that TV thing in, like, two hours, and I need your help.
Escucha, tengo lo de la tele en como dos horas, y necesito tu ayuda.
Okay, what do you think? This blue suit or this brown one?
Vale, ¿qué opinas? ¿Este traje azul o este marrón?
Well, the brown one brings out your eyes.
Bueno, el marrón resalta tus ojos.
But your butt looks great in the blue one.
Pero tu trasero se ve genial en el azul.
Really?
¿En serio?
Ow.
Ay.
Wow. That aspirin dance really works.
Vaya. Ese baile de la aspirina sí que funciona.
Ow. - Oh, my God. Is that still?
Ay. - ¡Dios mío! ¿Eso todavía?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Estoy bien. Estoy bien.
- No, you're not. - Yes, I am.
- No, no lo estás. - Sí, lo estoy.
- Rach. - Look, I'm fine.
- Rach. - Mira, estoy bien.
Watch. Look at that. Uh-oh.
Mira. Mira eso. Uh-oh.
Okay, okay. Look, you've got to go to a doctor, okay?
Vale, vale. Mira, tienes que ir al médico, ¿vale?
No, I have to get ready and go to a dinner at my boss's house.
No, tengo que arreglarme e ir a una cena en casa de mi jefe.
Very big deal. There's people there that I have to meet.
Muy importante. Hay gente allí que tengo que conocer.
Yeah, and I'm sure you're gonna make a great impression. "Hi, I'm Rachel.
Sí, y estoy seguro de que causarás una gran impresión. "Hola, soy Rachel.
It's nice to meet you. "
Encantada de conocerte."
Come on, you probably have a broken rib.
Vamos, probablemente tienes una costilla rota.
Well, I will go to the hospital tomorrow. It'll still be broken then.
Bueno, iré al hospital mañana. Seguirá rota entonces.
But you know, I could use a hand getting ready.
Pero sabes, podría usar una mano para arreglarme.
- Rachel. - Look, either help me or go.
- Rachel. - Mira, o me ayudas o me voy.
Fine. I'll go.
Bien. Me voy.
Okay, but before you go, could you help me first?
Vale, pero antes de que te vayas, ¿podrías ayudarme primero?
Sure. I'll help you.
Claro. Te ayudaré.
Oh, good. Good.
Oh, bien. Bien.
Do you guys know how to get a chick out of a VCR?
¿Saben cómo sacar una polluela de un VCR?
You know what? I cannot do this with my left hand.
¿Sabes qué? No puedo hacer esto con la mano izquierda.
Would you please help me with this too?
¿Me ayudarías con esto también, por favor?
- Okay. Let's use this brush. - Okay.
- Vale. Usemos este pincel. - Vale.
- This stuff? All right. - Yeah. Careful.
- ¿Esto? De acuerdo. - Sí. Cuidado.
Light. Okay, you know, just sweep it across the lid.
Luz. Vale, sabes, solo pásalo por el párpado.
- Okay, just sweep it. - Okey-dokey.
- Vale, solo pásalo. - Okey-dokey.
- Oh. Hey. - Sorry.
- Oh. Hola. - Perdón.
- Ha, ha. That's poking me in the eye. - Ha, ha.
- Ja, ja. Me estás picando en el ojo. - Ja, ja.
I'm sorry. Close, close, close.
Lo siento. Cerca, cerca, cerca.
- Okay, just sweep it. - I'm sweeping.
- Está bien, solo barre. - Estoy barriendo.
- Right. - Sweep, sweep...
- Correcto. - Barre, barre...
Okay, now make it even, because we don't...
Okay, ahora hazlo uniforme, porque no queremos...
- What? - We don't want it...
- ¿Qué? - No queremos que...
I don't want it to be too much. I want it to be subtle.
No quiero que sea demasiado. Quiero que sea sutil.
You know, you don't wear enough of this.
Sabes, no usas suficiente de esto.
Since when...? Since when do you think I don't wear enough of this?
¿Desde cuándo...? ¿Desde cuándo crees que no uso suficiente de esto?
Well, I... Close your eye. I just think you're gonna like this better because...
Bueno, yo... Cierra el ojo. Creo que te va a gustar más porque...
- Close, close. - Blow it.
- Cerca, cerca. - Sopla.
Sorry.
Lo siento.
Because, um, I think this will make you a little more sophisticated.
Porque, eh, creo que esto te hará un poco más sofisticada.
Sophisticated like a hooker?
¿Sofisticada como una prostituta?
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- Guess what I'm doing tonight. - What?
- Adivina qué hago hoy. - ¿Qué?
I'm checking out the restaurant with Pete.
Voy a revisar el restaurante con Pete.
- Oh. Monica, I am so excited for you. - I know.
- Oh. Monica, estoy muy emocionada por ti. - Lo sé.
Ooh, I have to tell you something.
Ooh, tengo que contarte algo.
- What? - Well, I can't tell you.
- ¿Qué? - Bueno, no puedo decírtelo.
Okay, but wouldn't it be easier to tell me something that you could tell me?
Está bien, pero ¿no sería más fácil decirme algo que sí puedas decirme?
Well, sure, in a perfect world.
Bueno, claro, en un mundo perfecto.
But no. I promised I wouldn't tell, and I swore to, like, all my gods.
Pero no. Prometí no decirlo, y lo juré por, como, todos mis dioses.
Okay.
Does it have to do with Ross and Rachel?
¿Tiene que ver con Ross y Rachel?
No.
- Does it have to do with Joey? - No.
- ¿Tiene que ver con Joey? - No.
Does it have to do with Chandler and that sock that he keeps by his bed?
¿Tiene que ver con Chandler y ese calcetín que guarda junto a su cama?
No, but let's come back to that later.
No, pero volvamos a eso más tarde.
There you go. Good enough for your party? Huh?
Ahí tienes. ¿Suficiente para tu fiesta? ¿Eh?
Sure.
Claro.
Sure. I'll just sit next to the transsexual from Purchasing.
Claro. Me sentaré junto a la persona transexual de Compras.
Come on.
Vamos.
Okay, come on. All right, I gotta go. So good luck at the party, okay?
Okay, vamos. Bien, tengo que irme. Así que suerte en la fiesta, ¿okay?
Oh, wait, Ross. Could you just stay and help me get dressed?
Oh, espera, Ross. ¿Podrías quedarte y ayudarme a vestirme?
Sure. Okay.
Claro. Está bien.
Okay. Okay, great. Um, okay, just turn around.
Okay. Okay, genial. Eh, okay, solo date la vuelta.
- What? - I don't want you to see me naked.
- ¿Qué? - No quiero que me veas desnuda.
Rachel, I've seen you naked a million times. I ate hot fudge off you naked.
Rachel, te he visto desnuda un millón de veces. Comí dulce de chocolate de tu cuerpo desnudo.
I sucked that mini-marshmallow out of your bellybutton.
Te saqué ese mini-malvavisco de tu ombligo.
Yeah, but that was different, you know? We were going out then.
Sí, pero eso era diferente, ¿sabes? Estábamos saliendo entonces.
Now it's weird.
Ahora es raro.
Rach, you know, I can see you naked anytime I want.
Rach, sabes que puedo verte desnuda cuando quiera.
- What? - Ha, ha.
- ¿Qué? - Ja, ja.
All I have to do is close my eyes. See? Woo-hoo.
Solo tengo que cerrar los ojos. ¿Ves? Woo-hoo.
- Ross, stop that. - I'm sorry.
- Ross, para con eso. - Lo siento.
Come on. I don't want you thinking of me like that anymore.
Vamos. Ya no quiero que pienses en mí así.
Uh, sorry. Nothing you can do about it.
Uh, lo siento. No hay nada que puedas hacer al respecto.
It's one of my, uh, rights as the ex-boyfriend.
Es uno de mis, eh, derechos como exnovio.
Huh? Oh. Oh, yeah.
¿Eh? Oh. Oh, sí.
- Stop it. Cut it out. Cut it out. - Okay, okay.
- Para. Corta eso. Corta eso. - Está bien, está bien.
I'm sorry. It will never happen... Uh-oh.
Lo siento. Nunca volverá a pasar... Ay, no.
Wait a minute. Wait, wait...
Espera un minuto. Espera, espera...
Now there are a hundred of you, and I'm the king.
Ahora son cien y yo soy el rey.
- Ross... - Oh, come on.
- Ross... - Ay, vamos.
Would you grow up? It's no big deal.
¿Puedes madurar? No es para tanto.
All right. Fine.
De acuerdo. Bien.
- Yowza. - Okay.
- ¡Wow! - Vale.
See what you did? I'm gonna be doing it by myself now.
¿Ves lo que hiciste? Ahora lo haré yo solo.
- Okay, that's it. Ow! - Oh, come on.
- Vale, eso es todo. ¡Ay! - Ay, vamos.
Oh, my God. All right, look, look, okay.
Dios mío. Está bien, mira, mira, vale.
Rach. Easy. Easy. You have to go to the hospital, okay?
Rach. Tranquila. Tranquila. Tienes que ir al hospital, ¿vale?
- Okay, I do. I really do. - Okay.
- Vale, lo hago. De verdad que sí. - Vale.
Okay, I'm gonna get your coat, then I'll put you in a cab.
Vale, voy a buscar tu abrigo, luego te subo a un taxi.
Oh, wait, wait, you're not gonna come with me?
Oh, espera, espera, ¿no vienes conmigo?
Of course I am.
Claro que sí.
Uh, I just have to make a call.
Eh, solo tengo que hacer una llamada.
- Okay. - Okay?
- Okay. - ¿Okay?
Thank you.
Gracias.
Ow!
¡Ay!
What's wrong?
¿Qué pasa?
I'm sorry. I just can't go to the hospital looking like this.
Lo siento. No puedo ir al hospital así.
- Does it involve travel? - No.
- ¿Implica viajar? - No.
Does it involve clogs?
¿Implica zuecos?
Wait, wait. Clogs or claws?
Espera, espera. ¿Zuecos o garras?
- Clogs. - No.
- ¿Zuecos? - No.
- Claws? - No.
- ¿Garras? - No.
Okay, so it doesn't involve Ross or Rachel or Chandler or Joey.
Vale, entonces no tiene que ver con Ross, Rachel o Chandler o Joey.
- What about Pete? - No.
- ¿Y Pete? - No.
What is it?
¿Qué es?
- What about Pete? - I don't know.
- ¿Y Pete? - No lo sé.
Okay, I feel like I'm talking to Lassie.
Vale, siento que estoy hablando con Lassie.
- Phoebe, would you just tell me? - I can't.
- Phoebe, ¿me lo dices ya? - No puedo.
- Okay, you know, I gotta go. - But you're so close. No.
- Vale, sabes qué, me tengo que ir. - Pero estás muy cerca. No.
Something to do with Pete's company?
¿Algo que ver con la empresa de Pete?
Ugh. Just go. You're never gonna get it.
Uf. Anda, vete ya. Nunca lo vas a adivinar.
I know.
Lo sé.
See, yes. That's Yasmine Bleeth.
Mira, sí. Esa es Yasmine Bleeth.
She's a completely different kind of chick.
Es un tipo de chica completamente diferente.
I love you both.
Los quiero a los dos.
But in very different ways.
Pero de maneras muy diferentes.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Ooh. Ah.
What are you doing? I though you were gonna take her back.
¿Qué estás haciendo? Pensé que la ibas a devolver.
I did. But the store wouldn't take her back.
Lo hice. Pero la tienda no la aceptó de vuelta.
So then I took her to the shelter. And you know what I found out?
Así que la llevé al refugio. ¿Y sabes qué descubrí?
If they can't find a home for her, they kill her.
Si no encuentran un hogar para ella, la matan.
And I'm not gonna let that happen to little Yasmine.
Y no voy a dejar que eso le pase a la pequeña Yasmine.
Okay, good, good, good.
Vale, bien, bien, bien.
Because I was kind of having second thoughts too.
Porque yo también estaba dudando un poco.
Okay. And it's not just chicks, you know? It's all kinds of other animals.
Vale. Y no son solo chicas, ¿sabes? Son todo tipo de animales.
That's horrible. Well, you did the right thing, man.
Eso es horrible. Bueno, hiciste lo correcto, amigo.
Thanks. I'm glad you see it that way.
Gracias. Me alegra que lo veas así.
Oh, funny story.
Oh, qué historia tan graciosa.
I don't believe this.
No puedo creer esto.
Wow, look at this refrigerator. It's gigantic.
Vaya, mira este refrigerador. Es gigantesco.
I mean, I could live in this thing. I'd be cold, but I'm always cold.
O sea, podría vivir en esta cosa. Tendría frío, pero yo siempre tengo frío.
Oh, my God. Look at these spider burners. I love spider burners.
Oh, Dios mío. Mira estos quemadores de araña. Me encantan los quemadores de araña.
So you like it?
Entonces, ¿te gusta?
Oh, it is so perfect. Thank you so much.
Oh, es tan perfecto. Muchas gracias.
- You're welcome. - Oh.
De nada. Oh.
Did you just smell my hair?
¿Acabas de oler mi pelo?
No. No way. What? No.
No. De ninguna manera. ¿Qué? No.
- Oh, God. - What?
Oh, Dios. ¿Qué?
You still have feelings for me, don't you?
Todavía sientes algo por mí, ¿verdad?
No. I'm just excited about the restaurant, that's all.
No. Solo estoy emocionado por el restaurante, eso es todo.
- Pete? - Okay, I love you. Is that so bad?
¿Pete? Está bien, te amo. ¿Eso está tan mal?
No, it's not bad. It's not bad at all.
No, no está mal. No está mal para nada.
It's really nice.
Es realmente agradable.
Look, the only one who stands to get hurt is me, and I'm okay with that.
Mira, el único que podría salir herido soy yo, y estoy bien con eso.
Yeah, you may be okay with getting hurt...
Sí, tú puedes estar bien con salir herido...
...but I am not okay with being the one who hurts you.
...pero yo no estoy bien con ser quien te lastima.
- That's why I can't take this job. - What?
Por eso no puedo aceptar este trabajo. ¿Qué?
Well, we probably shouldn't see each other anymore.
Bueno, probablemente no deberíamos vernos más.
I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
Okay. Yeah.
Está bien. Sí.
I mean, if that's really what you want, okay.
O sea, si eso es realmente lo que quieres, está bien.
Okay. Bye.
Está bien. Adiós.
I'm sorry things didn't work out...
Lamento que las cosas no hayan funcionado...
Shut up for a second and let me just see something.
Cállate un segundo y déjame ver algo.
Oh, wow.
Okay, you'd tell me the truth, right?
Está bien, me dirías la verdad, ¿verdad?
- Rach, you can't look fat in an x-ray. - Okay.
Rach, no puedes salir gorda en una radiografía. Está bien.
Hey, now, you stay out here and you think about what you did.
Oye, ahora, tú quédate aquí afuera y piensa en lo que hiciste.
- That's a duck. - That's a bad duck.
Eso es un pato. Ese es un pato malo.
- How'd the thing go tonight, Ross? - Oh, it was... No, no.
¿Cómo fue lo de esta noche, Ross? Oh, fue... No, no.
What thing? What thing?
¿Qué cosa? ¿Qué cosa?
Nothing. There was this thing at the museum. Come on.
Nada. Hubo una cosa en el museo. Vamos.
Easy.
Tranquila.
Okay, now, when you come back...
Está bien, ahora, cuando vuelvas...
...I hope you remember that that chick is not a toy.
...espero que recuerdes que esa chica no es un juguete.
What thing? What is this thing?
¿Qué cosa? ¿Qué es esta cosa?
Aw, I was kind of supposed to be on TV tonight for the Discovery Channel.
Ay, se suponía que iba a estar en la tele esta noche para el Discovery Channel.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
Ross, why didn't you tell me that?
Ross, ¿por qué no me dijiste eso?
Ah, I knew that if I told you, you'd make me go...
Ah, sabía que si te lo decía, me harías ir...
...and I knew you needed someone to be with you tonight. Come on.
...y sabía que necesitabas a alguien contigo esta noche. Vamos.
- Come on. - I cannot believe you.
Vamos. No puedo creerlo.
- What? - That is the sweetest thing.
¿Qué? Eso es lo más dulce.
You should get some sleep.
Deberías dormir un poco.
Okay.
- So I'll, um... - I'm sorry I spoiled your evening.
Entonces yo, eh... Lamento haber arruinado tu noche.
No, that's... No, as long as you're okay.
No, eso es... No, mientras tú estés bien.
So I'll, uh... I'll see you tomorrow.
Entonces yo, eh... Te veo mañana.
Mm-hm. Yeah.
Mm-hm. Sí.
See you.
Nos vemos.
What did you do?
¿Qué hiciste?
What you doing?
¿Qué haces?
Having a swim.
Nadando.
What about the chick?
¿Y la chica?
Chicks don't swim.
Las chicas no nadan.
Are you sure?
¿Estás segura?
I don't know.
No sé.
- Should we try? - Sure.
¿Deberíamos intentarlo? - Claro.
See, I told you. They don't swim.
¿Ves? Te lo dije. No nadan.
- Well, give him a minute. - No.
Bueno, dale un minuto. - No.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay, baby, baby, baby.
Oh, está bien. Está bien, nena, nena, nena.