Wait a minute. You're telling me this actress person...
[ERROR API]
...is the only woman you ever wanted who didn't want you back?
Yeah.
Sí.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
Is this what it's like to be you?
[ERROR API]
- Wow, you're really crazy about her, huh? - Oh. You have no idea.
And when we're on-stage, I get to kiss her and touch her.
[ERROR API]
But then she goes home with the director...
...and it's like somebody's ripping out my heart.
[ERROR API]
Oh, it's so great to see you feeling like this.
- Hey. Hey.
- Oye. Oye.
Monica, uh, Dad called this morning...
[ERROR API]
...and, uh, Aunt Sylvia passed away.
Yes. Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[ERROR API]
We were all pretty shaken up about it.
Wait, am I missing something?
[ERROR API]
Because I always thought death was supposed to be sad, in a way.
Well, uh, Aunt Sylvia was...
[ERROR API]
...well, not a nice person.
No, she was a cruel, cranky old bitch.
[ERROR API]
And I'm sorry she died.
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
[ERROR API]
- You get the dollhouse. - I get the dollhouse.
Wow. A house for dolls. That is so cool.
[ERROR API]
When I was a kid, I had a barrel.
Uh, Pheebs, you had a barrel for a dollhouse?
[ERROR API]
No, just a barrel.
You know what? You can play with my dollhouse.
[ERROR API]
- Really? Really? - Any time you want.
When I was younger, all I wanted to do was to play with this dollhouse.
[ERROR API]
But no. It was to be looked at, but never played with.
My grandmother used to say that exact same thing to me.
[ERROR API]
- Hey, Sophie. - Hey, Rach.
Hey.
Oye.
Thanks for lunch, Chandler. You didn't have to walk me here.
[ERROR API]
Oh, that's okay. No problem.
Honey, you do realize we don't keep the women's lingerie here in the office.
[ERROR API]
Yes, I realize that.
- Summer catalog. - That's the stuff.
[ERROR API]
Rachel, I need the Versace invoice.
Hello. You don't work for me.
[ERROR API]
Joanna, this is my friend Chandler Bing. Joanna.
Bing? Heh. That's a great name.
[ERROR API]
Thanks, it's Gaelic for, "Thy turkey's done. "
- So, uh, I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you. - You too.
[ERROR API]
Bye, Chandler.
So, uh, what's wrong with him?
[ERROR API]
Oh, nothing. He's just goofy like that. I actually hardly notice it anymore.
Oh, no, no, no. I mean, is he, um, married or involved with anyone?
[ERROR API]
No, no. He's not married or involved with anyone.
Oh, Rachel...
Ay, Rachel...
Actually, you know what? Forget it.
En realidad, ¿sabes qué? Olvídalo.
- I'll ask him for you if you want me to. Would you?
- Se lo preguntaré por ti si quieres. ¿Lo harías?
Or is it just too sad and desperate...
¿O es simplemente demasiado triste y desesperado...
...you know, something that Sophie would do?
...sabes, algo que haría Sophie?
- I am here. - I know that.
- Estoy aquí. - Lo sé.
Look at it.
Míralo.
Oh.
Wallpaper's a little faded. That's okay.
El papel tapiz está un poco descolorido. No importa.
Carpet's a little loose.
La alfombra está un poco suelta.
Hardwood floors?
¿Pisos de madera?
- Hey. Oh! Hello.
- Hola. ¡Oh! Hola.
Oh, Monica.
- It's so beautiful. - I know.
- Es tan hermoso. - Lo sé.
- So I'm here, ready to play. Hee-hee. - Okay.
- Así que aquí estoy, lista para jugar. Ji, ji. - De acuerdo.
I brought a bunch of stuff for the house, so check it out. Ha, ha.
Traje un montón de cosas para la casa, así que échale un vistazo. Ja, ja.
What's this?
¿Qué es esto?
That's a dog. Every house should have a dog.
Eso es un perro. Toda casa debería tener un perro.
Not one that can pee on the roof.
No uno que pueda orinar en el techo.
Well, maybe it's so big because the house was built on radioactive waste.
Bueno, tal vez es tan grande porque la casa fue construida sobre residuos radiactivos.
And is this in case the house sneezes?
¿Y esto es por si la casa estornuda?
No. No, that's the ghost for the attic.
No. No, ese es el fantasma para el ático.
- I don't want a ghost. - Well, nobody wants a ghost.
- No quiero un fantasma. - Bueno, nadie quiere un fantasma.
But you've got one...
Pero tienes uno...
...because the house is sitting on an ancient Indian burial ground.
...porque la casa está construida sobre un antiguo cementerio indio.
Wait a minute. The house was built on radioactive waste...
Espera un minuto. La casa fue construida sobre residuos radiactivos...
...and an ancient Indian burial ground?
...¿y un antiguo cementerio indio?
Ha, ha. That would never happen.
Ja, ja. Eso nunca pasaría.
Okay, obviously you don't know much about the U.S. Government. Ha, ha.
Está bien, obviamente no sabes mucho sobre el Gobierno de EE. UU. Ja, ja.
- Hey. Hey.
- Oye. Oye.
- I need to talk to you. - Sure. What's up?
- Necesito hablar contigo. - Claro. ¿Qué pasa?
Oh, sorry. I meant Chandler.
Oh, lo siento. Me refería a Chandler.
Heh. I know.
Lo sé.
Well, if something comes up...
Bueno, si surge algo...
Well, I'm glad you guys are past that little awkward phase.
Bueno, me alegro de que hayan superado esa pequeña fase incómoda.
Okay. My boss, Joanna. When you left...
Está bien. Mi jefa, Joanna. Cuando te fuiste...
...she started asking questions about you.
...ella empezó a hacer preguntas sobre ti.
Ha, ha. Liked what she saw, huh?
Ja, ja. Le gustó lo que vio, ¿eh?
Dug my action, did she?
¿Le gustó mi estilo, verdad?
Checking out the Chan Chan Man.
Viendo al Chan Chan Man.
That was...
Eso fue...
...surreal.
...surrealista.
Okay, what do you think? You interested at all?
Está bien, ¿qué opinas? ¿Te interesa en algo?
Yeah, she seemed cool, attractive. I'll do it.
Sí, parecía buena onda, atractiva. Lo haré.
Oh, thank you, Chandler. This is great. She's gonna love me.
Oh, gracias, Chandler. Esto es genial. Le voy a encantar.
Okay, dinosaur attack. Quick, everybody into the house. Aah!
Está bien, ataque de dinosaurios. Rápido, todos a la casa. ¡Aah!
All right, Phoebe, you know what? That's it. That's it. All right?
Muy bien, Phoebe, ¿sabes qué? Eso es todo. Eso es todo. ¿De acuerdo?
No dinosaurs, no ghosts, no giant dogs, okay?
No dinosaurios, no fantasmas, no perros gigantes, ¿de acuerdo?
They're not the right size, they're not Victorian, and they just don't go.
No son del tamaño adecuado, no son victorianos, y simplemente no pegan.
Okay.
Fine.
Está bien.
Come, dinosaur. We're not welcome in the house of no imagination.
Ven, dinosaurio. No somos bienvenidos en la casa de la falta de imaginación.
Uh, Pheebs, while we're hovering around the subject...
Eh, Pheebs, ya que estamos en el tema...
...I just have to say that dinosaurs, they don't go, "Ruff. "
...tengo que decir que los dinosaurios no dicen "guau".
The little ones do.
Los pequeños sí.
Hey, Kate. - Morning.
Hola, Kate. - Buenos días.
Listen, I, uh, went to that restaurant you talked about...
Mira, eh, fui a ese restaurante del que me hablaste...
Hey, lovely.
Hola, encantadora.
Come, talk to me for a minute.
Ven, habla conmigo un minuto.
And I ate the food. It was good. I had the fish.
Y comí la comida. Estaba buena. Pedí pescado.
Yeah, it was pretty good. Yeah.
Sí, estaba bastante bueno. Sí.
Hi.
Hola.
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
Soy Lauren. La suplente de Kate.
Oh. Hey. Joey Tribbiani.
Oh. Hola. Joey Tribbiani.
I know. I'm a big fan of yours.
Lo sé. Soy muy fan tuya.
What?
¿Qué?
I used to, um, schedule my classes so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
Solía, eh, programar mis clases para poder ver al Dr. Drake Ramoray...
...on Days of our Lives.
...en "Days of our Lives".
Get out of here. Really?
No me digas. ¿En serio?
- Absolutely. - Huh.
- Absolutamente. - Vaya.
Oh, but then they went and dropped you down that elevator shaft.
Oh, pero luego te tiraron por el hueco del ascensor.
Yeah, they gave me the shaft, all right.
Sí, me dieron la patada, sí.
You're so funny.
Eres tan gracioso.
Listen, um, what are you doing after rehearsal?
Escucha, eh, ¿qué haces después del ensayo?
Do you wanna get a drink or something?
¿Quieres tomar algo o algo así?
Well, uh...
Bueno, eh...
Yeah. Yeah, sure. A drink sounds great.
Sí. Sí, claro. Tomar algo suena genial.
- Cool. I'll see you then. - Okay. All right.
- Genial. Te veo entonces. - Vale. De acuerdo.
All right. It's time to act, my talking props.
Muy bien. Es hora de actuar, mis utilería parlante.
- Hey. Hey.
- Oye. Oye.
Look, everybody. Look at my new dollhouse.
Miren, todos. Miren mi nueva casa de muñecas.
Wow.
Guau.
Ha, ha. Look, look.
Ja, ja. Miren, miren.
Hey, what's this?
Oye, ¿qué es esto?
Oh, okay. It's a slide instead of stairs. Look.
Oh, vale. Es un tobogán en lugar de escaleras. Miren.
Oh!
¡Oh!
Very interesting, Phoebe.
Muy interesante, Phoebe.
What's this?
¿Qué es esto?
The licorice room. You can eat all the furniture.
La habitación de regaliz. Puedes comerte todos los muebles.
And when guests come over, they can stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
Y cuando vengan invitados, pueden quedarse en la cama "Tootsie Roll-away".
This is the coolest house ever.
Esta es la casa más genial de la historia.
Hey. Does anyone want to join me in the Aroma Room?
Oye. ¿Alguien quiere unirse a mí en la Sala de Aromas?
All right. I would.
De acuerdo. Yo sí.
Hey, guys? Guys.
Oigan. Chicos, chicos.
Did you see my new china cabinet?
¿Vieron mi nuevo aparador?
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
Watch. Watch.
Miren. Miren.
Ooh. - And? And?
Ooh. - ¿Y? ¿Y?
Hey, my father's house does that.
Oye, la casa de mi padre hace eso.
Okay, how did it go? Tell me everything.
Vale, ¿cómo fue? Cuéntamelo todo.
Well, the movie was great...
Bueno, la película estuvo genial...
...dinner was great, and there's nothing like a cool, crisp New York evening.
...la cena estuvo genial, y no hay nada como una noche fresca y agradable en Nueva York.
Of course, I didn't get to enjoy any of that because Joanna's such a big dull dud.
Claro, no pude disfrutar nada de eso porque Joanna es un rollo.
Chandler is fantastic.
Chandler es fantástico.
- What? - Oh, God. You know how people just click?
- ¿Qué? - Dios mío. ¿Sabes cómo la gente conecta?
Like, he came by to pick me up. I opened the door, and it was just like, "click. "
Por ejemplo, vino a recogerme. Abrí la puerta y fue como, "clic".
- Did he tell you? - Well...
- ¿Te lo dijo? - Bueno...
Oh, and he's got such a good heart. Doesn't he have a good heart?
Oh, y tiene un corazón tan bueno. ¿No tiene un buen corazón?
Oh, I know. And he's so sweet.
Oh, lo sé. Y es tan dulce.
He said he'd call, so put him straight through.
Dijo que llamaría, así que ponlo directamente.
- Isn't this great? - Don't spoil it.
- ¿No es genial? - No lo arruines.
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
Vamos, cariño, no te vayas. ¿Por favor?
What do you say?
¿Qué dices?
Hello? Oh!
¿Hola? ¡Oh!
It's you. Just, uh... Just one sec.
Eres tú. Solo, eh... Solo un segundo.
I am going to take this call.
Voy a contestar esta llamada.
When I continue, I hope that there will appear on-stage...
Cuando continúe, espero que aparezca en el escenario...
...this magical thing that in the theater we call...
...esta cosa mágica que en el teatro llamamos...
...committing to the moment.
...comprometerse con el momento.
The guy's like a cartoon.
El tipo es como un dibujo animado.
What do you see in him, anyway?
¿Qué le ves, de todos modos?
He happens to be brilliant.
Resulta que es brillante.
Which is more than I can say for that sweater you're dating.
Que es más de lo que puedo decir de ese suéter que estás saliendo.
Hey, I'm not interested in her sweater.
Oye, no me interesa su suéter.
It's what's underneath her sweater that counts.
Es lo que hay debajo de su suéter lo que cuenta.
And besides, since, uh...
Y además, desde, eh...
Since when do you care who I'm going out with?
¿Desde cuándo te importa con quién salgo?
I don't care. Why? Do you want me to care?
No me importa. ¿Por qué? ¿Quieres que me importe?
Heh. Do you want me to want you to care?
¿Quieres que quiera que te importe?
Do you?
¿Tú sí?
What?
¿Qué?
Okay. I'm afraid to say this, but let's pick it up where we left off.
Ok. Me da miedo decir esto, pero retomemos donde lo dejamos.
Come on, baby, don't go. Please? What do you say?
Vamos, cariño, no te vayas. ¿Por favor? ¿Qué dices?
I've got no reason to stay.
No tengo ninguna razón para quedarme.
Stop.
Para.
Stop it. You must stop.
Para. Debes parar.
You are bad actors.
Son malos actores.
This is a terrible play.
Esta es una obra terrible.
I'll see you in the morning.
Nos vemos por la mañana.
I can't believe we go on in a week.
No puedo creer que estrenemos en una semana.
- Hey, it's gonna be all right. Hey.
- Oye, todo va a estar bien. Oye.
So since we're getting off early, do you want to go and paint mugs?
Así que, como salimos temprano, ¿quieres ir a pintar tazas?
What?
¿Qué?
You know, at that place I told you about last night?
¿Sabes? ¿Al lugar del que te hablé anoche?
Oh, yeah, with the mug-painting. Yeah.
Oh, sí, lo de pintar tazas. Sí.
- I was so listening to that. Ha, ha.
- Estaba escuchando atentamente. Ja, ja.
But, uh, you know what? I think I need to work on my stuff tonight.
Pero, eh, ¿sabes qué? Creo que necesito trabajar en mis cosas esta noche.
- Oh, okay. Okay.
- Oh, ok. Ok.
- I'll see you tomorrow. Okay.
- Te veo mañana. Ok.
- Okay. Ha, ha. Night.
- Ok. Ja, ja. Buenas noches.
Uh, are you okay?
Oye, ¿estás bien?
Yeah, I guess.
Sí, supongo.
Like, what are we gonna do about the scene, huh?
O sea, ¿qué vamos a hacer con la escena, eh?
I don't know.
No sé.
Well, um...
Bueno, um...
Maybe if it had more heat.
Quizás si tuviera más pasión.
Well, how do you mean?
Bueno, ¿a qué te refieres?
Well, Adrianne's looking for a reason to stay, right?
Bueno, Adrianne está buscando una razón para quedarse, ¿verdad?
Victor can't just kiss her. He's gotta...
Victor no puede solo besarla. Tiene que...
He's gotta really give her a reason, you know?
Tiene que darle una verdadera razón, ¿sabes?
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
Quizás podría meterle la lengua.
Or maybe...
O quizás...
Maybe he could grab her and lift her up.
Quizás podría levantarla.
Yeah, yeah. Then Adrianne, maybe she could wrap her legs around his waist.
Sí, sí. Entonces Adrianne, quizás podría enrollar sus piernas alrededor de su cintura.
And then she could rip off his shirt and kiss his chest and his stomach.
Y entonces ella podría arrancarle la camisa y besarle el pecho y el estómago.
And then he could use his teeth, his teeth, to undo her dress and...
Y entonces él podría usar sus dientes, sus dientes, para desabrocharle el vestido y...
And bite her.
Y morderla.
And then right when the scene ends, he could take her...
Y justo cuando la escena termina, él podría llevarla...
...with this raw, animal...
...con esa cruda, animal...
Something like that?
¿Algo así?
Yeah, that's pretty much what I had in mind.
Sí, eso es básicamente lo que tenía en mente.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Sí. - Sí.
- Hi. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
It's a little early to be drinking.
Es un poco temprano para beber.
Things, uh, finally happened with Kate.
Las cosas, eh, finalmente pasaron con Kate.
- Oh. That's great. - You're kidding. That's great.
- Oh. Eso es genial. - ¿Me estás bromeando? Eso es genial.
Oh, it was so amazing.
Oh, fue tan increíble.
After the lovemaking...
Después del acto sexual...
Oh, my.
Oh, vaya.
- I just watched her sleep for, like, hours.
- Solo la miré dormir durante, como, horas.
- Just breathing in... Huh.
- Solo respirando... Eh.
...and breathing out.
...y exhalando.
And I knew she was dreaming because her eyes kept going like this:
Y sabía que estaba soñando porque sus ojos seguían haciendo esto:
I'm telling you, Joanna's got it all wrong, okay?
Te digo, Joanna lo tiene todo mal, ¿okay?
All I said was, "This was fun. Let's do it again sometime.
Todo lo que dije fue: "Esto fue divertido. Hagámoslo de nuevo alguna vez.
I'll give you a call. "
Te llamaré."
Oh, gee...
Oh, caray...
I wonder why she thinks you're going to call her?
Me pregunto por qué piensa que la vas a llamar.
That's what you say at the end of a date.
Eso es lo que dices al final de una cita.
You can't just say, "Nice to meet you. Good night"?
¿No puedes simplemente decir: "Encantado de conocerte. Buenas noches"?
To her face?
¿En su cara?
It's the end of the date, I'm standing there...
Es el final de la cita, estoy ahí parado...
...she's waiting for me to say I'll call her...
...ella está esperando que diga que la llamaré...
...and it just, you know, comes out. I can't help it.
...y simplemente, ya sabes, se me escapa. No puedo evitarlo.
It's a compulsion.
Es una compulsión.
Come on, Rach, when a guy says he's gonna call...
Vamos, Rach, cuando un chico dice que va a llamar...
...it doesn't mean he's going to call.
...no significa que vaya a llamar.
This never happened to you?
¿Nunca te ha pasado esto?
Well, they always called.
Bueno, siempre llamaban.
Bite me.
Muerde.
- Did he call? - No, sorry.
- ¿Te llamó? - No, lo siento.
Why? Why? He said he'd call. Why hasn't he called?
¿Por qué? ¿Por qué? Dijo que llamaría. ¿Por qué no ha llamado?
Maybe he's intimidated by really smart, strong, successful women.
Quizás se siente intimidado por mujeres muy inteligentes, fuertes y exitosas.
Sophie, will you please climb out of my butt.
Sophie, ¿puedes por favor dejar de meterme las narices en todo?
- Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why? - Okay, okay.
- ¿Por qué no ha llamado, Rachel? ¿Por qué? - Está bien, está bien.
Um, well, uh, maybe he feels awkward because you are my boss.
Mmm, bueno, eh, quizás se siente incómodo porque tú eres mi jefa.
Awkward? Why should he feel awkward?
¿Incómodo? ¿Por qué debería sentirse incómodo?
The only person that should feel awkward is you.
La única persona que debería sentirse incómoda eres tú.
You didn't tell him not to call me?
¿No le dijiste que no me llamara?
If you're uncomfortable with your friend dating someone you work for...
Si te sientes incómoda con que tu amiga salga con alguien para quien trabajas...
...there are always ways to fix that.
...siempre hay maneras de arreglar eso.
Uh...
Eh...
Call her. Call her now.
Llamala. Llamala ahora.
Multiple, so many paper cuts.
Múltiples, tantos cortes de papel.
"Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why? Why?
"¿Por qué no ha llamado, Rachel? ¿Por qué? ¿Por qué?
I don't understand. He said he'd call. "
No entiendo. Dijo que llamaría."
Chandler, I'm telling you, she's flipped out. She's gone crazy.
Chandler, te digo que se ha vuelto loca. Se ha vuelto loca.
Oh. Well, give me the phone, then.
Oh. Bueno, dame el teléfono, entonces.
This isn't funny. She thinks it's my fault you haven't called her.
Esto no es gracioso. Cree que es mi culpa que no la hayas llamado.
You have to call her.
Tienes que llamarla.
Look, you can't call somebody after this long just to say:
Mira, no puedes llamar a alguien después de tanto tiempo solo para decir:
"In case you didn't notice, I don't like you. "
"Por si no te diste cuenta, no me caes bien."
Then you're gonna have to take her out again.
Entonces tendrás que volver a invitarla a salir.
No. She's really dull, and she gets this...
No. Es muy aburrida y se le pone esa...
...gross mascara-goop thing in the corner of her eye.
...cosa de rímel pegajoso en la comisura del ojo.
I don't care. I don't care.
No me importa. No me importa.
You'll take her out again and end it...
La volverás a invitar a salir y terminarás...
...and end it in a way that she knows it's actually ended.
...y terminarás de una manera que ella sepa que realmente ha terminado.
And I don't care how hard it is for you. Do not tell her you'll call her again.
Y no me importa lo difícil que sea para ti. No le digas que la llamarás de nuevo.
All right, fine.
Está bien, de acuerdo.
But it's just a lunch date. From now on, I get my own dates.
Pero es solo una cita para almorzar. De ahora en adelante, consigo mis propias citas.
I don't want you setting me up with anybody again.
No quiero que me presentes a nadie más.
That's fine.
Está bien.
- That's just a lot of big talk, you know. - I know.
- Eso es solo mucha labia, ¿sabes? - Lo sé.
Mon?
¿Mon?
I'm in the shower.
Estoy en la ducha.
Aah! Fire. There's a fire. Fire.
¡Aah! Fuego. Hay fuego. Fuego.
- Hey. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
So I, uh, talked to Lauren. I kind of told her how things were with us.
Así que, eh, hablé con Lauren. Le conté cómo estaban las cosas entre nosotros.
Did you, uh...? Did you talk to Marshall?
¿Hablaste, eh...? ¿Hablaste con Marshall?
About what?
¿Sobre qué?
Ha, ha. You know, about what happened with us.
Ja, ja. Sabes, sobre lo que pasó entre nosotros.
No.
And there's really no reason why he should find out.
Y realmente no hay razón por la que él deba enterarse.
So, uh, let's not make a big deal out of it, okay?
Así que, eh, no hagamos un gran problema de esto, ¿de acuerdo?
What are you talking about?
¿De qué estás hablando?
It was a big deal.
Fue un gran problema.
I mean, come on, you can't tell me last night didn't mean something to you.
Quiero decir, vamos, no puedes decirme que anoche no significó algo para ti.
I was there. You're not that good an actress.
Estuve allí. No eres tan buena actriz.
Look.
Mira.
Um, I was... I was just caught up in the moment.
Mmm, solo me dejé llevar por el momento.
That's all it was.
Eso fue todo.
Joey, I'm sorry you feel bad...
Joey, lamento que te sientas mal...
...but haven't you ever slept with a woman where it meant more to her than to you?
...pero ¿nunca te has acostado con una mujer donde significó más para ella que para ti?
No.
- Hi, Kate. Hi, Lauren.
- Hola, Kate. Hola, Lauren.
Hi, Lauren.
Hola, Lauren.
Hi, pig.
Hola, cerdita.
Sorry I, uh... I scared you in there.
Perdón si, eh... te asusté ahí.
Oh, that's okay.
Oh, no pasa nada.
By the way...
Por cierto...
...I was just checking the shower massager.
...solo estaba revisando el masajeador de ducha.
Yeah.
Sí.
Hey.
Oye.
I tried to reach you at work.
Intenté contactarte en el trabajo.
There's been a fire.
Ha habido un incendio.
What? Oh, my... Oh, my God.
¿Qué? Oh, Dios... Dios mío.
What happened?
¿Qué pasó?
Well, we believe it originated here...
Bueno, creemos que se originó aquí...
...in the Aroma Room.
...en el Cuarto del Aroma.
All right, did everyone get out okay?
Bien, ¿todos salieron bien?
Well, the giraffe's okay and so is the pirate.
Bueno, la jirafa está bien y el pirata también.
- What is this? - No, Phoebe, don't look.
- ¿Qué es esto? - No, Phoebe, no mires.
You don't want to see what's under there.
No quieres ver lo que hay debajo.
The foster puppets.
Los títeres de acogida.
It's not a big deal.
No es gran cosa.
It's just... It's right here, and it's all the time.
Es solo que... está aquí mismo, y es todo el tiempo.
Well, thanks again for lunch.
Bueno, gracias de nuevo por el almuerzo.
- Yes, this was pleasant. - It was, wasn't it?
- Sí, fue agradable. - ¿Verdad que sí?
- The food there was great. - Wasn't it?
- La comida estuvo genial. - ¿Verdad que sí?
So take care.
Cuídate entonces.
You too.
A ti también.
This was great. I'll give you a call. We should do it again.
Esto fue genial. Te llamaré. Deberíamos repetirlo.
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
Genial. Tengo ganas.
- Rachel, any messages? Sophie's desk.
- Rachel, ¿algún mensaje? El escritorio de Sophie.
Chandler. Are you gonna call her?
Chandler. ¿Vas a llamarla?
- No. - Chandler.
Look, I'm sorry, okay? I'm weak and pathetic and sorry.
Mira, lo siento, ¿vale? Soy débil y patético y lo siento.
Okay, you are gonna tell her. You're gonna tell her now.
Está bien, vas a decírselo. Vas a decírselo ahora.
Ow, I'm not gonna call you.
Ay, no te voy a llamar.
What?
¿Qué?
I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
I'm sorry that I said I was going to when I'm not.
Lamento haber dicho que lo haría cuando no lo voy a hacer.
Ugh. Look, this has nothing to do with you.
Ugh. Mira, esto no tiene nada que ver contigo.
And this isn't Rachel's fault. It's me.
Y esto no es culpa de Rachel. Soy yo.
I have serious, serious problems when it comes to women.
Tengo serios, serios problemas con las mujeres.
I have issues with commitment, intimacy...
Tengo problemas con el compromiso, la intimidad...
...mascara goop.
...restos de rímel.
And I'm really sorry. It's just that this is not... This isn't gonna work out.
Y lo siento mucho. Es solo que esto no... Esto no va a funcionar.
Well, this isn't how I was hoping this would end...
Bueno, no esperaba que esto terminara así...
...but I guess I have to appreciate your honesty.
...pero supongo que tengo que apreciar tu honestidad.
Yeah, okay.
Sí, está bien.
So...
Así que...
Well, this is great. I'll give you a call. We should do it again sometime.
Bueno, esto es genial. Te llamaré. Deberíamos repetir alguna vez.
Wha... So anyway, Beth, what I'm saying is...
¿Qué... Entonces, Beth, lo que quiero decir es...
...I should have considered your feelings before I went home with you that night.
...debería haber considerado tus sentimientos antes de irme a casa contigo esa noche.
I've, uh...
Yo, eh...
I've recently learned what it's like to be on your side of it...
Recientemente he aprendido cómo es estar de tu lado...
...and I'm sorry.
...y lo siento.
So do you think you can forgive me?
Entonces, ¿crees que puedes perdonarme?
Great. Thanks.
Genial. Gracias.
Okay. Bye.
Está bien. Adiós.
Whoo.
Hello, Jennifer?
¿Hola, Jennifer?
Oh, hi, Mrs. Laurio. Is Jennifer there?
Oh, hola, Sra. Laurio. ¿Está Jennifer?
Oh, she's not home, huh?
Oh, ¿no está en casa, eh?
Well, uh, actually I kind of need to talk to you too.
Bueno, eh, en realidad yo también necesito hablar contigo.