Everybody. Shh. Uh, Central Perk is proud to present...
Todos. Shh. Uh, Central Perk se enorgullece de presentar...
...the music of Miss Phoebe Buffay.
...la música de la señorita Phoebe Buffay.
PHOEBE: Thanks.
PHOEBE: Gracias.
Hi. Um, I wanna start with a song that's about that moment...
Hola. Um, quiero empezar con una canción que trata sobre ese momento...
...when you suddenly realize what life is really all about.
...en que de repente te das cuenta de lo que realmente es la vida.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, allá vamos.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Okay. Muchas gracias.
CHANDLER: What...?
CHANDLER: ¿Qué...?
Oh, great. This is just...
Oh, genial. Esto es justo...
This is so cool, you guys.
Esto es tan genial, chicos.
The entire city's blacked out.
Toda la ciudad está a oscuras.
Mom says it's Manhattan, Brooklyn and Queens...
Mamá dice que es Manhattan, Brooklyn y Queens...
...and doesn't know when it'll be back on.
...y no sabe cuándo volverá la luz.
PHOEBE: Wow. RACHEL: You guys, this is big.
PHOEBE: Guau. RACHEL: Chicos, esto es grande.
Pants and a sweater. Why, Mom?
Pantalones y un suéter. ¿Por qué, mamá?
Who will I meet in a blackout?
¿A quién voy a conocer en un apagón?
Power-company guys? Eligible looters?
¿Chicos de la compañía eléctrica? ¿Ladrón elegible?
Can we talk about this later? Okay.
¿Podemos hablar de esto después? Okay.
Can I borrow the phone?
¿Puedo tomar prestado el teléfono?
I wanna call my apartment and check on my grandma.
Quiero llamar a mi apartamento y ver cómo está mi abuela.
What's my number?
¿Cuál es mi número?
I never call me.
Nunca me llamo.
CHANDLER [THINKING]: Oh, my God. It's her.
CHANDLER [PENSANDO]: Dios mío. Es ella.
It's that Victoria Secret model.
Es esa modelo de Victoria Secret.
Something Goodacre.
Algo de Goodacre.
Hi, Mom, it's Jill.
Hola, mamá, soy Jill.
She's right. It's Jill. Jill Goodacre.
Tiene razón. Es Jill. Jill Goodacre.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
I am trapped in an ATM vestibule with Jill Goodacre.
Estoy atrapado en el vestíbulo de un cajero automático con Jill Goodacre.
Is it a vestibule? Maybe it's an atrium?
¿Es un vestíbulo? ¿Quizás es un atrio?
Yeah, that is the part to focus on, you idiot.
Sí, esa es la parte en la que debes concentrarte, idiota.
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just stuck at the bank in an ATM vestibule.
Sí, estoy bien. Solo estoy atascado en el banco en el vestíbulo de un cajero automático.
Jill says vestibule...
Jill dice vestíbulo...
...I'm going with vestibule.
...yo me quedo con vestíbulo.
JILL: I'm fine.
JILL: Estoy bien.
No, I'm not alone.
No, no estoy sola.
I don't know. Some guy.
No sé. Algún tipo.
Oh, some guy. I am some guy.
Oh, algún tipo. Yo soy algún tipo.
Hey, Jill, I saw you with some guy last night.
Oye, Jill, te vi con algún tipo anoche.
Yes, he was some guy.
Sí, él era algún tipo.
JOEY: Hey, everyone.
JOEY: Hola a todos.
Officiating at tonight's blackout is Rabbi Tribbiani.
Oficiando en el apagón de esta noche está el Rabino Tribbiani.
Chandler's old roommate was Jewish, and these are the only candles we have...
El antiguo compañero de cuarto de Chandler era judío, y estas son las únicas velas que tenemos...
...so happy Hanukkah.
...así que feliz Janucá.
PHOEBE: Ooh, look. Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
PHOEBE: Ooh, mira. El Chico Feo y Desnudo encendió un montón de velas.
ALL: Ooh.
TODOS: Ooh.
Oh!
¡Oh!
Ooh. That had to hurt.
Ooh. Eso debió doler.
CHANDLER [THINKING]: All right, all right. It's been 14 and a half minutes...
CHANDLER [PENSANDO]: Muy bien, muy bien. Han pasado 14 minutos y medio...
...and you still haven't said one word. Oh, God.
...y todavía no has dicho una palabra. Oh, Dios.
Do something. Just make contact. Smile.
[ERROR API]
There you go.
Ahí tienes.
You're definitely scaring her.
[ERROR API]
Uh, would you like to call somebody?
Yeah, about 300 guys I went to high school with.
[ERROR API]
Yeah, thanks.
[PHONE RINGS]
[SUENA EL TELÉFONO]
Hello?
¿Hola?
- It's me. - It's Chandler.
[ERROR API]
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[ERROR API]
[MUMBLING] I'm stuck in an ATM vestibule...
...with Jill Goodacre.
[ERROR API]
What?
¿Qué?
[MUMBLING] I'm stuck...
[ERROR API]
...in an ATM vestibule...
...with Jill Goodacre.
[ERROR API]
I have no idea what you said.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Put Joey on the phone.
[ERROR API]
What's up, man?
[MUMBLING] I'm stuck...
[ERROR API]
...in an ATM vestibule...
...with Jill Goodacre.
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
He's trapped in an ATM vestibule with Jill Goodacre.
[ERROR API]
Chandler, listen.
[MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY]
[ERROR API]
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Yeah, like that thought never entered my mind.
RACHEL: Come on, somebody.
[ERROR API]
MONICA: I'll go. I'll go.
Okay, um, senior year of college, on a pool table.
[ERROR API]
JOEY: Ooh. - Pool table?
That's my sister.
[ERROR API]
Okay, okay. My weirdest place would have to be...
...the women's room on the second floor of the New York City Public Library.
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God. What were you doing in a library?
- Pheebs, what about you? - Oh, um, Milwaukee.
[ERROR API]
Uh, Ross?
Eh, ¿Ross?
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SE ACLARA LA GARGANTA]
Disneyland, 1989. "It's a small world after all."
[ERROR API]
No way.
De ninguna manera.
The, uh, ride broke down...
[ERROR API]
...so Carol and I went behind a couple of those mechanical Dutch children.
They fixed the ride, and we were asked never to return to the Magic Kingdom.
[ERROR API]
Ooh. Rachel?
I already went.
[ERROR API]
- You did not go. - Yes, I did.
MONICA: Tell us. Come on.
[ERROR API]
All right, uh, the weirdest place would have to be...
...the foot of the bed.
[ERROR API]
- Step back. - We have a winner.
- Hazte para atrás. - Tenemos un ganador.
I've never had a relationship with that kind of passion.
Nunca he tenido una relación con esa clase de pasión.
Where you have to have somebody right there in the middle of a theme park.
Donde tienes que tener a alguien justo ahí en medio de un parque temático.
It was the only thing to do there that didn't have a line.
Era lo único que se podía hacer allí que no tuviera fila.
Well, Barry wouldn't even kiss me on a miniature-golf course.
Bueno, Barry ni siquiera me besaba en un campo de minigolf.
- Come on. - No.
- Vamos. - No.
He said we were holding up the people behind us.
Dijo que estábamos retrasando a la gente detrás de nosotros.
And you didn't marry him because?
¿Y no te casaste con él porque?
Do you think there are people that go through life...
¿Crees que hay gente que pasa por la vida...
...never having that kind of?
...sin tener nunca esa clase de?
- Probably. - Really?
- Probablemente. - ¿En serio?
I'll tell you something. Passion is way overrated.
Te digo algo. La pasión está muy sobrevalorada.
- Yeah, right. - It is.
- Sí, claro. - Lo está.
Eventually, it kind of burns out.
Eventualmente, como que se apaga.
But hopefully what you're left with is trust and security and, uh...
Pero esperemos que lo que te quede sea confianza y seguridad y, eh...
In my ex-wife's case, lesbianism.
En el caso de mi exmujer, lesbianismo.
For all those people who miss out on that, uh, passion thing...
Para toda esa gente que se pierde esa, eh, cosa de la pasión...
...there's other good stuff.
...hay otras cosas buenas.
Okay.
But, um, I don't think that'll be you.
Pero, um, no creo que ese seas tú.
- You don't? - Mm-mm.
- ¿No crees? - Mm-mm.
See, I see, uh...
Mira, veo, eh...
...big passion in your future.
...mucha pasión en tu futuro.
- Really? - Mm-hm.
- ¿En serio? - Mm-hm.
- You do? - I do.
- ¿Tú crees? - Yo sí.
Ross, you're so great.
Ross, eres genial.
ROSS: Ah.
It's never gonna happen.
Nunca va a pasar.
- What? - You and Rachel.
- ¿Qué? - Tú y Rachel.
[CHUCKLES]
[RÍE]
[STUTTERS]
[BALBUCEA]
Why not?
¿Por qué no?
Because you waited too long to make your move...
Porque esperaste demasiado para dar tu paso...
...and now you're in the "Friend Zone."
...y ahora estás en la "Zona de Amigos".
No, no, no. I'm not in the Zone.
No, no, no. No estoy en la Zona.
No, Ross. You're mayor of the Zone.
No, Ross. Eres el alcalde de la Zona.
Look, I'm taking my time, all right?
Mira, me estoy tomando mi tiempo, ¿de acuerdo?
I'm laying the groundwork.
Estoy sentando las bases.
Every day I get a little bit closer to, uh...
Cada día me acerco un poco más a, eh...
Priesthood.
El sacerdocio.
Ross, I'm telling you, she has no idea what you're thinking.
Ross, te digo, ella no tiene idea de lo que estás pensando.
If you don't ask her out soon, you'll end up stuck in the Zone forever.
Si no la invitas a salir pronto, terminarás atrapado en la Zona para siempre.
I will, I will.
Lo haré, lo haré.
I'm waiting for the, uh, right moment.
Estoy esperando el, eh, momento adecuado.
What?
¿Qué?
- What, now? - Yeah.
- ¿Qué, ahora? - Sí.
What's messing you up? The wine?
¿Qué te está afectando? ¿El vino?
The candles? The moonlight? Huh?
¿Las velas? ¿La luz de la luna? ¿Eh?
You gotta go up to her and say, "Look, Rachel, I think..."
Tienes que ir hacia ella y decir: "Mira, Rachel, creo..."
- Shh! - Shh!
- ¡Shh! - ¡Shh!
- What are we shushing? - We're shushing...
- ¿De qué nos callamos? - Nos callamos...
...because we're trying to hear something.
...porque intentamos oír algo.
- What? - Uh, don't you hear that?
- ¿Qué? - Eh, ¿no oyes eso?
Ah.
- See? - Huh.
- ¿Ves? - Mmm.
- Would you like some gum? - Oh. Is it sugarless?
- ¿Quieres chicle? - Oh. ¿Es sin azúcar?
- Uh, sorry, it's not. - Then, no, thanks.
- Eh, lo siento, no lo es. - Entonces, no, gracias.
CHANDLER [THINKING]: What the hell was that?
CHANDLER [PENSANDO]: ¿Qué demonios fue eso?
Mental note: If Jill Goodacre offers you gum, you take it.
Nota mental: Si Jill Goodacre te ofrece chicle, lo aceptas.
If she offers you mangled animal carcass, you take it.
Si te ofrece un cadáver de animal mutilado, lo aceptas.
PHOEBE [SINGING]: New York City has no power
PHOEBE [CANTANDO]: La ciudad de Nueva York no tiene luz
And the milk is getting sour
Y la leche se está agrietando
But to me it is not scary
Pero para mí no es aterrador
'Cause I stay away from dairy
Porque me mantengo alejada de los lácteos
La-la La-la-la-la-la
- Here goes. - You'll do it?
- Allá voy. - ¿Lo harás?
- I'll do it. - Want help?
- Lo haré. - ¿Quieres ayuda?
You come out there, you're a dead man.
Si sales ahí, estás muerto.
Ross, Ross.
Good luck, man.
Suerte, amigo.
Thanks.
Gracias.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Vale. - Vale.
JOEY: Where you going? MONICA: Outside.
JOEY: ¿A dónde vas? MONICA: Afuera.
You can't go out there.
No puedes salir ahí.
- Why not? - Because of, uh, the reason.
- ¿Por qué no? - Por, eh, la razón.
And that would be?
¿Y cuál sería?
I, uh... I can't tell you.
Yo, eh... no puedo decírtelo.
What's going on?
¿Qué está pasando?
Okay, listen. You gotta promise you'll never, ever tell Ross that I told you.
Ok, escucha. Tienes que prometerme que nunca, jamás le dirás a Ross que te lo dije.
- About what? - He's planning your birthday party.
- ¿Sobre qué? - Él te está planeando la fiesta de cumpleaños.
Oh, my God. I love him.
Dios mío. Lo quiero.
You better act surprised.
Será mejor que finjas sorpresa.
- About what? - My surprise party.
- ¿Sobre qué? - Mi fiesta sorpresa.
- What surprise party? - Oh, stop it. Joey already told me.
- ¿Qué fiesta sorpresa? - Oh, para ya. Joey ya me lo dijo.
Well, he didn't tell me.
Bueno, a mí no me lo dijo.
Don't look at me. This is Ross' thing.
No me mires. Esto es cosa de Ross.
This is so typical. I'm always the last to know everything.
Esto es tan típico. Siempre soy la última en enterarme de todo.
- You are not. We tell you stuff. - Uh-huh.
- No es verdad. Te contamos cosas. - Ajá.
I was the last one to know when Chandler got bit by the peacock at the zoo.
Fui la última en enterarme cuando a Chandler lo mordió el pavo real en el zoológico.
I was the last to know you had a crush on Joey when he was moving in.
Fui la última en enterarme de que te gustaba Joey cuando se estaba mudando.
What?
¿Qué?
Oh. Looks like I was second to last.
Oh. Parece que fui la penúltima.
It's so nice.
Es muy bonito.
Hey, I have a question.
Oye, tengo una pregunta.
Uh, actually, it's not so much a question...
Eh, en realidad, no es tanto una pregunta...
...it's more of a general wondering...
...es más bien una duda general...
...ment.
...sobre algo.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Vale. - Vale.
Here goes.
Allá voy.
Um, well, for a while now, I've been wanting to, um...
Um, bueno, desde hace un tiempo, he querido, um...
- Oh. - Yes, that's right.
- Oh. - Sí, así es.
Look at that little kitty.
Mira ese gatito.
What?
¿Qué?
[YELLS]
[GRITA]
ALL [SINGING]: I'm on the top of the world Looking down on creation
TODOS [CANTANDO]: Estoy en la cima del mundo Mirando la creación
And the only explanation I can find
Y la única explicación que puedo encontrar
Is the love that I found Ever since you've been around
Es el amor que encontré Desde que estás aquí
All right, this is just Bactine. It won't hurt.
Está bien, esto es solo Bactine. No dolerá.
Ow. Ow.
Ay. Ay.
Sorry, that was wax.
Perdón, era cera.
Poor little Tootie's scared. We should find his owner.
Pobre Tootie está asustado. Deberíamos encontrar a su dueño.
Why not put "poor little Tootie" in the hall?
¿Por qué no poner al "pobre Tootie" en el pasillo?
During a blackout? She'll get trampled.
¿Durante un apagón? La pisotearán.
Yeah?
¿Sí?
You know, on second thought, gum would be perfection.
Sabes, pensándolo bien, el chicle sería la perfección.
CHANDLER [THINKING]: Gum would be perfection?
CHANDLER [PENSANDO]: ¿El chicle sería la perfección?
Gum would be perfection.
El chicle sería la perfección.
Could've said, "Gum would be nice." "I'll have a stick." But, no.
Pudo haber dicho: "El chicle estaría bien". "Me daré un chicle". Pero no.
For me, gum is perfection.
Para mí, el chicle es la perfección.
I loathe myself.
Me odio a mí mismo.
Oh, no, the Mellons. They hate all living things, right?
Oh, no, los Mellon. Odian a todos los seres vivos, ¿verdad?
PHOEBE: Oh.
Hi. We just found this cat...
Hola. Acabamos de encontrar este gato...
...and we're looking for the owner.
...y estamos buscando al dueño.
Um, yeah, it's, uh... It's mine.
Eh, sí, es... Es mío.
He seems to hate you. Are you sure?
Parece que te odia. ¿Estás seguro?
Yeah. It's my cat. Give me my cat.
Sí. Es mi gato. Devuélveme mi gato.
Wait a minute. What's his name?
Espera un minuto. ¿Cómo se llama?
Um, Bob... Buttons.
Eh, Bob... Buttons.
- Bob Buttons? - Uh-huh.
- ¿Bob Buttons? - Ajá.
Bob Buttons. Here, Bob Buttons.
Bob Buttons. Aquí, Bob Buttons.
Oh!
¡Oh!
You are a very bad man.
Eres un hombre muy malo.
You owe me a cat.
Me debes un gato.
RACHEL: Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
RACHEL: Aquí, gatito, gatito, gatito.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Aquí, gatito, gatito.
Where did you go, little kitty, kitty, kitty?
¿A dónde fuiste, gatito, gatito, gatito?
Kitty, kitty, kitty. Come here, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty...
Gatito, gatito, gatito. Ven aquí, gatito, gatito, gatito, gatito, gatito...
Hi.
Hola.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
[HABLA EN ITALIANO]
Wow.
Guau.
Come on, lucky sixes.
Vamos, seis suertudos.
Everybody, this is Paolo.
Todos, este es Paolo.
Paolo, I want you to meet my friends.
Paolo, quiero que conozcas a mis amigos.
- This is Monica... - Hi.
- Esta es Monica... - Hola.
...and Joey... MONICA: Hi.
...y Joey... MONICA: Hola.
...and Ross. MONICA: Hi.
...y Ross. MONICA: Hola.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
[HABLA EN ITALIANO]
Ha, ha. He doesn't speak much English.
Ja, ja. No habla mucho inglés.
Monopoly.
Look at that.
Mira eso.
So, uh...
Entonces, eh...
Where did, uh, Paolo come from?
¿De dónde vino, eh, Paolo?
Italy, I think. Heh.
Italia, creo. Je.
No, I mean tonight, in the building? Suddenly into our lives?
No, me refiero a esta noche, ¿en el edificio? ¿De repente en nuestras vidas?
The cat turned out to be Paolo's cat. Isn't that funny?
El gato resultó ser el gato de Paolo. ¿No es gracioso?
That is funny. And Rachel keeps touching him.
Es gracioso. Y Rachel no deja de tocarlo.
I looked all over the building and I couldn't find the kitty anywhere.
Busqué por todo el edificio y no pude encontrar al gatito en ninguna parte.
Oh, I found him. It was Paolo's cat.
Oh, lo encontré. Era el gato de Paolo.
Ah. Well, there you go. Last to know again.
Ah. Bueno, ahí lo tienes. La última en enterarse, de nuevo.
And I'm guessing, since nobody told me, this is Paolo?
Y supongo, como nadie me dijo, ¿este es Paolo?
Oh. Paolo, this is Phoebe.
Oh. Paolo, esta es Phoebe.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
[HABLA EN ITALIANO]
You betcha.
Claro que sí.
CHANDLER [THINKING]: All right. Okay. What next?
CHANDLER [PENSANDO]: Bien. De acuerdo. ¿Qué sigue?
Blow a bubble. A bubble's good.
Soplar una burbuja. Una burbuja es buena.
It's got a, uh, boyish charm. It's impish.
Tiene, eh, un encanto juvenil. Es travieso.
Here we go.
Aquí vamos.
Nice going, imp.
Bien hecho, travieso.
Okay. It's okay. All I need to do is...
Está bien. Está bien. Lo único que tengo que hacer es...
...reach over and put it back in my mouth.
...estirarme y volver a ponérmela en la boca.
Good save. We're back on track and I'm...
Buen salvavidas. Estamos de vuelta en marcha y estoy...
...chewing someone else's gum.
...masticando el chicle de otra persona.
This is not my gum.
Este no es mi chicle.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Dios mío. Dios mío.
And now you're choking.
Y ahora te estás ahogando.
Are you all right?
¿Estás bien?
Oh, my God. You're choking.
Dios mío. Te estás ahogando.
Better?
¿Mejor?
Yes.
Sí.
Thank you. That was...
Gracias. Eso fue...
That was...
Eso fue...
Perfection?
¿Perfección?
[SPEAKING IN ITALIAN]
[HABLANDO EN ITALIANO]
[MIMICKING PAOLO]
[IMITANDO A PAOLO]
[RACHEL LAUGHS]
[RACHEL SE RÍE]
What'd he say that was so funny?
¿Qué dijo que fue tan gracioso?
I have absolutely no idea.
No tengo ni idea.
That's classic.
Eso es clásico.
My God, you guys. What am I doing?
Dios mío, chicos. ¿Qué estoy haciendo?
This is so un-me.
Esto es tan poco yo.
If you want, I'll do it.
Si quieres, lo hago yo.
I know. I just wanna bite his bottom lip.
Lo sé. Solo quiero morderle el labio inferior.
But I won't.
Pero no lo haré.
God. The first time he smiled at me...
Dios. La primera vez que me sonrió...
...those three seconds were more exciting than three weeks in Bermuda with Barry.
...esos tres segundos fueron más emocionantes que tres semanas en Bermuda con Barry.
Did you rent mopeds?
¿Alquilaron ciclomotores?
Because I've heard...
Porque he oído...
Oh, it's not about that right now. Okay.
Oh, no se trata de eso ahora mismo. De acuerdo.
I know it's totally superficial, and we have nothing in common...
Sé que es totalmente superficial, y no tenemos nada en común...
...and we don't even speak the same language...
...y ni siquiera hablamos el mismo idioma...
...but, God.
...pero, Dios.
Paolo, hi.
Paolo, hola.
- Ross. - Listen, uh...
- Ross. - Escucha, eh...
Listen, um, heh, something you should, uh, know.
Oye, um, je, algo que deberías, eh, saber.
Rachel and I are...
Rachel y yo estamos...
We're kind of a thing.
Somos algo.
- Thing? - Thing. Yes, thing.
- ¿Algo? - Sí, algo.
- You have the sex? - No.
- ¿Tienen sexo? - No.
No, no. Um, technically, the sex is not being had. But that's, uh...
No, no. Um, técnicamente, no se está teniendo sexo. Pero eso es, eh...
That's not the point.
Ese no es el punto.
The point is that, uh, Rachel and I should be, uh...
El punto es que, eh, Rachel y yo deberíamos, eh...
Well, Rachel and I should be together.
Bueno, Rachel y yo deberíamos estar juntos.
And if you get in the, uh...
Y si te interpones en el, eh...
- In bed? - No.
- ¿En la cama? - No.
Ha. No, not where I was going.
Ja. No, no era por ahí por donde iba.
If you get in the way of us becoming a thing...
Si te interpones en que seamos algo...
...then, uh, I would be, well, very sad.
...entonces, eh, estaría, bueno, muy triste.
Oh.
So do you, um?
Entonces, ¿tú, um?
[BOTH SPEAK IN ITALIAN]
[AMBOS HABLAN EN ITALIANO]
- You do know a little English? - Little.
- ¿Sabes un poco de inglés? - Poco.
Do you know the word crap-weasel?
¿Sabes la palabra 'crap-weasel'?
No? That's funny, you are a huge crap-weasel.
¿No? Qué gracioso, eres un gran 'crap-weasel'.
Chandler, we've been here for an hour doing this. Watch, it's easy.
Chandler, hemos estado aquí una hora haciendo esto. Mira, es fácil.
- Ready? - Mm-hm.
- ¿Listo? - Mm-hm.
Okay? Now try it.
¿Okay? Ahora inténtalo.
You gotta whip it.
Tienes que moverla.
Look, look. The last candle's about to burn out.
Mira, mira. La última vela está a punto de apagarse.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
Diez, nueve, ocho, siete...
...minus 46, minus 47, minus 48...
...menos 46, menos 47, menos 48...
ROSS: Thank you. MONICA: Thanks.
ROSS: Gracias. MONICA: Gracias.
ROSS: Kind of spooky without any lights.
ROSS: Da un poco de miedo sin luces.
[JOEY LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[JOEY RÍE MANIACOMENTE]
[ALL LAUGH MANIACALLY]
[TODOS RÍEN MANIACOMENTE]
ROSS: Okay, guys, I have the definitive one.
ROSS: Okay, chicos, tengo la definitiva.
[ROSS LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[ROSS RÍE MANIACOMENTE]
[GROANS]
[GEMIDO]
Uh, Ross...
Eh, Ross...
This probably isn't the best time to bring it up...
Probablemente no sea el mejor momento para decirlo...
...but you have to throw a party for Monica.
...pero tienes que organizar una fiesta para Monica.
- This has been fun. - Yes.
- Esto ha sido divertido. - Sí.
Yes. Thanks for, uh, letting me use your phone...
Sí. Gracias por, eh, dejarme usar tu teléfono...
...and for saving my life.
...y por salvarme la vida.
Well, goodbye, Chandler.
Bueno, adiós, Chandler.
I had a great blackout.
Tuve un apagón genial.
See you.
Nos vemos.
Hi. Um, I'm account number 7143457. And I don't know if you got any of that...
Hola. Um, soy el número de cuenta 7143457. Y no sé si recibieron algo de eso...
...but I would really like a copy of the tape.
...pero me gustaría mucho una copia de la cinta.