NARRATOR: Previously on Friends:
NARRADOR: Anteriormente en Friends:
- Excuse me, miss. - It's Phoebe.
- Disculpe, señorita. - Soy Phoebe.
- Will that be all? CHANDLER: They're twins.
- ¿Será todo? CHANDLER: Son gemelas.
Phoebe's Phoebe. Ursula's hot.
Phoebe es Phoebe. Ursula es sexy.
- It's for Ursula. - Sure, yeah. Okay, it fits.
- Es para Ursula. - Claro, sí. Okay, le queda.
Marcel, give Rossy the remote.
Marcel, dale el control a Rossy.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[HABLANDO EN ESPAÑOL]
How did he do this?
¿Cómo hizo esto?
It's this whole stupid Ursula thing.
Es todo este asunto tonto de Ursula.
So he's going out with her. Is it really so terrible?
Entonces va a salir con ella. ¿Es realmente tan terrible?
- You don't know my sister. - Talk to Joey.
- No conoces a mi hermana. - Habla con Joey.
- He's falling in love with her. - You won't lose him.
- Se está enamorando de ella. - No lo vas a perder.
They haven't even slept together yet. That's not serious.
Ni siquiera han dormido juntos todavía. Eso no es serio.
Oh. Um, yeah.
Oh. Eh, sí.
May we help you?
¿Podemos ayudarla?
[RACHEL YELLS]
[RACHEL GRITA]
Rachel! Rachel!
¡Rachel! ¡Rachel!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Estoy bien. Estoy bien.
RACHEL: Ow, ow, ow. Ow, ow, ow.
RACHEL: Ay, ay, ay. Ay, ay, ay.
Ow, ow, ow. Ow, ow, ow.
Ay, ay, ay. Ay, ay, ay.
Uh, hi, uh, my friend was taking down our Christmas lights...
Eh, hola, eh, mi amiga estaba quitando las luces de Navidad...
...and she fell off the balcony and may have broken her foot or ankle.
...y se cayó del balcón y puede que se haya roto el pie o el tobillo.
My God, you still have your Christmas lights up?
Dios mío, ¿todavía tienen puestas las luces de Navidad?
Fill this out and bring it back.
Llene esto y devuélvalo.
- Okay. Here you go. - Ow, ow, ow. Ow, ow, ow.
- Okay. Aquí tiene. - Ay, ay, ay. Ay, ay, ay.
MONICA: Okay. Whew.
MONICA: Okay. Uf.
All right.
De acuerdo.
Name...
Nombre...
...address...
...dirección...
Okay. In case of emergency, call?
Okay. En caso de emergencia, ¿a quién llamo?
You.
Tú.
Really?
¿En serio?
Yeah.
Sí.
Oh, that is so sweet.
Oh, eso es tan tierno.
Oh, gosh. I love you.
Oh, cielos. Te amo.
Okay, insurance?
Okay, ¿seguro médico?
Oh, yeah, check it. Definitely gonna want some of that.
Oh, sí, revísalo. Definitivamente querrás algo de eso.
You don't have insurance?
¿No tienes seguro?
Why? How much is this gonna cost?
¿Por qué? ¿Cuánto va a costar esto?
I have no idea, but X-rays alone could be a couple hundred dollars.
No tengo idea, pero solo las radiografías podrían ser un par de cientos de dólares.
- What are we gonna do? - There's not much we can do.
- ¿Qué vamos a hacer? - No hay mucho que podamos hacer.
Uh, unless I use yours.
Eh, a menos que use el tuyo.
No, no, no, no, no.
Well, now, wait a second.
Bueno, espera un segundo.
Who did I just put as my "in case of emergency" person?
¿A quién acabo de poner como mi persona "en caso de emergencia"?
That's insurance fraud.
Eso es fraude al seguro.
Well, all right, then. Forget it. Might as well just go home.
Bueno, entonces está bien. Olvídalo. Mejor vámonos a casa.
- Ow, ow, ow, ow! - Okay, okay.
- ¡Ay, ay, ay, ay! - Okay, okay.
- Okay, come here. I hate this. - Thank you. I love you.
- Okay, ven aquí. Odio esto. - Gracias. Te amo.
Hi, heh. Um, I'm gonna need a new set of these forms.
Hola, je. Eh, voy a necesitar un nuevo juego de estos formularios.
Why?
¿Por qué?
[LAUGHING]
[RÍEN]
I am really an idiot.
Soy un verdadero idiota.
You see, I was filling out my friend's form...
Verás, estaba llenando un formulario para mi amiga...
...and instead of putting her information...
...y en lugar de poner su información...
...I put mine.
...puse la mía.
You are an idiot.
Eres un idiota.
Yep, that's me. Heh. I am that stupid.
Sí, ese soy yo. Je. Soy así de tonto.
I had a dream last night where I was playing football with my kid.
Anoche soñé que jugaba fútbol americano con mi hijo.
- That's nice. - That's nice.
- Qué bien. - Qué bien.
No, no. With him.
No, no. Con él.
I'm on this field, and they hike me the baby.
Estoy en este campo y me pasan al bebé.
I know I've gotta do something because the Tampa Bay defense is coming right at me.
Sé que tengo que hacer algo porque la defensa de Tampa Bay viene hacia mí.
Tampa Bay's got a terrible team.
Tampa Bay tiene un equipo terrible.
Right, but...
Cierto, pero...
...it is just me and the baby, so I'm thinking they can take us.
...solo somos el bebé y yo, así que pienso que pueden con nosotros.
And so I, uh, heh...
Y entonces yo, eh, je...
I just heave it downfield.
Simplemente la lanzo al campo.
What are you, crazy? That's a baby.
¿Qué te pasa? Es un bebé.
He should take the sack?
¿Debería dejarse placar?
Anyway, suddenly I'm downfield.
En fin, de repente estoy en el campo.
And I realize that I'm the one who's supposed to catch him, right?
Y me doy cuenta de que se supone que yo debo atraparlo, ¿verdad?
Only I know there's no way I'm not gonna get there in time.
Solo que sé que no hay forma de que llegue a tiempo.
So I am running and I'm running...
Así que corro y corro...
...and that is when I woke up.
...y es entonces cuando me desperté.
See, I am so not ready to be a father.
Ves, no estoy nada preparado para ser padre.
Hey, you're gonna be fine.
Oye, vas a estar bien.
You're one of the most caring, responsible men in North America.
Eres uno de los hombres más cariñosos y responsables de Norteamérica.
You're gonna make a great dad.
Serás un gran papá.
Yeah, Ross. You and the baby just need better blocking.
Sí, Ross. Tú y el bebé solo necesitan mejor bloqueo.
Oh. Have either of you ever been to the Rainbow Room? Is it expensive?
Oh. ¿Alguno de ustedes ha ido al Rainbow Room? ¿Es caro?
Only if you order stuff.
Solo si pides cosas.
I'm taking Ursula tonight. It's her birthday.
Llevo a Ursula esta noche. Es su cumpleaños.
- Whoa. What about Phoebe's birthday? - When's that?
- ¡Vaya! ¿Y el cumpleaños de Phoebe? - ¿Cuándo es?
ROSS: Uh...
ROSS: Eh...
...tonight.
...esta noche.
Ugh, man, what are the odds of that happening?
Uf, tío, ¿qué probabilidades hay de que eso pase?
You take your time.
Tómate tu tiempo.
There it is.
Ahí está.
So, what are you gonna do?
Entonces, ¿qué vas a hacer?
What can I do? I don't want to screw it up with Ursula.
¿Qué puedo hacer? No quiero arruinarlo con Ursula.
And your friend Phoebe?
¿Y tu amiga Phoebe?
If she's my friend, hopefully she'll understand. Wouldn't you guys?
Si es mi amiga, espero que lo entienda. ¿Ustedes no?
Man, if you tried that on my birthday...
Tío, si intentaras eso en mi cumpleaños...
...you'd be staring at the business end of a hissy fit.
...estarías mirando el lado malo de un berrinche.
You add a pinch of saffron, it makes all the difference.
Añades una pizca de azafrán y marca la diferencia.
Okay, uh...
Está bien, uh...
- Monica? - Yes?
- ¿Monica? - ¿Sí?
Yes, she is.
Sí, lo es.
- Hi. This is my friend Rachel. - Hi.
- Hola. Esta es mi amiga Rachel. - Hola.
Hi, uh, Rachel, I'm Dr. Mitchell.
Hola, eh, Rachel, soy el Dr. Mitchell.
And I'm his friend Dr. Rosen.
Y yo soy su amigo, el Dr. Rosen.
Aren't you a little cute to be a doctor?
¿No eres un poco linda para ser doctora?
Excuse me?
¿Perdón?
God, young, young. I meant young, heh.
Dios, joven, joven. Quise decir joven, je.
Young to be a doctor.
Joven para ser doctora.
- Oh, good, Rach. - Thank you.
- Oh, bien, Rach. - Gracias.
Right.
Cierto.
[R.E.M.'S "WHAT'S THE FREQUENCY, KENNETH?" PLAYING ON STEREO]
[SUENA "WHAT'S THE FREQUENCY, KENNETH?" DE R.E.M. EN ESTÉREO]
So he said it was just a sprain, and that was it.
Entonces dijo que solo era un esguince, y eso fue todo.
Uh, you left out the stupid part.
Eh, te saltaste la parte estúpida.
It's not stupid.
No es estúpido.
The very cute doctors asked us out for tomorrow night, and I said yes.
Los doctores, muy lindos, nos invitaron a salir para mañana por la noche, y dije que sí.
I think it's totally insane. I mean, they work for the hospital.
Me parece una locura. O sea, trabajan para el hospital.
It's like returning to the scene of the crime.
Es como volver a la escena del crimen.
- I say we blow off the dates. - What? Monica, they are cute.
- Digo que cancelamos las citas. - ¿Qué? Monica, son lindos.
They are doctors. Cute doctors. Doctors who are cute.
Son doctores. Doctores lindos. Doctores que son lindos.
All right, what have we learned so far?
Bien, ¿qué hemos aprendido hasta ahora?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[LA MÚSICA SE DETIENE]
ALL: Surprise!
TODOS: ¡Sorpresa!
What the hell are you doing? You scared the crap out of me.
¿Qué demonios hacen? Me asustaron muchísimo.
- Was that the cake? - Yeah.
- ¿Era ese el pastel? - Sí.
I got a lemon shmush.
Me tocó un 'lemon shmush'.
Come on. She'll be here any minute.
Vamos. Ella llegará en cualquier minuto.
RACHEL: I hope it's okay.
RACHEL: Espero que esté bien.
"Happy Birthday, Peehee."
"Feliz Cumpleaños, Peehee."
Maybe we can make a B out of one of those roses.
Quizás podamos hacer una B con una de esas rosas.
Yeah, we'll just use our special cake tools.
Sí, usaremos nuestras herramientas especiales para pasteles.
- Hey, what's going on? CHANDLER: Oh, we just...
- Oye, ¿qué pasa? CHANDLER: Oh, solo...
ALL: Surprise!
TODOS: ¡Sorpresa!
Oh, oh, oh!
¡Oh, oh, oh!
This is so great.
Esto es genial.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
This was not at all scary.
Esto no dio nada de miedo.
Hi, everybody. Hi, Betty.
Hola a todos. Hola, Betty.
Betty, hi.
Hola, Betty.
You found Betty. Oh, my gosh. This is so great.
Encontraste a Betty. Oh, Dios mío. Esto es genial.
Everybody I love is in the same room.
Todas las personas que amo están en la misma habitación.
Where's Joey?
¿Dónde está Joey?
Did you see Betty?
¿Viste a Betty?
I tell you, I wouldn't mind having a piece of this sun-dried-tomato business.
Te digo que no me importaría tener un pedazo de este negocio de tomates secados al sol.
Five years ago, if somebody'd said to me, "Here's a tomato that looks like a prune"...
Hace cinco años, si alguien me hubiera dicho: "Aquí tienes un tomate que parece una ciruela pasa"...
...I'd have said, "Get out of my office."
...le habría dicho: "Fuera de mi oficina".
Dad, before I was born, did you freak out at all?
Papá, antes de que yo naciera, ¿te asustaste un poco?
I'm not freaking out. I'm just saying...
No me estoy asustando. Solo digo...
...if someone had come to me with the idea...
...si alguien hubiera venido a mí con la idea...
Dad, Dad, Dad. I'm talking about the whole, uh, baby thing.
Papá, papá, papá. Estoy hablando de todo, eh, lo del bebé.
Did you, uh, ever get this sort of...
¿Alguna vez te dio este tipo de...
...panicky, "Oh, my God, I'm gonna be a father" kind of a thing?
...pánico, el tipo de "Dios mío, voy a ser padre"?
No.
Your mother really did the work. I was busy with the business.
Tu madre hizo todo el trabajo. Yo estaba ocupado con el negocio.
I wasn't around that much.
Yo no estuve mucho tiempo.
Is that what this is about?
¿De eso se trata?
No, no, Dad. I was just wondering.
No, no, papá. Solo me preguntaba.
There's time to make up for that. We can do stuff together.
Hay tiempo para compensar eso. Podemos hacer cosas juntos.
You always wanted to go to colonial Williamsburg. How about we do that?
Siempre quisiste ir a la Williamsburg colonial. ¿Qué tal si hacemos eso?
Thanks, Dad. Really, heh.
Gracias, papá. De verdad, jeh.
You know, I just, I just...
Sabes, yo solo, yo solo...
I just needed to know, um...
Solo necesitaba saber, eh...
...when did you start to feel like a father?
...¿cuándo empezaste a sentirte como un padre?
Oh. Well, I guess it must have been the day after you were born.
Oh. Bueno, supongo que fue el día después de que naciste.
We were in the hospital room, your mother was asleep...
Estábamos en la habitación del hospital, tu madre estaba dormida...
...and they brought you in and gave you to me.
...y te trajeron y me los diste.
You were this ugly little red thing.
Eras una cosita roja y fea.
[CHUCKLES]
[RÍE]
And all of a sudden, you grabbed my finger with your whole fist...
Y de repente, agarraste mi dedo con todo el puño...
...and you squeezed it...
...y lo apretaste...
...so tight.
...muy fuerte.
And that's when I knew.
Y ahí fue cuando lo supe.
So you don't want to go to Williamsburg?
Entonces, ¿no quieres ir a Williamsburg?
We can go to Williamsburg.
Podemos ir a Williamsburg.
Eat your fish.
Come tu pescado.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[HABLANDO EN ESPAÑOL]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
MONICA: Rachel, the cute doctors are here.
MONICA: Rachel, los doctores guapos están aquí.
RACHEL: Okay, coming.
RACHEL: Okay, voy.
Hi, come on in. Hey, Michael, Jeffrey.
Hola, pasen. Hola, Michael, Jeffrey.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
Uh, here, we brought wine.
Eh, aquí, trajimos vino.
Look at this. It's from the cellars of Ernest and Tova Borgnine.
Mira esto. Es de las bodegas de Ernest y Tova Borgnine.
- So how could we resist? - Oh, that's great.
- ¿Cómo podíamos resistirnos? - Oh, eso es genial.
- So, Monica, how's the ankle? - It's, uh...
- Entonces, Mónica, ¿cómo va el tobillo? - Está, eh...
[RACHEL CLEARS THROAT]
[RACHEL SE ACLARA LA GARGANTA]
Why don't you tell them?
¿Por qué no les dices tú?
After all, it is your ankle.
Después de todo, es tu tobillo.
You know, it's feeling a lot better. Thank you.
Sabes, se siente mucho mejor. Gracias.
Listen, why don't you guys sit down, and we'll get you some glasses.
Escucha, ¿por qué no se sientan y les traigo unos vasos?
- Okay. - Okay.
- Vale. - Vale.
- Um... - Stat.
- Eh... - Rápido.
Okay, listen, I'm thinking, why don't we just tell them who we really are?
Okay, escucha, estoy pensando, ¿por qué no les decimos quiénes somos realmente?
- I mean, I think it'll be fine. - It will not. We'll get in trouble.
- Quiero decir, creo que estará bien. - No lo estará. Nos meteremos en problemas.
Monica, would you stop being such a wuss?
Mónica, ¿dejarás de ser una gallina?
A wuss? Excuse me for living in the real world.
¿Una gallina? Disculpa por vivir en el mundo real.
- So? - So they still seem normal.
- ¿Y bien? - Y bien, todavía parecen normales.
That's because they are.
Eso es porque lo son.
You have to admit, when we go out with women we meet at the hospital...
Tienes que admitir que cuando salimos con mujeres que conocemos en el hospital...
Would you relax? Take a look around.
¿Te relajas? Mira a tu alrededor.
There are no pagan altars.
No hay altares paganos.
No piles of bones in the corners.
No hay pilas de huesos en las esquinas.
They're fine. Go like this:
Están bien. Hazlo así:
I said we are not going to do it, okay? Sometimes you can be such a big baby.
Dije que no vamos a hacerlo, ¿de acuerdo? A veces puedes ser un bebé.
- I am not a baby. - Be serious.
- No soy un bebé. - Habla en serio.
- You get uptight... - You act like a princess.
- Te pones nervioso... - Actúas como una princesa.
- You know what? You know what? - What? What?
- ¿Sabes qué? ¿Sabes qué? - ¿Qué? ¿Qué?
Every day you are becoming more and more like your mother.
Cada día te pareces más a tu madre.
Excuse me. Hello, here we go.
Disculpa. Hola, aquí vamos.
This is a great place. How long have you lived here?
Este es un gran lugar. ¿Cuánto tiempo has vivido aquí?
Thanks. I've been here about six years.
Gracias. He estado aquí unos seis años.
And Rachel moved in a few months ago.
Y Rachel se mudó hace unos meses.
See, I was supposed to get married...
Mira, se suponía que me iba a casar...
...but, um, I left the guy at the altar.
...pero, eh, dejé al chico en el altar.
- Really? - Yeah.
- ¿En serio? - Sí.
Yeah, I know it's pretty selfish, but, heh...
Sí, sé que es bastante egoísta, pero, je...
...hey, that's me.
...bueno, así soy yo.
- Why don't you try the hummus? RACHEL: Ahem.
- ¿Por qué no pruebas el hummus? RACHEL: Ejem.
So, Monica, what do you do?
Entonces, Monica, ¿a qué te dedicas?
Uh, I am a, uh, chef at a restaurant uptown.
Uh, soy, eh, chef en un restaurante del centro.
- Oh, good for you. - Yeah, it is.
- Oh, qué bien por ti. - Sí, lo es.
Mostly because I get to boss people around, which I just love to do.
Principalmente porque puedo dar órdenes, lo cual me encanta hacer.
Well, this hummus is great.
Bueno, este hummus está genial.
God bless the chickpea.
Dios bendiga al garbanzo.
[LAUGHING]
[RÍEN]
Oh, God.
Ay, Dios.
I am so spoiled.
Soy tan consentida.
That's it.
Eso es todo.
And by the way, have I mentioned that back in high school...
Y por cierto, ¿te he dicho que en la secundaria...
...I was a cow?
...era una vaca?
I used to wet my bed.
Solía mojar la cama.
I use my breasts to get other people's attention.
Uso mis pechos para llamar la atención de la gente.
We both do that.
Ambas lo hacemos.
[PHONE RINGING]
[SUENA EL TELÉFONO]
Monica and Rachel's apartment.
Apartamento de Monica y Rachel.
Uh... Uh, yeah, just one second. Uh, Rachel, it's your dad.
Uh... Uh, sí, solo un segundo. Uh, Rachel, es tu papá.
Hi, Dad.
Hola, papá.
No, no. It's me.
No, no. Soy yo.
Listen, Dad, I can't talk right now. Um...
Escucha, papá, no puedo hablar ahora. Um...
But there's something, um...
Pero hay algo, um...
There's something that I've been meaning to tell you.
Hay algo que he querido decirte.
Excuse me.
Disculpe.
Remember back in freshman year?
¿Recuerdas cuando estábamos en primer año?
Well, Billy Dreskin and I had sex on your bed.
Bueno, Billy Dreskin y yo tuvimos sexo en tu cama.
Daddy...
Papi...
Daddy... Daddy, why? Why would I sleep with Billy Dreskin?
Papi... Papi, ¿por qué? ¿Por qué me acostaría con Billy Dreskin?
His father tried to put you out of business.
Su padre intentó sacarte del negocio.
You are dead.
Estás muerta.
Ross, he's got the remote again.
Ross, él tiene el control otra vez.
Good.
Bien.
Maybe he can switch it back.
Quizás pueda cambiarlo de nuevo.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[HABLANDO EN ESPAÑOL]
Maybe not.
Quizás no.
Hello?
¿Hola?
Uh, ueah... Uh...
Eh, sí... Eh...
Okay, uh, hold on a second and let me just check and see if she's here.
Okay, eh, espera un segundo y déjame ver si está aquí.
It's the woman from the hospital. There's a problem with the form.
Es la mujer del hospital. Hay un problema con el formulario.
Oh, God, what do we do?
Oh, Dios, ¿qué hacemos?
I don't know. Just find out what they want.
No sé. Solo averigua qué quieren.
Okay. No, you do it.
Okay. No, tú hazlo.
Hello. This is Monica.
Hola. Habla Monica.
Yeah?
¿Sí?
Oh. Okay.
Oh. De acuerdo.
Yes, we'll be right down. Thank you.
Sí, bajamos enseguida. Gracias.
We forgot to sign one of the admissions forms.
Olvidamos firmar uno de los formularios de admisión.
- Okay, you're right, this wasn't worth it. - Thank you.
- Okay, tienes razón, esto no valió la pena. - Gracias.
- Okay, let me just change. - Yes.
- Okay, déjame cambiarme. - Sí.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Trouble?
¿Problemas?
Your sister stood me up the other night.
Tu hermana me dejó plantado la otra noche.
Oh, no. Don't you hate it when people aren't there for you?
Oh, no. ¿No odias cuando la gente no está ahí para ti?
- Did you try calling her? - I've been trying for two days.
- ¿Intentaste llamarla? - He estado intentando por dos días.
When I called the restaurant, they said she was too busy to talk.
Cuando llamé al restaurante, dijeron que estaba muy ocupada para hablar.
I can't believe she's blowing me off.
No puedo creer que me esté ignorando.
Hey.
Oye.
Oh.
Um, you got a minute?
Eh, ¿tienes un minuto?
Um, yeah, I'm just working.
Eh, sí, solo estoy trabajando.
- So... - Uh-huh?
- Entonces... - Ajá?
Um, oh, I got you a birthday present.
Eh, oh, te compré un regalo de cumpleaños.
Oh, wow, you remembered.
Oh, wow, te acordaste.
Oh. It's a Judy Jetson Thermos.
Oh. Es un termo de Judy Jetson.
Right. Like the kind you...
Cierto. Como el tipo de los...
Right.
Cierto.
Oh, I got something for you too.
Oh, yo también te traje algo.
How'd you know I was coming?
¿Cómo sabías que venía?
Um, yeah, um, "twin" thing.
Eh, sí, eh, cosa de "gemelos".
I can't believe you did this.
No puedo creer que hiciste esto.
I can't believe you...
No puedo creer que tú...
...did this.
...hiciste esto.
So, what's the deal with, um, you and Joey?
Entonces, ¿cuál es la onda contigo y Joey?
Oh, right.
Oh, claro.
He is so great. But that's over.
Él es genial. Pero eso se acabó.
- Does he know? - Who?
- ¿Él lo sabe? - ¿Quién?
Joey. You know, um, ahem, he's really nutsy about you.
Joey. Sabes, eh, ejem, él está muy loco por ti.
He is? Why?
¿Lo está? ¿Por qué?
- You got me. - Right.
- Tú me dirás. - Cierto.
Excuse me...
Disculpe...
...doesn't this come with a side salad?
...¿esto no viene con una ensalada?
So, um, are you gonna call him?
Entonces, eh, ¿vas a llamarlo?
- What, you think he likes me? - No. Joey.
- ¿Qué, crees que le gusto? - No. Joey.
Oh. No, no. He is so smart. He'll figure it out.
Oh. No, no. Él es muy inteligente. Lo resolverá.
Do you want some chicken?
¿Quieres pollo?
No, no. No food with a face, remember?
No, no. Nada de comida con cara, ¿recuerdas?
You have not changed.
No has cambiado.
Yeah, you too.
Sí, tú tampoco.
- Hi. Remember us? - Mm-hm.
- Hola. ¿Nos recuerdas? - Mm-hm.
Um, yeah, you just called about needing a signature on the admissions form?
Um, sí, ¿llamó sobre la necesidad de una firma en el formulario de admisión?
Well, it turns out we need a whole new one.
Bueno, resulta que necesitamos uno completamente nuevo.
Because, um, you see...
Porque, um, verá...
...I put the wrong name again.
...puse el nombre equivocado otra vez.
- Because, um... - You're that stupid.
- Porque, um... - Eres así de estúpido.
I am. I'm that stupid.
Lo soy. Soy así de estúpido.
Yeah, and I'm just gonna pay for this with a check.
Sí, y voy a pagar esto con un cheque.
You know, your insurance will cover that.
Sabes, tu seguro lo cubrirá.
Yeah, I know. I'm just not that bright either.
Sí, lo sé. Tampoco soy muy listo.
Okay, worst case scenario:
Okay, el peor de los casos:
- Say you never feel like a father. - Uh-huh.
- Digamos que nunca te sientes como un padre. - Ajá.
Say your son never feels connected to you as one.
Digamos que tu hijo nunca se siente conectado contigo como tal.
Say all of his relationships are affected by this.
Digamos que todas sus relaciones se ven afectadas por esto.
Do you have a point?
¿Tienes algún punto?
You know, you'd think I would.
Sabes, pensarías que sí.
[MARCEL GASPING]
[MARCEL TOSIENDO FUERTE]
What's up with the simian?
¿Qué pasa con el simio?
It's just a fur ball.
Es solo una bola de pelo.
Okay, whose turn is it?
Okay, ¿a quién le toca?
Yours. I just got 43 points for "kidney."
A ti. Acabo de sacar 43 puntos por "riñón".
No, you got zero points for "idney."
No, sacaste cero puntos por "riñón".
I had a K. Where's my K?
Tenía una K. ¿Dónde está mi K?
[GASPING]
[JADEANDO]
You've got to help me. My monkey swallowed a K.
Tienes que ayudarme. Mi mono se tragó una K.
Get that animal out of here.
Saca a ese animal de aquí.
The animal hospital is way across town. He's choking. I don't know what to do.
El hospital de animales está al otro lado de la ciudad. Se está ahogando. No sé qué hacer.
- What's going on? - Marcel swallowed a Scrabble tile.
- ¿Qué está pasando? - Marcel se tragó una ficha de Scrabble.
Excuse me. This hospital is for people.
Disculpe. Este hospital es para personas.
Lady, he is people. He has a name, okay?
Señora, él es una persona. Tiene nombre, ¿de acuerdo?
He watches Jeopardy...
Ve Jeopardy...
...he touches himself when nobody's watching.
...se toca cuando nadie lo ve.
Please, have a heart.
Por favor, tenga corazón.
- I'll take a look at him. - Oh, thank you.
- Le echaré un vistazo. - Oh, gracias.
- Michael. - Rachel.
- What? - Monica.
- ¿Qué? - Monica.
- Oh. - Hi.
- Oh. - Hola.
Hey.
Oye.
Urs.
What are you doing here? I've been trying to call you.
¿Qué haces aquí? He estado intentando llamarte.
Listen, um...
Escucha, um...
Don't say "listen." I know that "listen." I've said that "listen."
No digas "escucha". Sé ese "escucha". He dicho ese "escucha".
I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
I don't get it. What happened?
No lo entiendo. ¿Qué pasó?
What about everything you said under the bridge?
¿Qué pasó con todo lo que dijiste bajo el puente?
Yeah, um, ahem...
Sí, um, ejem...
You know, just forget about what I said under the bridge.
[ERROR API]
I was talking crazy that night. I was so drunk.
You don't drink.
[ERROR API]
That's right, I don't.
But I was drunk on you.
[ERROR API]
- Oh, Urs. - But, yeah, so it's not gonna work.
Why? Is it because I'm friends with Phoebe?
[ERROR API]
If it was, would you stop hanging out with her?
No.
No, I couldn't do that.
[ERROR API]
Um, then, yeah, it's because of Phoebe.
So you know, it's either her or me.
[ERROR API]
Then, uh... Then I'm sorry.
You know...
Sabes...
...you're gonna be really, really hard to get over.
[ERROR API]
I know.
Lo sé.
I don't know whether it's just because we're breaking up or what...
[ERROR API]
...but you have never looked so beautiful.
Really?
¿En serio?
- Pheebs? - Yeah.
[ERROR API]
He looks so tiny.
- We just got the message. - Is he all right?
[ERROR API]
Yeah, the doctor got the K out.
He also found an M and an O.
[ERROR API]
We think he was trying to spell out "monkey."
The doctor says he'll be fine. He's just sleeping now.
[ERROR API]
So you feel like a dad yet?
No. Why?
No. ¿Por qué?
Hey, come on, you came through. You did what you had to do.
[ERROR API]
That is very dad.
Oh, look, he's waking up.
[ERROR API]
ROSS: Hey, fella. How you doing?
[DUBBED IN SPANISH]
[ERROR API]
ALL: Ooh.
TODOS: Ooh.