I can't believe you would actually say that.
No puedo creer que realmente dijeras eso.
I would much rather be Mr. Peanut than Mr. Salty.
Preferiría ser el Sr. Cacahuete que el Sr. Salado.
No way. Mr. Salty is a sailor, all right?
No puede ser. El Sr. Salado es un marinero, ¿vale?
He's gotta be, like, the toughest snack there is.
Tiene que ser, como, el snack más duro que existe.
I don't know. You don't wanna mess with corn nuts.
No sé. No querrás meterte con los frutos secos.
They're crazy.
Están locos.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. You gotta come see this.
Dios mío. Dios mío. Tienes que venir a ver esto.
There's some creep out there with a telescope.
Hay un pervertido ahí fuera con un telescopio.
[RACHEL GASPS]
[RACHEL AHOGA UN GRITO]
I can't believe it. He's looking right at us.
No puedo creerlo. Nos está mirando directamente.
Oh, that is so sick.
Oh, eso es muy asqueroso.
I feel violated.
Me siento violada.
And not in a good way.
Y no de una buena manera.
How can people do that?
¿Cómo puede la gente hacer eso?
[ALL GROANING AND SCOFFING]
[TODOS PROTESTAN Y SE RÍEN CON DESDÉN]
Oh, you guys, look. Ugly Naked Guy got gravity boots.
Oh, chicos, miren. El Chico Feo y Desnudo tiene botas antigravedad.
I'm telling you, years from now, school children will study it...
Te digo que, años después, los escolares lo estudiarán...
...as one of the greatest first dates of all time.
...como una de las mejores primeras citas de todos los tiempos.
It was unbelievable.
Fue increíble.
We could totally be ourselves. We didn't have to play any games.
Podríamos ser totalmente nosotros mismos. No tuvimos que jugar a ningún juego.
- So have you called her yet? - Let her know I like her? Are you insane?
- ¿Entonces la has llamado ya? - ¿Hacerle saber que me gusta? ¿Estás loco?
Guys. It's gross.
Chicos. Es asqueroso.
It's the next day. How needy do I wanna seem?
Es al día siguiente. ¿Qué tan necesitado quiero parecer?
I'm right. Right?
Tengo razón. ¿Verdad?
- Let her dangle. - Yeah, definitely.
- Déjala en ascuas. - Sí, definitivamente.
Oh.
I can't believe my parents are pressuring me...
No puedo creer que mis padres me estén presionando...
...to find one of you people.
...para encontrar a uno de ustedes.
God. Come on. Just do it.
Dios. Vamos. Solo hazlo.
Call her. Stop being so testosterone-y.
Llámala. Deja de ser tan testosterónico.
Which, by the way, is the real San Francisco treat.
Lo cual, por cierto, es el verdadero placer de San Francisco.
- I got her machine. - Her answering machine?
- Dejé mensaje. - ¿En su contestador?
No, interestingly enough, her leaf blower picked up.
No, curiosamente, su soplador de hojas respondió.
So, um, why didn't you say anything?
Entonces, eh, ¿por qué no dijiste nada?
Oh, no, no, no. Last time I left a spontaneous message...
Oh, no, no, no. La última vez que dejé un mensaje espontáneo...
...I ended up using the phrase, "Yes, indeed-io."
...terminé usando la frase: "¡Sí, en efecto-io!"
MONICA: Look, it's Rachel and Barry. No, no, don't everybody look at once.
MONICA: Miren, son Rachel y Barry. No, no, no miren todos a la vez.
- Okay, okay. What's going on? - Okay, they're just talking.
- Vale, vale. ¿Qué pasa? - Vale, solo están hablando.
Yeah, well, does he look upset?
Sí, bueno, ¿parece molesto?
Does he look like he was just told to shove anything?
¿Parece que le acaban de decir que se meta algo?
No. No, actually, he's smiling.
No. No, de hecho, está sonriendo.
Oh, my God. Don't do that.
Dios mío. No hagas eso.
What? What? What?
¿Qué? ¿Qué? ¿Qué?
That man across the street just kicked that pigeon.
Ese hombre al otro lado de la calle acaba de patear a esa paloma.
Oh.
And basically, that's how a bill becomes a law.
Y básicamente, así es como un proyecto de ley se convierte en ley.
GROUP: Oh.
GRUPO: Oh.
- See? Hey, Rach. - Hey.
- ¿Ves? Hola, Rach. - Hola.
How'd it go?
¿Cómo fue?
You know, it was, uh... It was actually really great.
Sabes, fue, eh... En realidad fue muy bueno.
Took me to lunch at the Russian Tea Room.
Me llevó a almorzar al Russian Tea Room.
I had that chicken, you know, where you poke it and butter squirts out.
Comí ese pollo, ¿sabes?, al que le picas y le sale mantequilla.
Not a good day for birds.
No es un buen día para los pájaros.
And then we took a walk to Bendel's.
Y luego fuimos a caminar a Bendel's.
And I told him not to, but he got me a little bottle of Chanel.
Y le dije que no, pero me compró una botellita de Chanel.
That's nice. Now was that before or after you told him...
Qué bien. ¿Y eso fue antes o después de que le dijeras...
...to stop calling, stop sending you flowers and to generally leave you alone, huh?
...que dejara de llamar, de mandarte flores y que en general te dejara en paz, ¿eh?
Right. Well, we never actually got to that.
Correcto. Bueno, en realidad nunca llegamos a eso.
Oh, it was just so nice to see him again, you know? It was...
Oh, fue tan agradable verlo de nuevo, ¿sabes? Fue...
It was comfortable and it was familiar.
Fue cómodo y familiar.
It was just nice.
Simplemente fue agradable.
That's "nice" twice.
Eso son "agradable" dos veces.
Rachel, what's going on?
Rachel, ¿qué pasa?
Isn't this the same Barry who you left at the altar?
¿No es este el mismo Barry que dejaste plantado en el altar?
Duh. Where have you been?
Obvio. ¿Dónde has estado?
Yeah, but it was different with him today.
Sí, pero fue diferente con él hoy.
He wasn't, like, Orthodontist Guy, you know?
No era el Chico del Ortodoncista, ¿sabes?
I mean, we had fun. Is there anything wrong with that?
Quiero decir, nos divertimos. ¿Hay algo malo en eso?
Yes.
Sí.
- Why? - I have my reasons.
- ¿Por qué? - Tengo mis razones.
Okay, how about the fact that he's engaged to another woman...
Está bien, ¿qué tal el hecho de que está comprometido con otra mujer...
...who just happens to be your ex-best friend?
...que resulta ser tu ex-mejor amiga?
All right. All right, all right, all right. I know it's stupid.
Está bien. Está bien, está bien, está bien. Sé que es estúpido.
I'll go see him this afternoon and I will just put an end to it.
Lo veré esta tarde y pondré fin a esto.
Wow.
Guau.
- Wow. - Ha, ha.
- Vaya. - Ja, ja.
Yeah.
Sí.
I'm not crazy, right? I mean, it was never like that.
No estoy loca, ¿verdad? Quiero decir, nunca fue así.
No, it wasn't.
No, no lo fue.
Oh. It was so nice having this little sink here.
Oh. Qué bien tener este pequeño lavabo aquí.
"Oh, Danielle, I wasn't expecting the machine.
"Oh, Danielle, no esperaba la máquina.
Give me a call when you get a chance."
Llámame cuando tengas un momento."
Bye-bye.
Adiós.
Oh, God.
Ay, Dios.
That's what you've been working on for the past two hours?
¿Eso es en lo que has estado trabajando durante las últimas dos horas?
Hey, I've been honing.
Oye, he estado perfeccionando.
What was with the dishes?
¿Qué pasó con los platos?
Oh, uh, I wanted her to think I might be in a restaurant...
Oh, eh, quería que pensara que podría estar en un restaurante...
...you know, I might have some kind of life.
...sabes, que podría tener algún tipo de vida.
Like I haven't been sitting around here honing for the last two hours?
¿Como si no hubiera estado sentada aquí perfeccionando durante las últimas dos horas?
He's doing it again. The guy with the telescope.
Lo está haciendo de nuevo. El tipo del telescopio.
PHOEBE: Oh, my God.
PHOEBE: Dios mío.
Oh. Go away. Stop looking in here!
Oh. Vete. ¡Deja de mirar aquí dentro!
Great. Now he's waving back.
Genial. Ahora está saludando.
We gotta do something about that guy.
Tenemos que hacer algo con ese tipo.
This morning, I caught him looking into our apartment.
Esta mañana, lo pillé mirando en nuestro apartamento.
It creeps me out. I feel like I can't do stuff.
Me da escalofríos. Siento que no puedo hacer cosas.
What kind of stuff?
¿Qué tipo de cosas?
Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff...
¿Madura de una vez? No estoy hablando de cosas sexys...
...but, like, when I'm cooking naked.
...sino, como, cuando estoy cocinando desnuda.
You cook naked?
¿Cocinas desnudo?
Yeah, toast, oatmeal. Nothing that spatters.
Sí, tostadas, avena. Nada que salpique.
What are you looking at me for? I didn't know that.
¿Por qué me miras? Yo no sabía eso.
What's the matter?
¿Qué pasa?
Oh, I just... Oh, Barry, this was not good.
Oh, yo solo... Oh, Barry, esto no estuvo bien.
No, it was. It was very, very good.
No, sí lo estuvo. Estuvo muy, muy bien.
- What about Mindy? - Oh, way better than Mindy.
- ¿Y Mindy? - Oh, mucho mejor que Mindy.
No, not that. I mean, what about you and Mindy?
No, eso no. Me refiero a ti y Mindy.
Oh. If you want, I'll just break it off with her.
Oh. Si quieres, rompo con ella.
No. No, no, no.
No, don't do that. Not for me.
No, no hagas eso. No por mí.
BERNICE: Dr. Farber, Bobby Rush is here for his adjustment.
BERNICE: Dr. Farber, Bobby Rush está aquí para su ajuste.
Thanks, Bernice.
Gracias, Bernice.
Let's go away this weekend.
Vamos a irnos este fin de semana.
Oh, Barry. Come on. This is all way too...
Oh, Barry. Vamos. Esto es demasiado...
No, we can go to Aruba.
No, podemos ir a Aruba.
When I went there on what would've been our honeymoon...
Cuando fui allí en lo que habría sido nuestra luna de miel...
...it was, uh... It was really nice. You would've liked it.
...fue, eh... Fue muy agradable. Te habría gustado.
I had a bra.
Tenía un sostén.
Hey, Dr. Farber.
Hola, Dr. Farber.
All right, Miss Green, everything looks fine.
Muy bien, señorita Green, todo parece estar bien.
Yep, I think we're starting to see some real progress here.
Sí, creo que estamos empezando a ver un progreso real aquí.
- What? - I'm 12, I'm not stupid.
- ¿Qué? - Tengo 12 años, no soy estúpida.
- Can I use your phone? - Yeah.
- ¿Puedo usar tu teléfono? - Sí.
Uh, but for future reference, um, that thing in your hand...
Eh, pero como referencia futura, eh, eso que tienes en la mano...
...can also be used as a phone.
...también se puede usar como teléfono.
[PHONE RINGS]
[SUENA EL TELÉFONO]
Yes, it's working.
Sí, está funcionando.
Why isn't she calling me back?
¿Por qué no me devuelve la llamada?
Maybe she never got your message.
Quizás nunca recibió tu mensaje.
You know, you could call her machine, and if she has a lot of beeps...
Sabes, podrías llamarle a su máquina, y si tiene muchos pitidos...
...that means she probably didn't get her messages yet.
...eso significa que probablemente no ha recibido sus mensajes todavía.
- You don't think that makes me seem...? - Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
- ¿No crees que eso me hace parecer...? - ¿Desesperado? ¿Necesitado? ¿Patético?
Ah, you obviously saw my personal ad.
Ah, obviamente viste mi anuncio personal.
- How many beeps? - She answered.
- ¿Cuántos pitidos? - Ella respondió.
You see, this is where you'd use that "hello" word we talked about.
Ves, aquí es donde usarías esa palabra "hola" de la que hablamos.
I'm not going to. She obviously got my message...
No lo voy a hacer. Obviamente recibió mi mensaje...
...and is choosing not to call me. Now I'm needy and snubbed.
...y está eligiendo no llamarme. Ahora estoy necesitado y despreciado.
God, I miss just being needy.
Dios, extraño ser solo necesitado.
GROUP: Hey.
GRUPO: ¡Hey!
So how'd he take it?
¿Y cómo se lo tomó?
Pretty well, actually.
Bastante bien, la verdad.
Uh, Rach. How come you have dental floss in your hair?
Eh, Rach. ¿Por qué tienes hilo dental en el pelo?
Oh, do I?
¿Oh, sí?
We ended up having sex in his chair.
Terminamos teniendo sexo en su silla.
You had sex in his chair?
¿Tuviste sexo en su silla?
I said that a little too loudly, didn't I?
Dije eso un poco alto, ¿verdad?
You had what?
¿Tuviste qué?
Sex in his chair.
Sexo en su silla.
What?
¿Qué?
What were you thinking?
[ERROR API]
I don't know. I mean, we still care about each other.
There's a history there. It's like you and Carol.
[ERROR API]
No. No, no.
It's nothing like me and Carol.
[ERROR API]
Please. If she said to you, "Ross, I want you on this couch...
...right here, right now," what would you say?
[ERROR API]
If it helps I could slide over.
It's a totally different situation.
[ERROR API]
It's apples and oranges. It's orthodontists and lesbians...
I gotta go.
[ERROR API]
- Where are you going? - I just have to go, all right?
Do I need a reason, huh? I have things to do with my life.
[ERROR API]
I have a jam-packed schedule.
And I am late for keeping up with it, okay?
[ERROR API]
[PHONE RINGING]
[SUENA EL TELÉFONO]
Hello? Hello?
[ERROR API]
[PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
Hello?
¿Hola?
Huh. Mindy.
[ERROR API]
Hi. Hey, how are you?
Yes, yes, I heard. Congratulations. That is so great.
[ERROR API]
Really, oh, God...
Okay.
Okay, I'm working tomorrow...
[ERROR API]
...but if you want, you can come by if you'd like.
Okay.
Great.
Genial.
All right.
De acuerdo.
So I'll see you tomorrow.
[ERROR API]
Okay. Bye.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
[ERROR API]
So how's Mindy?
Oh, she wants to see me tomorrow.
[ERROR API]
Oh, she sounded really weird. I gotta call Barry.
Hi, it's me. I just... Ha! Mindy.
[ERROR API]
Mindy. Hi.
No, I figured that's where you'd be.
[ERROR API]
[MIMICKING PHONE]
Hell is filled with people like you.
[ERROR API]
He's back. The peeper's back.
- Get down. - Get down?
[ERROR API]
And boogie.
Thanks, but I gotta go to work and get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
[ERROR API]
Relax. She may not even know.
Please, I haven't heard from her in seven months, and now she calls me.
[ERROR API]
I mean, what else is it about?
She was my best friend, you guys.
[ERROR API]
We went to camp together...
...she taught me how to kiss... - Yeah?
[ERROR API]
Now, you know, I'm, like, the other woman.
Ahora, ya sabes, soy como la otra mujer.
- Ugh, I feel so... - Naughty.
- Ugh, me siento tan... - Traviesa.
- I'll see you guys later. - I'll walk out with you.
- Los veo luego, chicos. - Salgo contigo.
When she taught you to kiss, you were at camp...
Cuando te enseñó a besar, estabas en un campamento...
...and were you wearing any kind of little uniform or...?
...¿y llevabas algún tipo de uniforme o...?
That's fine, yeah.
Está bien, sí.
Okay, I'm gonna go the bathroom. Will you watch my phone?
Ok, voy al baño. ¿Me cuidas el teléfono?
- Why don't you just take it with you? - Hey.
- ¿Por qué no te lo llevas contigo? - Oye.
We haven't been on a second date. She needs to hear me pee?
No hemos tenido una segunda cita. ¿Necesita oírme hacer pipí?
Why don't you just call her?
¿Por qué no la llamas?
I can't call her. I left a message. I have some pride.
No puedo llamarla. Dejé un mensaje. Tengo algo de orgullo.
- Do you? - No.
- ¿Sí? - No.
Danielle, hi.
Danielle, hola.
Hi, it's Chandler.
Hola, soy Chandler.
I'm fine. Ahem.
Estoy bien. Ejem.
Uh, listen...
Eh, escucha...
I don't know if you tried to call me because, uh, idiot that I am...
No sé si intentaste llamarme porque, eh, idiota de mí...
...I accidentally shut off my phone.
...accidentalmente apagué mi teléfono.
Ahem. Oh, okay. That's fine. That's great. Okay.
Ejem. Oh, ok. Está bien. Eso es genial. Ok.
She's on the other line. She's gonna call me back.
Está en otra línea. Me va a llamar de vuelta.
She's on the other line, gonna call me back.
Está en otra línea, me va a llamar de vuelta.
- Don't you have to pee? - That's why I'm dancing.
- ¿No tienes que hacer pipí? - Por eso estoy bailando.
- Mindy. - Hey, you.
- Mindy. - Hola, tú.
Hey, you.
Hola, tú.
So, what's up?
Entonces, ¿qué pasa?
Um, we should really be sitting for this.
Mmm, deberíamos sentarnos para esto.
Hmm.
Mmm.
Sure we should.
Claro que sí.
[SIGHS]
[SUSPIRA]
- So... - Now, I know things have been weird lately.
- Entonces... - Ahora, sé que las cosas han estado raras últimamente.
But you're my oldest friend, except for Laurie Schaefer...
Pero eres mi mejor amiga desde hace más tiempo, excepto por Laurie Schaefer...
...who I don't talk to anymore...
...con la que ya no hablo...
...because she's bitter that she lost the weight...
...porque está amargada porque perdió peso...
...and it turns out, she doesn't have a pretty face.
...y resulta que no tiene una cara bonita.
Okay, I'm gonna just ask you this once, and I want a straight answer.
Ok, te lo voy a preguntar solo una vez, y quiero una respuesta directa.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
[SUSPIRA]
Will you be my maid of honor?
¿Serás mi dama de honor?
- Of course! - Oh, that's so great!
- ¡Claro! - ¡Oh, qué bien!
It is! It is!
¡Lo es! ¡Lo es!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[AMBAS GRITANDO]
- Is that all you wanted to ask? - That's all.
- ¿Eso es todo lo que querías preguntar? - Eso es todo.
[BOTH SHOUTING]
[AMBAS GRITANDO]
[CRYING]
[LLORANDO]
What? What?
¿Qué? ¿Qué?
That's not all.
Eso no es todo.
- Oh, sure it is. - Oh, no, it isn't. No.
- Oh, claro que sí. - Oh, no, no lo es. No.
I think Barry's seeing someone in the city.
Creo que Barry está saliendo con alguien en la ciudad.
What would make you think that?
¿Qué te hace pensar eso?
Well, ever since we announced the engagement, he's acted weird.
Bueno, desde que anunciamos el compromiso, ha actuado raro.
And then last night, he came home smelling like Chanel.
Y anoche, llegó a casa oliendo a Chanel.
Really?
¿En serio?
Mindy, if it'll make you feel any better...
Mindy, si eso te hace sentir mejor...
...when Barry and I got engaged, he went through a weird thing too.
...cuando Barry y yo nos comprometimos, él también pasó por algo raro.
Oh, God. You see, that's what I was afraid of.
Ay, Dios. Ves, eso es lo que me temía.
- What? What's what you were afraid of? - Okay, okay.
- ¿Qué? ¿Qué es lo que te temías? - Está bien, está bien.
When Barry was engaged to you, he and I...
Cuando Barry estaba comprometido contigo, él y yo...
...kind of had a little thing on the side.
...tuvimos una cosita por ahí.
- What? - I know, I know.
- ¿Qué? - Lo sé, lo sé.
When he proposed to me, everyone said, "Don't do it.
Cuando él me propuso matrimonio, todos dijeron: "No lo hagas".
He's gonna do to you what he did to Rachel." And now I feel so stupid.
Te va a hacer lo que le hizo a Rachel". Y ahora me siento tan estúpida.
Ha, ha.
Ja, ja.
Hmm. Oh, Mindy.
Mmm. Ay, Mindy.
Oh, you are so stupid.
Ay, eres tan estúpida.
Oh, we are both so stupid.
Ay, las dos somos tan estúpidas.
What do you mean?
¿Qué quieres decir?
- Smell familiar? MINDY: Oh, no.
- ¿Te suena familiar? MINDY: Oh, no.
RACHEL: Mm-hm.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, lo siento mucho.
Oh, no, me. I am so sorry.
Oh, no, yo. Lo siento muchísimo.
No, I am sorry. I'm sorry.
No, lo siento yo. Lo siento.
Oh, my.
Oh, vaya.
Four letters, "circle or hoop."
Cuatro letras, "círculo o aro".
Ring, damn it, ring.
Anillo, ¡maldita sea, anillo!
Thanks.
Gracias.
You know our phone's not working?
¿Sabes que nuestro teléfono no funciona?
What?
¿Qué?
I tried to call you from the coffee shop. There was no answer.
Intenté llamarte desde la cafetería. No hubo respuesta.
I turned it off.
Lo apagué.
Mother of God, I turned it off.
Madre de Dios, lo apagué.
Just like you told her you did.
Justo como le dijiste que hiciste.
Just pointing out the irony.
Solo señalo la ironía.
So listen, I went across the street and talked to the doorman.
Así que mira, crucé la calle y hablé con el portero.
I got the peeper's name. Can I use the phone?
Conseguí el nombre del fisgón. ¿Puedo usar el teléfono?
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNIDOS]
Can I use your phone?
¿Puedo usar tu teléfono?
Yeah, the number for a Sidney Marks, please.
Sí, el número de un tal Sidney Marks, por favor.
"Heating device."
"Dispositivo de calefacción".
Radiator.
Radiador.
Five letters.
Cinco letras.
"Rdtor."
Yeah, is Sidney there?
Sí, ¿está Sidney?
Oh, this is?
Oh, ¿esta es?
- Sidney's a woman. - So she's a woman, so what?
- Sidney es una mujer. - Entonces es una mujer, ¿y qué?
Yeah, yeah, so what?
Sí, sí, ¿y qué?
Look, I live across the street...
Mira, vivo al otro lado de la calle...
...and I know all about you and your telescope.
...y sé todo sobre ti y tu telescopio.
And I don't appreciate it, okay?
Y no lo aprecio, ¿vale?
Yeah, I can see you right now. Hello?
Sí, te veo ahora mismo. ¿Hola?
Look, if I wanna walk around my apartment in my underwear...
Mira, si quiero andar por mi apartamento en ropa interior...
...I shouldn't have to feel like... Thank you.
...no debería sentirme así... Gracias.
That's not really the point.
Ese no es realmente el punto.
The point is, that...
El punto es que...
- Mostly free-weights, but occasionally... - Joey.
- Mayormente pesas libres, pero ocasionalmente... - Joey.
Yeah, my neighbor. Yeah, the brunette.
Sí, mi vecina. Sí, la morena.
She said you looked pretty that day in the green dress.
Dijo que te veías muy guapa ese día con el vestido verde.
The green dress? Really?
¿El vestido verde? ¿En serio?
She said you looked like Ingrid Bergman that day.
Dijo que te veías como Ingrid Bergman ese día.
Heh. No.
Je. No.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- You got a second? - Sure, sure.
- ¿Tienes un segundo? - Claro, claro.
Come on...
Vamos...
...in.
...dentro.
Hello, sweetheart.
Hola, cariño.
- What you guys doing here? - Uh, we are here to break up with you.
- ¿Qué hacen ustedes aquí? - Eh, hemos venido a romper contigo.
Both of you?
¿Los dos?
We think you're a horrible human being, and bad things should happen to you.
Creemos que eres un ser humano horrible y que te deberían pasar cosas malas.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. God, I am so sorry.
Lo siento. Lo siento. Dios, lo siento muchísimo.
I'm an idiot. I was weak. I couldn't help myself.
Soy un idiota. Fui débil. No pude evitarlo.
Whatever I did, I only did because I love you so much.
Lo que sea que hice, solo lo hice porque te amo tanto.
Uh, which one of us are you talking to there, Bar?
Uh, ¿con cuál de nosotras estás hablando, Bar?
Um...
Mindy.
Mindy, of course, Mindy. It was always Mindy.
Mindy, por supuesto, Mindy. Siempre fue Mindy.
Even when we were having sex in that chair?
¿Incluso cuando estábamos teniendo sexo en esa silla?
I swear, look, whatever I was doing, I was always thinking of you.
Lo juro, mira, hiciera lo que hiciera, siempre estaba pensando en ti.
Oh, please.
Oh, por favor.
During that second time, you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup.
Durante esa segunda vez, no podrías haberla identificado en una rueda de reconocimiento.
You did it twice?
¿Lo hiciste dos veces?
Well, the first time didn't really count. You know, it was Barry.
Bueno, la primera vez realmente no contó. Ya sabes, era Barry.
Oh, right.
Oh, claro.
Honey, baby, sweetheart, look...
Cariño, bebé, mi amor, mira...
Just give me another chance, okay?
Solo dame otra oportunidad, ¿sí?
We'll start all over again. We'll go back to Aruba.
Empezaremos todo de nuevo. Volveremos a Aruba.
What do you say?
¿Qué dices?
BERNICE [OVER INTERCOM]: Dr. Farber, we've got an emergency here.
BERNICE [POR INTERCOMUNICADOR]: Doctora Farber, tenemos una emergencia aquí.
Jason Castalano's choking on his retainer.
Jason Castalano se está ahogando con su retenedor.
Oh, God. Uh, I'll be right there, Bernice.
Oh, Dios. Uh, iré de inmediato, Bernice.
Look, please, please don't go anywhere, okay?
Mira, por favor, por favor no te vayas a ningún lado, ¿de acuerdo?
- I'll be right back. - Okay.
- Vuelvo enseguida. - De acuerdo.
Okay, and we'll be here, hating you.
Está bien, y nosotros estaremos aquí, odiándote.
See how he was sweating when he walked out of here?
¿Viste cómo sudaba cuando salió de aquí?
If I'm hogging the ball, you jump right in there...
Si estoy acaparando la pelota, tú te metes ahí...
...and take a couple of punches. Because I'm telling you, this feels great.
...y te llevas un par de golpes. Porque te digo, esto se siente genial.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.
Sí, estoy bastante segura de que todavía me voy a casar con él.
What are you talking about?
¿De qué estás hablando?
Mindy, the guy is the devil.
Mindy, el tipo es el diablo.
He is Satan in a smock.
Es Satanás con bata.
Look, I know he's not perfect.
Mira, sé que no es perfecto.
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNIDOS]
But the truth is, at the end of the day...
Pero la verdad es que, al final del día...
...I still really wanna be...
...todavía quiero mucho ser...
...Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber...
...la Sra. Dra. Barry Farber...
...D.D.S.
Oh, God.
Ay, Dios.
I hope you can find some way to be happy for me.
Espero que puedas encontrar una manera de alegrarte por mí.
And I hope you'll still be my maid of honor.
Y espero que sigas siendo mi dama de honor.
And I hope Barry doesn't kill you and eat you in Aruba.
Y espero que Barry no te mate y te devore en Aruba.
You okay?
¿Estás bien?
Yeah.
Sí.
Really?
¿En serio?
Yeah.
Sí.
You know, ever since I ran out on Barry at the wedding...
Sabes, desde que huí de Barry en la boda...
...I have wondered whether I made the right choice.
...me he preguntado si tomé la decisión correcta.
Oh. And now I know.
Oh. Y ahora lo sé.
MONICA: I'm so glad.
MONICA: Me alegro mucho.
Big day.
Gran día.
All right, I'll give you this: Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
Está bien, te concedo esto: el Sr. Peanut se viste mejor.
I mean, he's got the monocle, he's got the top hat...
Quiero decir, tiene el monóculo, tiene el sombrero de copa...
Did you know he's gay?
¿Sabías que es gay?
I just wanna clarify this. Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
Solo quiero aclarar esto. ¿Estás revelando que el Sr. Peanut es gay?
- Chandler? - Danielle, hi.
- ¿Chandler? - Danielle, hola.
Everybody, this is Danielle. Danielle, everybody.
Todos, ella es Danielle. Danielle, todos.
GROUP: Hi.
GRUPO: Hola.
- What are you doing here? - I've been calling you...
- ¿Qué haces aquí? - Te he estado llamando...
...but it turns out I had your number wrong.
...pero resulta que tenía tu número equivocado.
And when I finally got the right one from Information, there was no answer.
Y cuando finalmente conseguí el correcto en Información, no hubo respuesta.
So I thought I'd just come down here and make sure you were okay.
Así que pensé en venir aquí y asegurarme de que estabas bien.
Oh, uh, I'm okay.
Oh, eh, estoy bien.
Listen, uh, maybe we could get together later?
Escucha, eh, ¿quizás podríamos vernos más tarde?
That sounds good. I'll call you. Or you call me, whatever.
Suena bien. Te llamaré. O tú llámame, como sea.
- You know. - Ha, ha.
- Ya sabes. - Ja, ja.
- You got it. CHANDLER: Okay.
- Entendido. CHANDLER: De acuerdo.
- Bye, everybody. GROUP: Bye.
- Adiós a todos. GRUPO: Adiós.
Woo-hoo! Yeah, there you go.
¡Woo-hoo! Sí, ahí lo tienes.
Second date.
Segunda cita.
I don't know.
No sé.
RACHEL: You don't know?
RACHEL: ¿No lo sabes?
Oh, she seems nice, but that thing about her coming all the way here...
Oh, parece simpática, pero eso de que viniera hasta aquí...
...just to see if I was okay? I mean, how needy is that?
...¿solo para ver si estaba bien? Quiero decir, ¿qué tan necesitada es eso?
[ALL GROANING]
[TODOS GRUENEN]