PHOEBE: Oh, that's good.
PHOEBE: Oh, qué bien.
- Okay. All right, Phoebe? - Okay, okay.
— Vale. ¿Todo bien, Phoebe? — Vale, vale.
If I were omnipotent for a day, I would want, um, world peace...
Si fuera omnipotente por un día, querría, mmm, paz mundial...
...no more hunger, good things for the rain forest.
...no más hambre, cosas buenas para la selva tropical.
And bigger boobs.
Y un pecho más grande.
Well, see, you took mine, so...
Bueno, mira, te llevaste el mío, así que...
Chandler, what about you?
Chandler, ¿y tú?
If I were omnipotent for a day, I'd make myself omnipotent forever.
Si fuera omnipotente por un día, me haría omnipotente para siempre.
Heh. See, there's always one guy.
Je. Ya veo, siempre hay uno.
"If I had a wish, I'd wish for three more wishes."
"Si tuviera un deseo, desearía tres deseos más."
[ALL CHUCKLE]
[TODOS RÍEN]
ROSS & MONICA: Hey, Joey. - Hey, buddy.
ROSS Y MONICA: Hola, Joey. — Hola, amigo.
What would you do if you were omnipotent?
¿Qué harías si fueras omnipotente?
Probably kill myself.
Probablemente matarme.
Excuse me?
¿Perdón?
Hey, if Little Joey's dead, then I got no reason to live, you know?
Oye, si el pequeño Joey está muerto, entonces no tengo razón para vivir, ¿sabes?
Joey, uh, omnipotent.
Joey, eh, omnipotente.
You are?
¿Lo eres?
Ross, I'm...
Ross, yo...
How does she do that?
¿Cómo lo hace?
I cannot sleep in a public place.
No puedo dormir en un lugar público.
Would you look at her?
¿La has visto?
- She's so peaceful. - Yeah.
— Está tan tranquila. — Sí.
[BOTH SCREAM]
[AMBOS GRITAN]
What? What? Hi.
¿Qué? ¿Qué? Hola.
It's okay, you know. You just nodded off again.
Está bien, ya sabes. Te has vuelto a quedar dormida.
- Oh. - What's going on with you?
— Oh. — ¿Qué te pasa?
- I got no sleep last night. ROSS: Why?
— No dormí nada anoche. ROSS: ¿Por qué?
My grandmother has this new boyfriend...
Mi abuela tiene este nuevo novio...
...and they're both kind of insecure in bed, so...
...y ambos son un poco inseguros en la cama, así que...
And deaf.
Y sordos.
So they're constantly having to reassure each other that they're having a good time.
Así que constantemente tienen que asegurarse mutuamente de que se lo están pasando bien.
You have no idea how loud they are.
No tienes idea de lo ruidosos que son.
- You can stay with Rachel and me tonight. - Thanks.
— Puedes quedarte con Rachel y conmigo esta noche. — Gracias.
Ninety-five, 96, 97.
Noventa y cinco, noventa y seis, noventa y siete.
See, I told you. Less than 100 steps from our place to here.
¿Ves? Te lo dije. Menos de 100 pasos desde nuestro sitio hasta aquí.
You got way too much free time, man.
Tienes demasiado tiempo libre, tío.
Hey, there's the birthday boy.
Oye, ahí está el cumpleañero.
Ross, check it out. Hockey tickets.
Ross, mira. Entradas de hockey.
Rangers-Penguins tonight at the Garden. We're taking you.
Rangers contra Penguins esta noche en el Garden. Te llevamos.
- Happy birthday, pal. - We love you, man.
— Feliz cumpleaños, amigo. — Te queremos, tío.
[ROSS CHUCKLES]
[ROSS RÍE]
It's funny, my birthday was seven months ago.
Es curioso, mi cumpleaños fue hace siete meses.
- So? - So I'm guessing you had an extra ticket...
— ¿Y? — Y supongo que tenías una entrada extra...
...and couldn't decide which one of you got to bring a date? Huh?
...¿y no podías decidir cuál de los dos traía a una cita? ¿Eh?
Well, aren't we Mr. The-Glass-is-Half-Empty?
Bueno, ¿no somos nosotros el Sr. "El vaso está medio vacío"?
Oh, my God. Oh.
Oh, Dios mío. Oh.
Is today the 20th? October 20th?
¿Es hoy el 20? ¿20 de octubre?
- I was hoping you wouldn't remember. - Oh.
— Esperaba que no lo recordaras. — Oh.
What's wrong with the 20th?
¿Qué pasa con el 20?
Eleven days before Halloween? All the good costumes are gone?
¿Once días antes de Halloween? ¿Ya se acabaron los buenos disfraces?
Today's the day Carol and I...
Hoy es el día en que Carol y yo...
...first consummated...
...consumamos por primera vez...
...our physical relationship.
...nuestra relación física.
We had sex.
Tuvimos sexo.
You know what? I better pass on the game.
¿Saben qué? Mejor paso del partido.
I think I'm just gonna go home and think about my ex-wife and her lesbian lover.
Creo que iré a casa a pensar en mi exesposa y su novia lesbiana.
The hell with hockey. Let's all do that.
Al diablo con el hockey. Hagamos eso todos.
Come on, Ross. You, me, Joey, ice?
Vamos, Ross. ¿Tú, yo, Joey, patinar?
Guys' night out? Come on, what do you say, big guy?
¿Noche de chicos? Vamos, ¿qué dices, grandulón?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
¿Eh? ¿Eh? ¿Eh?
- What are you doing? - I have no idea.
- ¿Qué haces? - Ni idea.
Come on, Ross.
Vamos, Ross.
All right, all right. Maybe it will take my mind off it.
Está bien, está bien. Tal vez me distraiga.
- You promise to buy me a big foam finger? JOEY: You got it.
- ¿Prometes comprarme un dedo gigante de espuma? JOEY: Trato hecho.
- All right. - Look, look, look. My first paycheck.
- De acuerdo. - Mira, mira, mira. Mi primer sueldo.
[ALL CHATTERING]
[TODOS HABLANDO]
Look at the window. There's my name. Hi, me.
Mira por la ventana. Ahí está mi nombre. Hola, yo.
I remember the day I got my first paycheck.
Recuerdo el día que recibí mi primer sueldo.
There was a cave-in in one of the mines, and eight people were killed.
Hubo un derrumbe en una de las minas y murieron ocho personas.
Wow, you worked in a mine?
¿Guau, trabajabas en una mina?
No, I worked at a Dairy Queen. Why?
No, trabajaba en un Dairy Queen. ¿Por qué?
God, isn't this exciting? I earned this.
Dios, ¿no es emocionante? Me lo gané.
I wiped tables for it. I steamed milk for it.
Limpié mesas por él. Calenté leche por él.
And it was totally...
Y no valió la pena...
...not worth it.
...en absoluto.
Who's FICA? Why's he getting all my money?
¿Quién es FICA? ¿Por qué se lleva todo mi dinero?
I mean, what...? Chandler, look at that.
O sea, ¿qué...? Chandler, mira eso.
Oh, this is not that bad.
Oh, no está tan mal.
Oh, you're fine, yeah, for a first job.
Oh, estás bien, sí, para ser un primer trabajo.
- You can totally, totally live on this. MONICA: Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Puedes vivir totalmente, totalmente de esto. MONICA: Oh, sí, sí.
By the way, great service today.
Por cierto, gran servicio hoy.
- Ooh. - Oh, yeah.
- Ooh. - Oh, sí.
MONICA: Terrific. - It was excellent.
MONICA: Fantástico. - Fue excelente.
CHANDLER: Unbelievable. And all that milk and stuff? Great.
CHANDLER: Increíble. ¿Y toda esa leche y eso? Genial.
CHANDLER & JOEY: Hockey. - Hockey. Hockey.
CHANDLER Y JOEY: ¡Hockey! - Hockey. Hockey.
CHANDLER & JOEY: Hockey. - Hockey. Hockey. Hockey.
CHANDLER Y JOEY: ¡Hockey! - Hockey. Hockey. Hockey.
Rachel?
¿Rachel?
[GASPS]
[JADEOS]
Oh, my God!
¡Oh, Dios mío!
[ALL SHRIEKING]
[TODOS GRITANDO]
I swear I've seen birds do this on Wild Kingdom.
Juro que he visto pájaros hacer eso en Wild Kingdom.
What are you guys doing here?
¿Qué hacen ustedes aquí?
Well, we were in the city shopping, and your mom said you work here...
Bueno, estábamos comprando en la ciudad y tu mamá dijo que trabajas aquí...
...and it's true.
...y es verdad.
Yeah.
Sí.
Look at you in the apron. You look like you're in a play.
Mírate con el delantal. Pareces de una obra de teatro.
God, look at you. You are so big. I can't believe it.
Dios, mírate. Estás tan grande. No puedo creerlo.
I know, I know. I'm a duplex.
Lo sé, lo sé. Soy un dúplex.
RACHEL: So, what's going on with you?
RACHEL: Entonces, ¿qué hay de ti?
Well, guess who my dad's making partner in his firm.
Bueno, ¿adivina quién va a hacer socio en la firma de mi papá?
[ALL SHRIEK]
[TODOS GRITAN]
And while we're on the subject of news...
Y ya que estamos hablando de noticias...
[ALL SHRIEK]
[TODOS GRITAN]
Look, look. I have elbows.
Mira, mira. Tengo codos.
[BOTH SHRIEK]
[AMBOS GRITAN]
Passes it up to Leetch.
Se la pasa a Leetch.
Leetch spots Messier in the crease. Here's the pass.
Leetch ve a Messier en la zona. Aquí está el pase.
Oh. Oh.
We'll take a time-out while Messier stops to look at some women's shoes.
Tomaremos un tiempo muerto mientras Messier se detiene a mirar unos zapatos de mujer.
Carol was wearing boots just like those the night that we first...
Carol usaba botas como esas la noche que nos conocimos...
...you know.
...ya sabes.
In fact, she, uh...
De hecho, ella, eh...
She never took them off. Ha, ha.
Nunca se las quitó. Ja, ja.
It's because we... Sorry. Sorry.
Es porque nosotros... Perdón. Perdón.
I can't believe...
No puedo creer...
[ROSS SIGHS]
[ROSS SUSPIRA]
- What? - Peach pit.
- ¿Qué? - Hueso de durazno.
Yes, bunny?
Sí, conejita?
Peach pit.
Hueso de durazno.
- That night, we, uh, had... - Peaches?
- Esa noche, nosotros, eh, tuvimos... - ¿Duraznos?
Actually, nectarines, but basically.
En realidad, nectarinas, pero básicamente.
- Could've been a peach. - Then we, uh...
- Pudo haber sido un durazno. - Entonces nosotros, eh...
Then we got dressed and I walked her to...
Entonces nos vestimos y la acompañé a...
...the bus stop.
...la parada del autobús.
I'm fine.
Estoy bien.
Hey, that woman's got an ass like Carol's.
Oye, esa mujer tiene un trasero como el de Carol.
What? I thought we were trying to find stuff.
¿Qué? Pensé que estábamos buscando cosas.
Oh, come on, you guys. Tell me all the dirt.
Ay, vamos, díganme todos los chismes.
Well, the biggest news is still you dumping Barry at the altar.
Bueno, la noticia más grande sigue siendo tú dejando a Barry en el altar.
- All right, let's talk reality for a second. - Okay.
- Está bien, hablemos de la realidad por un segundo. - De acuerdo.
- When are you coming home? - What?
- ¿Cuándo vienes a casa? - ¿Qué?
Guys, I'm not.
Chicas, no voy a.
- Heh. Come on. This is us. - I'm not.
- Heh. Vamos. Somos nosotros. - No voy a.
This is what I'm doing now. I've got this job.
Esto es lo que estoy haciendo ahora. Tengo este trabajo.
Waitressing?
¿De camarera?
Heh. I'm not just waitressing.
Heh. No solo soy camarera.
I mean, I'm...
Quiero decir, yo...
I, um...
Yo, um...
I write the specials on the specials board.
Escribo los especiales en la pizarra de especiales.
And I take the dead flowers out of the vase.
Y quito las flores muertas del jarrón.
Um, oh, and sometimes Arturo lets me put the little chocolate blobbies on the cookies.
Um, oh, y a veces Arturo me deja poner las bolitas de chocolate en las galletas.
Well, your mom didn't tell us about the blobbies.
Bueno, tu mamá no nos contó sobre las bolitas.
[WHIRRING]
[ZUMBIDO]
MONICA: Hey, Rach. How was it with your friends?
MONICA: Oye, Rach. ¿Cómo te fue con tus amigas?
[MONICA & PHOEBE SHRIEK]
[MONICA Y PHOEBE GRITAN]
Okay, how would you like some Tiki Death Punch?
Está bien, ¿qué tal si les sirvo un "Puñetazo Mortal Tiki"?
What's that?
¿Qué es eso?
- Well, it's rum and... - Okay.
- Bueno, es ron y... - De acuerdo.
We thought since Phoebe's staying over we'd have a slumber party.
Pensamos que como Phoebe se queda a dormir, tendríamos una fiesta de pijamas.
We got some trashy magazines, we got cookie dough, we got Twister.
Tenemos revistas baratas, tenemos masa para galletas, tenemos Twister.
[PHONE RINGS]
[SUENA EL TELÉFONO]
Ooh, ooh. And I brought Operation.
Ooh, ooh. Y traje Operation.
But I lost the tweezers, so we can't operate.
Pero perdí las pinzas, así que no podemos operar.
But we can prep the guy.
Pero podemos preparar al tipo.
Rach, it's the Visa-card people.
Rach, son los de la tarjeta Visa.
Oh, God. Ask them what they want.
Oh, Dios. Pregúntales qué quieren.
Could you please tell me what this is in reference to?
¿Podrías decirme a qué se refiere esto?
Yes, hold on.
Sí, espera un momento.
Um, they say there's been unusual activity on your account.
Mmm, dicen que ha habido actividad inusual en tu cuenta.
- But I haven't used my card in weeks. - That is the unusual activity.
Pero si no he usado mi tarjeta en semanas. - Esa es la actividad inusual.
They just wanna see if you're okay.
Solo quieren ver si estás bien.
They wanna know if I'm okay?
¿Quieren saber si estoy bien?
Okay, they wanna know if I'm okay. Okay, let's see.
Okay, quieren saber si estoy bien. Okay, veamos.
Well, let's see. The FICA guys took all my money.
Bueno, veamos. Los del IRS se llevaron todo mi dinero.
Everyone I know is either getting married or getting pregnant or getting promoted...
Todos los que conozco se están casando, o quedando embarazadas, o ascendiendo...
...and I'm getting coffee.
...y yo estoy sirviendo café.
And it's not even for me.
Y ni siquiera es para mí.
So if that sounds like I'm okay, okay, then you can tell them I'm okay. Okay?
Así que si eso suena a que estoy bien, okay, entonces puedes decirles que estoy bien. ¿Okay?
Uh, Rachel has left the building.
Uh, Rachel ha salido del edificio.
- Can you call back? - All right. Come on.
- ¿Puedes devolver la llamada? - De acuerdo. Vamos.
[IN STRAINED VOICE] Let's play Twister.
[CON VOZ FORZADA] Juguemos Twister.
["CHARGE" PLAYING ON SPEAKERS]
["CHARGE" SONANDO EN LOS ALTAVOCES]
- Sorry. - Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- Perdón. - Perdón, perdón, perdón.
Uh-oh.
What? There was ice there that night with Carol?
¿Qué? ¿Hubo hielo esa noche con Carol?
Plastic seats? Four thousand angry Pittsburgh fans?
¿Asientos de plástico? ¿Cuatro mil fans furiosos de Pittsburgh?
No, actually, I was just saying it looks like we're not sitting together.
No, en realidad, solo estaba diciendo que parece que no vamos a sentarnos juntos.
But now that you mention it, there was ice there that night.
Pero ya que lo mencionas, sí hubo hielo esa noche.
It was the first frost.
Fue la primera helada.
- We were... - Sit. Just sit down. Sit.
- Estábamos... - Siéntate. Solo siéntate. Siéntate.
You should feel great.
Deberías sentirte genial.
You're doing this amazing independent thing.
Estás haciendo esta cosa independiente increíble.
Monica, what is so amazing?
Monica, ¿qué tiene de increíble?
I gave up like everything. And for what?
Lo dejé todo. ¿Y para qué?
You are just like Jack.
Eres igual que Jack.
Jack from downstairs?
¿Jack de abajo?
No, Jack and the Beanstalk.
No, Jack y las habichuelas mágicas.
- Ah, the other Jack. - Yeah, right.
- Ah, el otro Jack. - Sí, claro.
See, he gave up something, but then he got those magic beans.
Mira, él renunció a algo, pero luego consiguió esas habichuelas mágicas.
And then he woke up and there was this big plant...
Y luego se despertó y había una planta enorme...
...outside of his window, full of possibilities and stuff.
...fuera de su ventana, llena de posibilidades y cosas.
And he lived in a village, and you live in the Village.
Y él vivía en un pueblo, y tú vives en el Village.
Okay, but, Pheebs, Pheebs, Jack gave up a cow.
Okay, pero, Pheebs, Pheebs, Jack renunció a una vaca.
I gave up an orthodontist.
Yo renuncié a un ortodoncista.
Okay, I know I didn't love him, but...
Okay, sé que no lo quería, pero...
Oh, see, Jack did love the cow.
Oh, mira, Jack sí quería a la vaca.
But, see, it was a plan, you know? It was clear.
Pero, mira, era un plan, ¿sabes? Estaba claro.
Everything was figured out, and now everything's just kind of like...
Todo estaba planeado, y ahora todo es como...
- Flupie? - Yeah.
- ¿Flupie? - Sí.
You're not the only one. We don't know where we're going.
No eres el único. No sabemos a dónde vamos.
You gotta figure, at some point, it's gonna come together...
Tienes que pensar que, en algún momento, todo se va a juntar...
...and it's just gonna be "unflupie."
...y simplemente será "unflupie".
Yeah, like that's a word.
Sí, como si esa fuera una palabra.
Okay, but, Monica, what if it doesn't come together?
Okay, pero, Monica, ¿y si no se junta?
Pheebs?
¿Pheebs?
Well, because you just... I don't like this question.
Bueno, porque tú solo... No me gusta esta pregunta.
Okay, see? See, you guys? What if we don't get magic beans?
Okay, ¿ven? ¿Ven, chicos? ¿Y si no conseguimos frijoles mágicos?
I mean, what if all we've got are...
Quiero decir, ¿y si lo único que tenemos son...
...beans?
...frijoles?
Get him! Get him! Get him!
¡Agárrenlo! ¡Agárrenlo! ¡Agárrenlo!
Get... Yes! You're not laughing now, are you, pal?
¡Agárra... ¡Sí! Ya no te ríes, ¿verdad, amigo?
That's all you need, a bunch of toothless guys hitting each other with sticks.
Eso es todo lo que necesitas, un montón de tipos desdentados golpeándose con palos.
Pass it. Pass it.
Pásala. Pásala.
CHANDLER: He's open, he's open. Shoot it, shoot it, shoot it!
CHANDLER: Está abierto, está abierto. ¡Tírala, tírala, tírala!
[ROSS GROANS]
[ROSS SE QUEJA]
- Whoa. Oh. - Whoa.
- ¡Whoa! Oh. - ¡Whoa!
- Hey, look, we're on that TV thing. - Ooh, ooh, ooh.
- Oye, mira, salimos en esa cosa de la tele. - Ooh, ooh, ooh.
- I got it! - Hey, hey, we got it! Hey!
- ¡Lo tengo! - ¡Oye, oye, lo tenemos! ¡Oye!
Excuse me.
Disculpe.
It says to call this number if you're not completely satisfied with this candy bar.
Dice que llames a este número si no estás completamente satisfecho con esta barra de chocolate.
Well, I'm not completely satisfied.
Bueno, no estoy completamente satisfecho.
Listen, it's kind of an emergency.
Escucha, es una especie de emergencia.
I guess you'd know that, or we'd be in the predicament room.
Supongo que lo sabrías, o estaríamos en la sala de urgencias.
[CHANDLER CHUCKLES]
[CHANDLER SE RÍE]
Hold on. Fill these out. Sit over there.
Espera. Llenen esto. Siéntense allá.
ROSS: Look, I don't wanna make any trouble, okay?
ROSS: Mira, no quiero causar problemas, ¿okay?
But I'm in a lot of pain here, all right? My face is dented.
Pero tengo mucho dolor aquí, ¿de acuerdo? Tengo la cara abollada.
- Well, you'll have to wait your turn. - Well, how long do you think it'll be?
- Bueno, tendrás que esperar tu turno. - Bueno, ¿cuánto crees que tardará?
Any minute now.
En cualquier momento.
[LAUGHS]
[RÍE]
ROSS: Hey, listen... Ooh.
ROSS: Oye, escucha... Ooh.
[MELANCHOLY POP SONG PLAYING ON STEREO]
[SONIDO DE POP MELANCÓLICO SONANDO EN EL ESTÉREO]
I wake up and I start to cry
Me despierto y empiezo a llorar
Ain't no hope in...
No hay esperanza en...
Oh. I'm so sorry, you guys. I didn't mean to bring you down.
Oh. Lo siento mucho, chicos. No quise deprimirlos.
No, you were right.
No, tenías razón.
I don't have a plan.
No tengo un plan.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
MAN: Pizza guy.
HOMBRE: Chico de la pizza.
- Thank God. - Food.
- Gracias a Dios. - Comida.
- Phoebe? PHOEBE: What?
- ¿Phoebe? PHOEBE: ¿Qué?
- Do you have a plan? - I don't even have a "pla."
- ¿Tienes un plan? - Ni siquiera tengo un "pla".
Hi. One mushroom, green pepper and onion?
Hola. ¿Una de champiñones, pimiento verde y cebolla?
No, no, no. That's not what we ordered.
No, no, no. Eso no es lo que pedimos.
We ordered a fat-free crust with extra cheese.
Pedimos una masa sin grasa con extra queso.
- Wait, you're not G. Stephanopoulos? - No.
- Espera, ¿tú no eres G. Stephanopoulos? - No.
- Oh, man. My dad's gonna kill me. - Wait.
- Oh, hombre. Mi papá me va a matar. - Espera.
Did you say G. Stephanopoulos?
¿Dijiste G. Stephanopoulos?
Yeah, this one goes across the street. I must have given him yours.
Sí, esta va para la casa de enfrente. Debí darle la tuya.
Oh, bonehead. Bonehead.
Ay, cabeza hueca. Cabeza hueca.
Wait, was this a small Mediterranean guy with curiously intelligent good looks?
Espera, ¿era un tipo mediterráneo bajito con un atractivo curiosamente inteligente?
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Sí, eso suena bien.
- Was he wearing a stunning blue suit? - And a power tie?
- ¿Llevaba un traje azul espectacular? - ¿Y una corbata de poder?
No, pretty much just a towel.
No, prácticamente solo una toalla.
- Oh, God. - Oh. Oh.
- Ay, Dios. - Oh. Oh.
- Oh, my God. - You want me to take this back?
- Dios mío. - ¿Quieres que lo devuelva?
What? Are you nuts? We've got George Stephanopoulos' pizza.
¿Qué? ¿Estás loco? Tenemos la pizza de George Stephanopoulos.
Here.
Aquí.
- Uh, Pheebs? - Yeah?
- Eh, Pheebs? - ¿Sí?
Who's George Snuffleupagus?
¿Quién es George Snuffleupagus?
That's Big Bird's friend.
Es el amigo de Epi.
[LAUGHS]
[RÍE]
I see pizza.
Veo pizza.
PHOEBE: Oh, I wanna see. Let me see. Let me see.
PHOEBE: Oh, quiero ver. Déjame ver. Déjame ver.
Hello? Who are we spying on?
¿Hola? ¿A quién estamos espiando?
You know the White House adviser? Clinton's campaign guy?
¿Conoces al asesor de la Casa Blanca? ¿El de la campaña de Clinton?
The one with the great hair, sexy smile, really cute butt?
¿El del pelo genial, sonrisa sexy, trasero súper lindo?
Oh, him. The little guy. Oh, I love him.
Oh, él. El chiquito. Oh, me encanta.
Ooh. Oh, wait. Wait, I see a woman.
Ooh. Oh, espera. Espera, veo a una mujer.
Tell me it's his mother.
Dime que es su madre.
- Definitely not his mother. - Oh, no.
- Definitivamente no es su madre. - Oh, no.
Oh, wait, she's walking across the floor.
Oh, espera, está cruzando el piso.
She's walking, she's walking.
Está caminando, está caminando.
She's going for the pizza. Hey, that's not for you, bitch!
Va por la pizza. ¡Oye, eso no es para ti, perra!
WOMAN [OVER PA]: Dr. Max to Center 456.
MUJER [POR ALTAVOZ]: Dra. Max al Centro 456.
Dr. Max to Center 456.
Dra. Max al Centro 456.
[WHOOSHES]
[SONIDO DE AIRE]
Excuse me. We've been here for over an hour...
Disculpe. Hemos estado aquí por más de una hora...
...and people less sick than my friend have gone in.
...y han entrado personas menos enfermas que mi amiga.
I mean, that guy with the toe thing? Who's he sleeping with?
Quiero decir, ¿ese tipo con el problema del dedo del pie? ¿Con quién está durmiendo?
Oh, come on, Dora. Don't be mad.
Ay, vamos, Dora. No te enojes.
I know we both said some things...
Sé que ambas dijimos cosas...
...we didn't mean...
...que no queríamos decir...
...but that doesn't mean we still don't love each other.
...pero eso no significa que todavía no nos amemos.
You know, I feel like I've lost her.
Sabes, siento que la he perdido.
[YELLS]
[GRITA]
- Lights still out? - Yeah.
- ¿Sigue sin luz? - Sí.
Well, maybe they're napping.
Bueno, tal vez están echando una siesta.
Heh. Please. They're having sex.
Je. Por favor. Están teniendo sexo.
MONICA & PHOEBE: Shut up.
MONICA Y PHOEBE: Cállate.
So, what do you think George is like?
Entonces, ¿cómo crees que es George?
- I think he's shy. - Oh, yeah?
- Creo que es tímido. - ¿Ah, sí?
Yeah. I think you have to draw him out.
Sí. Creo que tienes que sacarlo.
And then when you do, he's a preppy animal.
Y luego, cuando lo haces, es un animal preppy.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[TODOS RÍEN]
Come on.
Vamos.
I remember the moonlight coming in through the open window...
Recuerdo la luz de la luna entrando por la ventana abierta...
...and her face had the most incredible glow.
...y su rostro tenía el brillo más increíble.
Yes, the moon, the glow, the magical feeling.
Sí, la luna, el brillo, la sensación mágica.
You did this part.
[ERROR API]
Could I get some painkillers over here, please?
He's right, enough already. What is the big deal about today?
[ERROR API]
So you slept with her for the first time. So what?
You slept with her for seven years after that.
[ERROR API]
It's just a little more complicated than that.
What? What is it? That she left you? That she likes women?
[ERROR API]
That she left you for a woman that likes women?
A little louder.
[ERROR API]
There's a man on the 12th floor in a coma who didn't quite hear you.
Then what?
[ERROR API]
My first time with Carol was...
Was my...
[ERROR API]
[MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY]
What?
¿Qué?
It was my first...
[ERROR API]
...time.
With Carol?
[ERROR API]
Oh.
So in your whole life, you've only been with one?
[ERROR API]
Oh.
Oh, boy. Hockey was a big mistake.
[ERROR API]
There's a whole bunch of stuff we could've done tonight.
Okay. Okay, I got one.
[ERROR API]
Do you remember that vegetarian pâté that I made that you loved so much?
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
[MONICA & RACHEL GIGGLE]
[ERROR API]
Well, unless goose is a vegetable...
- Oh! Oh! MONICA & RACHEL: Ha-ha-ha.
[ERROR API]
Okay, fine, fine.
Now I don't feel so bad about sleeping with Jason Hurley.
[ERROR API]
- What? You slept with Jason? - You had already broken up.
- How long? - Just a couple hours.
[ERROR API]
Oh, that's nice.
Okay, okay, okay, I got one.
[ERROR API]
Anyway.
The valentine Tommy Rollerson left in your locker was really from me.
[ERROR API]
Excuse me?
¿Perdón?
Oh, hello? Like he was really gonna send you one.
[ERROR API]
She was a big girl.
[LAUGHS]
[RÍE]
Really?
¿En serio?
Well, at least big girls don't pee in their pants in seventh grade.
[ERROR API]
I was laughing. You made me laugh.
Oh, my God. There he is. There he is. There he is.
[ERROR API]
- Where? - Right where we've been looking all night.
- Oh, he's so cute. - Oh, George, baby, drop the towel.
[ERROR API]
- Come on, drop the towel. RACHEL & PHOEBE: Drop the towel.
MONICA: Please drop the towel. Drop it.
[ERROR API]
ALL: Wow.
Man, can you believe he's only had sex with one woman?
[ERROR API]
I think it's great.
You know, it's sweet. It's romantic.
[ERROR API]
Really?
¿En serio?
No, are you kidding? The guy's a freak. I judge him.
[ERROR API]
- Hey, man. - Hey, buddy.
ROSS: Ah? Ah?
[ERROR API]
Oh.
That's attractive.
[ERROR API]
Oh, I thought you were great in Silence of the Lambs.
[JOEY LAUGHING]
[JOEY RIENDO]
Oh, come on, admit it, all things considered, you had fun tonight.
[ERROR API]
Fun? Where was the fun?
Tell me specifically, which part was the fun part?
[ERROR API]
Where's my puck?
- Oh. The kid has it. - The kid?
[ERROR API]
Ahem. Excuse me, uh, that's my puck.
I found it. Finders keepers, losers weepers.
[ERROR API]
You gotta do it, man.
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm rubber, you're glue. Whatever you...
[ERROR API]
I can't do it.
- Listen, uh, give me back my puck. - No.
[ERROR API]
- Yes, how about? - No.
- No, come here. Just give me my puck. - No, no, no.
[ERROR API]
SIZEMORE: Hey, no roughhousing in my ER.
Give me my puck! Unh.
[ERROR API]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNIDOS]
Now, that was fun.
[ERROR API]
ROSS: Okay, Monica.
Right foot, red.
[ERROR API]
Could've played Monopoly, but no.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
Thanks.
Gracias.
Okay, Pheebs. Right hand, blue.
[ERROR API]
- Good. JOEY: Hmm?
[PHONE RINGS]
[SUENA EL TELÉFONO]
Hello?
¿Hola?
- Oh. Rachel, it's the Visa-card people. RACHEL: Oh, okay. Will you take my place?
[ERROR API]
All right. Yes, this is Rachel.
RACHEL: No. - Oh.
[ERROR API]
Hello?
¿Hola?
Oh, yeah. No, I know. I haven't been using it much.
[ERROR API]
Oh, well, thanks, but I'm okay, really.
To the green, to the green.
[ERROR API]
MONICA: Oh, no. - To the green.
I've got magic beans.
[ERROR API]
No, no, never mind.
CHANDLER: To the left. To the left.
[ERROR API]
[ALL YELL]
I'm fine.
Estoy bien.