This is unbelievable. It's been half an hour.
Esto es increíble. Ha pasado media hora.
If this was a cartoon, you'd be looking like a ham right about now.
Si esto fuera un dibujo animado, ahora mismo parecerías un jamón.
There's the waitress. Excuse me, miss.
Ahí está la camarera. Disculpe, señorita.
JOEY: Hello, miss? - It's Phoebe.
JOEY: ¿Hola, señorita? - Soy Phoebe.
CHANDLER: Hi. - Hi.
CHANDLER: Hola. - Hola.
Okay, will that be all?
¿De acuerdo, será todo?
Wait, wait. What are you doing here?
Espera, espera. ¿Qué haces aquí?
Yeah, um, I was over there...
Sí, eh, estaba por allá...
...then you said, "Excuse me, miss." So now I'm here.
...y entonces dijiste: "Disculpe, señorita". Así que ahora estoy aquí.
No, no. How come you're working here?
No, no. ¿Cómo es que trabajas aquí?
Right. Because it's close to where I live, and the aprons are really cute.
Correcto. Porque está cerca de donde vivo, y los delantales son muy lindos.
Can we start over?
¿Podemos empezar de nuevo?
- Yeah. Okay, great. I'll be over here. - No, no, no, no.
- Sí. De acuerdo, genial. Estaré por aquí. - No, no, no, no.
I don't know whether he's testing me or just acting out...
No sé si me está poniendo a prueba o simplemente actuando...
...but my monkey is out of control.
...pero mi mono está fuera de control.
He keeps erasing the messages on my machine.
Sigue borrando los mensajes de mi contestador.
Supposedly by accident.
Supuestamente por accidente.
Oh, yeah, I've done that.
Oh, sí, he hecho eso.
And three days in a row, he got to the newspaper before I did...
Y tres días seguidos, llegó al periódico antes que yo...
...and peed all over the crossword.
...y se orinó en todo el crucigrama.
I've never done that.
Yo nunca he hecho eso.
Now tell me she doesn't look exactly like her sister.
Ahora dime que no se parece exactamente a su hermana.
I'm saying I see a difference.
Digo que veo una diferencia.
They're twins.
Son gemelas.
I don't care. Phoebe's Phoebe. Ursula's hot.
No me importa. Phoebe es Phoebe. Ursula está buena.
You know that thing when we talk about things?
¿Sabes eso que hacemos cuando hablamos de cosas?
- Let's not do that anymore. - Okay.
- Dejemos de hacer eso. - De acuerdo.
ROSS: Hey, guys. ALL: Hey.
ROSS: Hola, chicos. TODOS: Hola.
Hey, Pheebs. Guess who we saw today.
Hola, Pheebs. Adivina a quién vimos hoy.
Ooh. Oh, fun. Okay.
Ooh. Oh, qué divertido. De acuerdo.
- Um, Liam Neeson. - No.
- Eh, Liam Neeson. - No.
- Morley Safer. JOEY: Nope.
- Morley Safer. JOEY: No.
- The woman who cuts my hair. JOEY: No.
- La mujer que me corta el pelo. JOEY: No.
Look, this could be a really long game.
Mira, este podría ser un juego muy largo.
Your sister, Ursula.
Tu hermana, Ursula.
- Oh, really? - Yeah.
- ¿Ah, sí? - Sí.
She works at that place, uh...
Trabaja en ese lugar, eh...
Riff's. Yeah, I know.
Riff's. Sí, lo sé.
Oh, you do? She said you guys haven't talked in years.
¿Ah, sí? Dijo que ustedes no se hablaban en años.
Hmm? Yeah.
¿Mmm? Sí.
So, um, is she fat?
Entonces, eh, ¿está gorda?
Not from where I was standing.
No desde donde yo estaba parada.
Where were you standing?
¿Dónde estabas parada?
Uh, Pheebs, so you guys just don't get along?
Eh, Pheebs, ¿así que ustedes simplemente no se llevan bien?
It's mostly just dumb sister stuff, you know?
Son mayormente cosas tontas de hermanas, ¿sabes?
Everyone always thought of her as the pretty one.
Todos siempre la consideraron la bonita.
Oh. Oh. She was the first to walk...
Oh. Oh. Fue la primera en caminar...
...even though I did it later that same day.
...aunque yo lo hice más tarde ese mismo día.
To my parents, by then it was, "Yeah, what else is new?"
Para mis padres, para entonces era: "Sí, ¿qué más hay de nuevo?"
ROSS: Oh.
Pheebs, I'm sorry. I've gotta go. I've got Lamaze class.
Pheebs, lo siento. Tengo que irme. Tengo clase de Lamaze.
Oh, and I've got earth science, but I'll catch you in gym?
Oh, y tengo ciencias de la Tierra, ¿pero te veo en gimnasia?
So is this just gonna be you and Carol?
Entonces, ¿serán solo tú y Carol?
No. Susan will be there too.
No. Susan también estará allí.
We've got dads. We've got lesbians. The whole parenting team.
Tenemos papás. Tenemos lesbianas. Todo el equipo de crianza.
Well, isn't that gonna be weird?
Bueno, ¿eso no será raro?
No. It might have been at first...
No. Pudo haber sido al principio...
...but now I'm comfortable with the situation.
...pero ahora estoy cómoda con la situación.
- Ross, that's my jacket. - I know.
- Ross, esa es mi chaqueta. - Lo sé.
Hi. We're the Rostens.
Hola. Somos los Rostens.
I'm J.C. And he's Michael.
Soy J.C. Y él es Michael.
And we're having a boy and a girl.
Y vamos a tener un niño y una niña.
Good for you. Alrighty, next?
Bien por ti. Muy bien, ¿siguiente?
Hi. Um, I'm, uh... Ahem.
Hola. Eh, soy, eh... Ejem.
I'm Ross Geller.
Soy Ross Geller.
And, uh, that's my boy in there.
Y, eh, ese es mi hijo ahí dentro.
And, uh, this is Carol Willick, and this is Susan Bunch.
Y, eh, esta es Carol Willick, y esta es Susan Bunch.
Susan is, um, Carol's...
Susan es, eh, la... de Carol
[MUMBLES]
[MURMULLOS]
Who's next?
¿Quién sigue?
I'm sorry, Susan is?
¿Lo siento, Susan es?
- Susan is Carol's friend. - Life partner.
- Susan es amiga de Carol. - Pareja de vida.
Like buddies.
Como amigas.
Like lovers.
Como amantes.
You know how close women can get.
Ya sabes lo unidas que pueden estar las mujeres.
- Susan and I live together. - I was married to her.
- Susan y yo vivimos juntas. - Yo estuve casada con ella.
- Carol. Not me. - It's a little complicated.
- Carol. Yo no. - Es un poco complicado.
- But we're fine. - Absolutely.
- Pero estamos bien. - Absolutamente.
So, twins. Ha.
Entonces, gemelos. Ja.
That's like two births.
Eso son como dos nacimientos.
Ouch.
Auch.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
[ZUMBIDO DEL INTERCOMUNICADOR]
[MIMICS INTERCOM BUZZING] - To you too, Helen.
[IMITA ZUMBIDO DEL INTERCOMUNICADOR] - A ti también, Helen.
HELEN [OVER INTERCOM]: Nina Bookbinder is here to see you.
HELEN [POR INTERCOMUNICADOR]: Nina Bookbinder está aquí para verte.
Oh. Okay, send her in.
Oh. De acuerdo, hazla pasar.
Hi.
Hola.
- Hi, Nina. Come on in. - You wanted to see me?
- Hola, Nina. Pasa. - ¿Querías verme?
Uh, yes. Uh, I was just going over your data.
Eh, sí. Eh, estaba revisando tus datos.
You've been postdating your Friday numbers.
Has estado poniendo fechas posteriores a tus números del viernes.
Which is bad, because?
¿Lo cual es malo, por qué?
- Well, it throws my WENUS out of whack. - Ha, ha.
- Bueno, me desajusta mi WENUS. - Ja, ja.
Excuse me?
¿Perdón?
WENUS. Ahem.
WENUS. Ejem.
- Weekly Estimated... - Oh, Net Usage Statistics.
- Estimación Semanal... - Oh, Estadísticas de Uso Neto.
Right. Gotcha, gotcha.
Correcto. Entendido, entendido.
Won't happen again. I wouldn't want to do anything to hurt your...
No volverá a pasar. No querría hacer nada para dañar tu...
...WENUS.
It's not just that she's cute, okay? It's just that...
No es solo que sea linda, ¿de acuerdo? Es solo que...
...she's really, really cute.
...es realmente, realmente linda.
It doesn't matter. You don't dip your pen in the company ink.
No importa. No metas la pluma en la tinta de la empresa.
Ross.
Your little creature's got the remote again.
[ERROR API]
Marcel. Marcel, give Rossy the remote.
Marcel.
[ERROR API]
Marcel, you give Rossy the remote right now.
You give Rossy the remote...
[ERROR API]
[CHARACTERS SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
- Great. - Relax. I'll fix it.
[ERROR API]
Oh, cool. Urkel in Spanish is Urkel.
How did he do this?
¿Cómo hizo esto?
So tell me, is leaving the Christmas lights up...
[ERROR API]
...part of your plan to keep us merry all year long?
No, someone was supposed to take them down around New Year's...
[ERROR API]
...but obviously someone forgot.
Well, someone was supposed to write:
[ERROR API]
"Rach, take down the lights," and put it on the refrigera...
How long has that been there?
[ERROR API]
Hey, where you been?
I went back to Riff's. I think Ursula likes me. All I ordered was coffee.
[ERROR API]
She brought me a tuna melt and four plates of curly fries.
Score.
[ERROR API]
She is so hot.
Listen, okay, before you do anything Joey-like...
[ERROR API]
...you might want to run it by, uh...
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- ¿Sí? - Sí.
- Pheebs? - Yeah?
- ¿Pheebs? - ¿Sí?
Would it be okay if I asked out your sister?
[ERROR API]
Why? Why would you want to do that? Why?
So that if we went out on a date, she'd be there.
[ERROR API]
Well, I mean, I'm not my sister's, you know...
...whatever. And, um...
[ERROR API]
I mean, it's true, we were one egg once.
But, you know, we've grown apart, so, um...
[ERROR API]
I don't know. Why not?
Cool. Thanks.
[ERROR API]
You okay?
¿Estás bien?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[ERROR API]
Do you wanna watch Laverne y Shirley?
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[HABLANDO EN ESPAÑOL]
Sorry.
Lo siento.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
Sorry I'm late. Uh, where's Carol?
[ERROR API]
Stuck at school. Some parent-teacher thing.
You can go. I'll get the information.
[ERROR API]
No, no, ahem, I think I should stay. We should both know what's going on.
Oh, good.
[ERROR API]
This will be fun.
Alrighty. We're gonna start with some basic third-stage breathing exercises.
[ERROR API]
Mommies, get on your back.
And, coaches, you should be supporting Mommy's head.
[ERROR API]
- What? - What?
- ¿Qué? - ¿Qué?
I'm supposed to be the mommy?
¿Se supone que yo soy la mamá?
Okay, I'm gonna play my sperm card one more time.
Okay, voy a usar mi carta de esperma una vez más.
I don't see why I have to miss out on the coaching training because I'm a woman.
No veo por qué me tengo que perder el entrenamiento de entrenadores por ser mujer.
I see. So, what do you propose to do?
Ya veo. Entonces, ¿qué propones hacer?
- I'll flip you for it. - Flip me for it? No, no, no.
- Te apuesto a que gano. - ¿Me apuestas? No, no, no.
Heads, heads, heads.
Cara, cara, cara.
On your back, Mom.
Boca arriba, mamá.
All right, mommies, take a nice, deep, cleansing breath.
Muy bien, mamás, tomen una respiración profunda y purificadora.
Good.
Bien.
Now imagine your vagina is opening...
Ahora imaginen que su vagina se abre...
...like a flower.
...como una flor.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
Mr. Dee. How's it going, sir?
Sr. Dee. ¿Cómo va todo, señor?
Uh, it's been better.
Eh, ha ido mejor.
The Annual Net Usage Statistics are in.
Las Estadísticas Anuales de Uso Neto ya están aquí.
- And? - It's pretty ugly.
- ¿Y? - Es bastante feo.
We haven't seen an ANUS this bad since the '70s.
No habíamos visto un ANUS tan malo desde los años 70.
- So, what does this mean? - We're gonna be laying off people.
- Entonces, ¿qué significa esto? - Vamos a tener que despedir gente.
Listen, I know I came in late last week. I slept funny and my hair was snarly.
Miren, sé que llegué tarde la semana pasada. Dormí mal y tenía el pelo enredado.
Not you.
Tú no.
Relax.
Relájate.
Ever have to fire anyone?
¿Alguna vez has tenido que despedir a alguien?
CHANDLER: Nina...
Nina.
Nina...
Are you okay?
¿Estás bien?
Yes. Yes, I am.
Sí. Sí, lo estoy.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[SE ACLARA LA GARGANTA]
Uh, listen, the reason that I called you in here today was, uh...
Eh, miren, la razón por la que los llamé aquí hoy fue, eh...
Please don't hate me.
Por favor, no me odien.
What?
¿Qué?
Would you like to have dinner sometime?
¿Te gustaría cenar alguna vez?
So, Pheebs, what do you want for your birthday?
Entonces, Pheebs, ¿qué quieres para tu cumpleaños?
Well, what I really want is for my mom to be alive and enjoy it with me.
Bueno, lo que realmente quiero es que mi mamá esté viva y lo disfrute conmigo.
Okay.
Let me put it this way. Anything from Crabtree & Evelyn?
Déjame ponerlo de esta manera. ¿Algo de Crabtree & Evelyn?
- Bath salts would be nice. - Oh, okay. Good.
- Sales de baño estarían bien. - Oh, okay. Bien.
What is this place?
¿Qué es este lugar?
Look, you're cold, I have to pee, and there's coffee.
Mira, tienes frío, yo tengo que hacer pipí y hay café.
How bad could it be?
¿Qué tan malo podría ser?
I think we have an answer.
Creo que tenemos una respuesta.
What's she doing here?
¿Qué hace ella aquí?
This could be God's way of telling us to eat at home.
Esto podría ser la forma de Dios de decirnos que comamos en casa.
- Think she got fired at Riff's? - No, we were there last night.
- ¿Crees que la despidieron en Riff's? - No, estuvimos allí anoche.
She kept bringing swordfish. Are you gonna go?
No paraba de traer pez espada. ¿Vas a ir?
I'll wait until we order. It's her, right?
Esperaré hasta que pidamos. Es ella, ¿verdad?
It looks like her.
Parece ella.
- Um, excuse me? - Yeah?
- Eh, disculpe. - ¿Sí?
Hi, it's us.
Hola, somos nosotros.
Right. And it's me.
Correcto. Y soy yo.
So you're here too?
Entonces, ¿tú también estás aquí?
As much as you are.
Tanto como tú.
Your turn.
Tu turno.
- We know what we want. - Oh, that's good.
Sabemos lo que queremos. - Oh, eso está bien.
- All we want is two caffe lattes. - And some biscotti cookies.
Solo queremos dos lattes con café. - Y unas galletas de biscotti.
Good choice.
Buena elección.
- It's definitely her. - Yeah.
Definitivamente es ella. - Sí.
[CHARACTERS SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[LOS PERSONAJES HABLAN EN ESPAÑOL]
I can't believe you.
No puedo creerlo.
You still haven't told that girl she doesn't have a job yet?
¿Todavía no le has dicho a esa chica que ya no tiene trabajo?
Well, you still haven't taken down the Christmas lights.
Bueno, tú todavía no has quitado las luces de Navidad.
Congratulations. I think you found the world's thinnest argument.
Felicidades. Creo que encontraste el argumento más débil del mundo.
I'm just trying to find the right moment.
Solo estoy tratando de encontrar el momento adecuado.
Oh, well, that shouldn't be so hard, now that you're dating.
Oh, bueno, eso no debería ser tan difícil, ahora que sales con alguien.
"Sweetheart, you're fired. But how about a quickie before I go to work?"
"Cariño, estás despedida. Pero, ¿qué tal un rapidito antes de irme a trabajar?"
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
Once you're inside, you don't have to knock anymore.
Una vez que entras, ya no tienes que tocar.
I'll get it.
Yo abro.
Oh. Hi, Mr. Heckles.
Oh. Hola, Sr. Heckles.
You're doing it again.
Lo estás haciendo de nuevo.
We're not doing anything.
No estamos haciendo nada.
We're just sitting around talking quietly.
Solo estamos sentados hablando en voz baja.
I can hear you through the ceiling.
Puedo oírlos a través del techo.
My cats can't sleep.
Mis gatos no pueden dormir.
You don't even have cats.
Ni siquiera tienes gatos.
I could have cats.
Podría tener gatos.
Goodbye, Mr. Heckles.
Adiós, Sr. Heckles.
We'll try to keep it down.
Intentaremos no hacer ruido.
Phoebe, can you do me a favor?
Phoebe, ¿me haces un favor?
Try this on to make sure it fits.
Pruébate esto para asegurarte de que te queda bien.
Oh, my first birthday present. Oh, this is really...
Oh, mi primer regalo de cumpleaños. Oh, esto es realmente...
Oh, no, no. It's for Ursula. I just figured, you know, size-wise.
Oh, no, no. Es para Ursula. Solo pensé, ya sabes, por el tamaño.
Oh. Sure. Yeah.
Oh. Claro. Sí.
Okay, it fits.
Okay, me queda bien.
- Are you seeing her again tonight? - Yep, Ice Capades.
¿La vas a ver de nuevo esta noche? - Sí, Ice Capades.
Wow, this is serious.
Vaya, esto es serio.
I've never known you to pay money for any kind of capade.
Nunca te he visto pagar dinero por ningún tipo de 'capade'.
I don't know. I like her.
No sé. Me gusta.
She's different. There's, uh, something about her...
Es diferente. Hay, eh, algo en ella...
That you like. We get it. You like her. Great.
Que te gusta. Lo entendemos. Te gusta. Genial.
Hey, Phoebe, I asked you, and you said it was okay.
Oye, Phoebe, te pregunté y dijiste que estaba bien.
Well, maybe now it's not okay.
Bueno, quizás ahora no está bien.
Okay.
Well, maybe now I'm not okay with it not being okay.
Bueno, quizás ahora no estoy bien con que no esté bien.
Okay.
Knit, good woman. Knit. Knit.
Teje, buena mujer. Teje. Teje.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
And that's the Chrysler Building right there.
Y ese es el edificio Chrysler justo ahí.
NINA: Oh.
NINA: Vaya.
- Nina. - Mr. Douglas.
Nina. - Sr. Douglas.
Cool tie.
Bonita corbata.
She's still here.
Ella todavía está aquí.
Yes. Yes, she is.
Sí. Sí, lo está.
Didn't I memo you on this?
¿No te lo envié por memo?
See, after I let her go, uh, I got a call from her psychiatrist, Dr. Flanen...
Verás, después de que la despedí, eh, recibí una llamada de su psiquiatra, el Dr. Flanen...
...Dr. Flanan, Dr. Flan.
[CHANDLER CLEARS THROAT]
[CHANDLER SE ACLARA LA GARGANTA]
And, uh, he informed me that she took the news rather badly.
Y, eh, me informó que ella tomó la noticia bastante mal.
In fact, he, uh, mentioned the word "frenzy."
De hecho, él, eh, mencionó la palabra "frenesí".
You're kidding. She seems so...
¿Me estás bromeando? Ella parece tan...
Oh, no, no. Nina? She's:
Oh, no, no. ¿Nina? Ella está:
In fact, if you asked her now...
De hecho, si le preguntaras ahora...
...she'd have no recollection of being fired at all.
...no tendría ningún recuerdo de haber sido despedida.
That's unbelievable.
Eso es increíble.
And yet believable.
Y aun así creíble.
So I decided not to fire her again...
Así que decidí no despedirla de nuevo...
...until I'm sure she will be of no threat to herself or others.
...hasta que esté seguro de que no representará una amenaza para sí misma ni para otros.
I see. Hmm. You never really know what's going on inside a person's head.
Ya veo. Hmm. Uno nunca sabe realmente lo que pasa dentro de la cabeza de una persona.
Well, I guess that's why they call it psychology, sir.
Bueno, supongo que por eso lo llaman psicología, señor.
NARRATOR [ON TV]: The sound Mom and Dad will never forget.
NARRADOR [EN TV]: El sonido que mamá y papá nunca olvidarán.
For this, after all, is the miracle of birth.
Porque este, después de todo, es el milagro del nacimiento.
TEACHER: Lights, please.
PROFESORA: Luces, por favor.
And that's having a baby.
Y eso es tener un bebé.
Next week is our final class.
La próxima semana es nuestra última clase.
Susan, go deep.
Susan, ve profundo.
CAROL: It's impossible. It's just impossible.
CAROL: Es imposible. Es simplemente imposible.
What is, honey?
¿Qué es, cariño?
What that woman...
Lo que esa mujer...
...did.
...hizo.
I am not doing that. Heh.
No voy a hacer eso. Je.
It'll have to stay in, that's all. Everything will be the same.
Tendrá que quedarse, eso es todo. Todo será igual.
- It'll just stay in. Ha, ha. - Carol, honey. Shh.
- Se quedará así. Ja, ja. - Carol, cariño. Shh.
- Everything will be all right. - What do you know?
- Todo estará bien. - ¿Qué sabes tú?
No one's saying to you, "Hi, is that your nostril?
Nadie te dice: "Hola, ¿es esa tu fosa nasal?
Mind if we push this pot roast through it?"
¿Te importa si empujamos este asado de cerdo a través de ella?"
Carol, sweetie.
Carol, cariño.
Cleansing breath.
Respira profundo.
I know it's frightening. But big picture:
Sé que es aterrador. Pero en perspectiva:
The birth part is just one day...
La parte del parto es solo un día...
...and when it's over, we'll all be parents for the rest of our lives.
...y cuando termine, todos seremos padres por el resto de nuestras vidas.
SUSAN: I mean, that's what this is all about, right?
SUSAN: Quiero decir, de eso se trata todo, ¿verdad?
Ross?
¿Ross?
Ross.
I'm gonna be a father.
Voy a ser padre.
- This is just occurring to you? - I always knew I was having a baby.
- ¿Te estás dando cuenta de esto ahora? - Siempre supe que iba a tener un bebé.
I just never realized the baby was having me.
Solo que nunca me di cuenta de que el bebé me estaba teniendo a mí.
Oh, you're gonna be great.
Oh, serás genial.
How could you say that?
¿Cómo pudiste decir eso?
I can't even get Marcel to stop eating the bathmat.
[ERROR API]
How will I raise a kid?
You know, Ross, some scientists are now saying...
[ERROR API]
...that monkeys and babies are actually different.
- Where are you going? - Out.
[ERROR API]
With?
¿De?
Yes.
Sí.
All right, can I just ask you one question?
[ERROR API]
Have you two, you know, like, you know?
You know?
¿Sabes?
Yet?
[ERROR API]
Well, not that it's any of your business...
...but no, we haven't, okay?
[ERROR API]
You meant sex, right?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
- Do you have a sec? - Uh, sure, Nina. What's up?
[ERROR API]
I don't know. For the past couple days, people have been avoiding me...
...and giving me these really strange looks.
[ERROR API]
Oh, well, uh, maybe that's because...
...they're, uh, jealous of us.
[ERROR API]
Maybe.
Quizás.
But that doesn't explain why they keep taking my scissors.
[ERROR API]
Uh, well, maybe that's, uh, because you're getting a big raise.
- I am? - Sure. Why not?
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God. You're amazing.
Oh, you don't know.
[ERROR API]
Helen, make sure we put through the paperwork on Miss Bookbinder's raise.
HELEN [OVER INTERCOM]: Still want her psychological profile sent to personnel?
[ERROR API]
- What? - Helen drinks.
Will you marry me?
[ERROR API]
- Well, I ended up telling her everything. - Ooh. How'd she take it?
Pretty well. Except for the stapler thing.
[ERROR API]
Little tip. If you're ever in a similar situation...
...never, ever leave your hand on the desk.
[ERROR API]
Okay, I think I get how to do this.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[HABLANDO EN ESPAÑOL]
Can we turn this off? Can we make them go away?
[ERROR API]
Because I can't watch.
- Okay, Pheebs, they're gone. - Okay.
[ERROR API]
- Are you all right? - Yeah.
- ¿Estás bien? - Sí.
It's just, you know, this whole stupid Ursula thing.
[ERROR API]
Okay, Pheebs, can I ask?
So he's going out with her. Is it really so terrible?
Entonces va a salir con ella. ¿Es realmente tan terrible?
Um, yeah.
[ERROR API]
I mean, I'm not saying she's evil or anything.
She's just, you know, always breaking my stuff.
[ERROR API]
When I was 8, I wouldn't let her have my Judy Jetson Thermos...
...so she threw it under the bus.
[ERROR API]
And then there's Randy Brown...
...who was like...
[ERROR API]
Have you ever had a boyfriend who was like your best friend?
¿Alguna vez tuviste un novio que fuera como tu mejor amigo?
- No. - No.
Well, but that's what he was for me.
Bueno, pero para mí eso era él.
And she, you know, kind of stole him away...
Y ella, sabes, como que se lo robó...
...and then broke his heart.
...y luego le rompió el corazón.
And then he wouldn't even talk to me anymore.
Y luego ni siquiera me hablaba más.
He didn't want to be around anything that looked like either one of us.
No quería estar cerca de nada que se pareciera a alguno de nosotros.
Oh, Pheebs.
Ay, Pheebs.
I mean, I know Joey's not my boyfriend or my Thermos...
O sea, sé que Joey no es mi novio ni mi termo...
...or anything, but...
...ni nada, pero...
- You won't lose him. - You gotta talk to Joey.
- No lo vas a perder. - Tienes que hablar con Joey.
Yeah, okay.
Sí, está bien.
Come on. He doesn't know this stuff. If he knew how you felt...
Vamos. Él no sabe estas cosas. Si supiera cómo te sientes...
He's falling in love with her.
Se está enamorando de ella.
Oh, please. They've been going out a week.
Ay, por favor. Llevan una semana saliendo.
They haven't even slept together yet. I mean, that's not serious.
Ni siquiera han dormido juntos todavía. O sea, eso no es serio.
Okay.
Oh. Okay. Oh.
Oh. De acuerdo. Oh.
Oh.
Yeah, um, may we help you?
Sí, eh, ¿podemos ayudarle?
Rachel, what are you doing? It's freezing. Would you come inside?
Rachel, ¿qué haces? Hace un frío terrible. ¿Entras?
No, no, no.
You wanted me to take them down...
Querías que las bajara...
...so I'm taking them down, okay?
...así que las estoy bajando, ¿de acuerdo?
[RACHEL YELLS]
[RACHEL GRITA]
Rachel!
¡Rachel!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Estoy bien. Estoy bien.
Mr. Heckles?
¿Sr. Heckles?
Mr. Heckles, could you help me, please?
Sr. Heckles, ¿podría ayudarme, por favor?
See, this is just the kind of thing I was talking about.
¿Ves? Esto es justo de lo que estaba hablando.