Do you think they have yesterday's Daily News?
¿Crees que tengan el "Daily News" de ayer?
MONICA: Why? - I just wanna check my horoscope...
MONICA: ¿Por qué? - Solo quiero ver mi horóscopo...
...see if it was right.
...a ver si acertó.
Oh, my God. Phoebe. Don't look now, but, behind you there's a guy...
Ay, Dios mío. Phoebe. No mires, pero, detrás de ti hay un chico...
...who has the potential to break our hearts and plunge us into depression.
...que tiene el potencial de rompernos el corazón y sumirnos en la depresión.
Where?
¿Dónde?
Ooh, come to Mama.
Ooh, ven aquí, mamita.
Okay, he's coming. Be cool. Be cool. Be cool.
Okay, viene. Compórtate. Compórtate. Compórtate.
- Nice hat. BOTH: Thanks.
- Bonito sombrero. AMBOS: Gracias.
- We should do something. Whistle. - We're not gonna whistle.
- Deberíamos hacer algo. Silba. - No vamos a silbar.
- Yeah, come on, do it. - No.
- Sí, vamos, hazlo. - No.
- Do it. Do it. Do it. - Woo-hoo!
- Hazlo. Hazlo. Hazlo. - ¡Woo-hoo!
[AMBULANCE SIRENS WAILING]
[SUENAN SIRENAS DE AMBULANCIA]
[TIRES SQUEALING THEN THUD]
[CHILLAN LOS NEUMÁTICOS Y LUEGO UN GOLPE]
I can't believe you did that.
No puedo creer que hicieras eso.
MONICA: Why did I woo-hoo?
MONICA: ¿Por qué dije "Woo-hoo"?
I mean, what was I hoping? He'd turn around and say:
O sea, ¿qué esperaba? ¿Que se diera la vuelta y dijera:
"Ooh, I love that sound. I must have you now"?
"Ooh, me encanta ese sonido. Debo tenerte ahora"?
I just wish there was something we could do.
Solo desearía que pudiéramos hacer algo.
[EKG BEEPING]
[SUENA UN BIP DE ELECTROCARDIOGRAMA]
Hello. Hello, coma guy.
Hola. Hola, chico en coma.
Get up, you Girl Scout! Up, up, up!
¡Levántate, chica scout! ¡Arriba, arriba, arriba!
- Phoebe, what are you doing? - Maybe nobody's tried this.
- Phoebe, ¿qué haces? - Quizás nadie lo ha intentado.
I wish we at least knew his name.
Ojalá al menos supiéramos su nombre.
Would you look at that face?
Mira esa cara.
I mean, even sleeping he looks smart. I bet he's a lawyer.
O sea, incluso durmiendo se ve inteligente. Apuesto a que es abogado.
Yeah, but did you see the dents in his knuckles? That means he's artistic.
Sí, pero ¿viste los golpes en los nudillos? Eso significa que es artístico.
Okay. He's a lawyer who teaches sculpting on the side.
Okay. Es un abogado que enseña escultura los fines de semana.
And he can dance.
Y sabe bailar.
And he's the kind of guy who, when you're talking, he's listening...
Y es el tipo de chico que, cuando hablas, te escucha...
...you know, and not saying, "Yeah, I understand"...
...sabes, y no dice: "Sí, entiendo"...
...but wondering what you look like naked. - Oh, stop it.
...sino que se pregunta cómo te ves desnuda. - Ay, para.
I wish all guys could be like him.
Ojalá todos los chicos fueran como él.
I know.
Lo sé.
Are there no conscious men in the city for you two?
¿No hay hombres conscientes en la ciudad para ustedes dos?
- He doesn't have anyone. - Yeah. We feel kind of responsible.
- Él no tiene a nadie. - Sí. Nos sentimos un poco responsables.
I can't believe you said, "Woo-hoo."
No puedo creer que dijeras "Woo-hoo".
I don't even say, "Woo-hoo."
Yo ni siquiera digo "Woo-hoo".
Oh, she's coming up. She's coming up.
Oh, está subiendo. Está subiendo.
Folks, when we come back...
Amigos, cuando volvamos...
...we'll talk about her new book Euphoria Unbound...
...hablaremos de su nuevo libro "Euforia Desatada"...
...with always-interesting Nora Tyler Bing. Put the kids to bed for this one.
...con la siempre interesante Nora Tyler Bing. Manden a los niños a la cama para esto.
Don't watch this. Weekend at Bernie's is on Showtime and HBO and Cinemex.
No vean esto. "Un loco a domicilio" está en Showtime, HBO y Cinemex.
- No way. - Come on. She's your mom.
- Ni hablar. - Vamos. Es tu mamá.
Exactly. Weekend at Bernie's.
Exacto. "Un loco a domicilio".
Dead guy getting hit in the groin 20, 30 times.
Un tipo muerto recibiendo golpes en la ingle 20, 30 veces.
- No? - Chandler, I gotta tell you...
- ¿No? - Chandler, tengo que decirte...
...I love your mom's books. I love her books.
...me encantan los libros de tu mamá. Me encantan sus libros.
I cannot get on a plane without one. I mean, this is so cool.
No puedo subirme a un avión sin uno. O sea, esto es genial.
You wouldn't think it's cool if you were 11...
No pensarías que es genial si tuvieras 11 años...
...and all your friends were passing around page 79 of Mistress Bitch.
...y todos tus amigos se pasaban la página 79 de 'Mistress Bitch'.
Come on, Chandler. I love your mom. I think she's a blast.
Vamos, Chandler. Me cae bien tu mamá. Creo que es genial.
- You can say that. She's not your mom. ROSS: Oh, please. She's the...
- Puedes decir eso. Ella no es tu mamá. ROSS: Oh, por favor. Ella es la...
RACHEL: Hi, sweetie.
RACHEL: Hola, cariño.
When did Rigatoni get back from Rome?
¿Cuándo regresó Rigatoni de Roma?
- Last night. - Really?
- Anoche. - ¿En serio?
So then his plane didn't explode in a big ball of fire?
Entonces, ¿su avión no explotó en una gran bola de fuego?
Just a dream I had.
Solo un sueño que tuve.
But, phew.
Pero, uff.
Hey, hey, hey. She's on.
Oye, oye, oye. Ya está.
Ah. Nora Bing.
Before we get to the book.
Antes de llegar al libro.
What is this about you being arrested in London? What is that about?
¿Qué es eso de que te arrestaron en Londres? ¿De qué se trata?
- Your mom was arrested? - Shh, I'm busy beaming with pride.
- ¿Arrestaron a tu mamá? - Shh, estoy ocupada llenándome de orgullo.
This is kind of embarrassing...
Esto es un poco vergonzoso...
...but occasionally after I've been intimate with a man...
...pero ocasionalmente después de estar íntimamente con un hombre...
- Why would she say that's embarrassing? - Shh.
- ¿Por qué diría ella que eso es vergonzoso? - Shh.
- I just get this craving for Kung Pao chicken.
- Solo me da este antojo de pollo Kung Pao.
That's too much information.
Esa es demasiada información.
So now you're doing this book tour thing. How's that going?
Así que ahora estás haciendo esta gira de libros. ¿Cómo va eso?
Oh, fine. I'm leaving for New York tomorrow, which I hate.
Oh, bien. Me voy a Nueva York mañana, lo cual odio.
But I get to see my son, who I love.
Pero veré a mi hijo, a quien amo.
GROUP: Oh.
GRUPO: Oh.
This is the way that I find out. Most moms use the phone.
Así me entero. La mayoría de las madres usan el teléfono.
You know, don't take this wrong, I just don't see you as a mom somehow.
Sabes, no te lo tomes a mal, simplemente no te veo como una mamá.
- I don't mean that bad. - Oh, no. I'm a fabulous mom.
- No lo digo a mal. - Oh, no. Soy una mamá fabulosa.
I bought my son his first condoms.
Le compré a mi hijo sus primeros condones.
And then he burst into flames.
Y entonces él explotó en llamas.
[EKG BEEPING]
[SUENA UN BIP DE ELECTROCARDIOGRAMA]
MONICA: Let's see. "Congress is debating a new deficit-reduction bill.
MONICA: Veamos. "El Congreso está debatiendo un nuevo proyecto de ley de reducción del déficit.
The mayor wants to raise subway fares again.
El alcalde quiere subir las tarifas del metro de nuevo.
The high today was 45."
La máxima de hoy fue de 45."
And, oh. And teams played sports.
Y, oh. Y los equipos jugaron deportes.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[DIÁLOGO INAUDIBLE]
PHOEBE: What about Glen? MONICA: No.
PHOEBE: ¿Qué hay de Glen? MONICA: No.
- He could be a Glen. - Mm-mm. Not special enough.
- Podría ser un Glen. - Mm-mm. No es lo suficientemente especial.
Ooh, how about Agamemnon?
Ooh, ¿qué tal Agamenón?
Way too special.
Demasiado especial.
I'm famished. What do I want?
Estoy famélica. ¿Qué quiero?
Please, God, don't let it be Kung Pao chicken.
Por favor, Dios, que no sea pollo Kung Pao.
Oh, you watched the show. What did you think?
Oh, viste el programa. ¿Qué te pareció?
Well, I think you need to come out of your shell just...
Bueno, creo que necesitas salir de tu caparazón un poco...
What is this dive?
¿Qué es este tugurio?
- Only you could've picked this place. - Oh.
- Solo tú podrías haber elegido este lugar. - Oh.
Come on. Shut up. It's fun.
Vamos. Cállate. Es divertido.
- Hi. NORA: Give me a hug.
- Hola. NORA: Dame un abrazo.
- Well, I think we're ready for some tequila. - I know I am.
- Bueno, creo que estamos listos para un tequila. - Yo sí lo estoy.
- Who's doing shots? - Hit me.
- ¿Quién va a tomar shots? - Échame uno.
- I'm in. - There you go. Ross?
- Me apunto. - Ahí tienes. ¿Ross?
Uh, I'm not really a shot-drinking kind of guy.
Uh, realmente no soy de los que toman shots.
Hi. Sorry. Sorry we're late.
Hola. Perdón. Perdón por llegar tarde.
We, uh, kind of just, you know, lost track of time.
Nos, eh, como que perdimos la noción del tiempo.
But a man can change.
Pero un hombre puede cambiar.
Anyone want me to appraise anything?
¿Alguien quiere que valore algo?
Mrs. Bing, I have to tell you, I've read everything you've ever written.
Señora Bing, tengo que decirle que he leído todo lo que ha escrito.
No, I mean it. When I read Euphoria at Midnight...
No, lo digo en serio. Cuando leí "Euforia a medianoche"...
...all I wanted to do was become a writer.
...lo único que quise fue ser escritor.
Oh, please, honey. If I can do it, anybody can.
Oh, por favor, cariño. Si yo puedo hacerlo, cualquiera puede.
You just start with half a dozen European cities...
Solo empiezas con media docena de ciudades europeas...
...throw in 30 euphemisms for male genitalia...
...añades 30 eufemismos para genitales masculinos...
...and, bam, you have got yourself a book.
...y, ¡zas!, ya tienes un libro.
My mother, ladies and gentlemen.
Mi madre, señoras y señores.
Yeah, any messages for room 226?
Sí, ¿algún mensaje para la habitación 226?
- You okay, slugger? - Oh, yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine.
- ¿Estás bien, campeón? - Oh, sí. Estoy bien. Estoy bien.
What is with you tonight?
¿Qué te pasa esta noche?
Nothing. Nothing, nothing, nothing.
Nada. Nada, nada, nada.
NORA: Okay, thank you.
NORA: Okay, gracias.
It's the Italian hand-licker, isn't it?
Es el italiano que se lame los dedos, ¿verdad?
No. It's the one he's licking.
No. Es el que él se lame.
She's supposed to be with you.
Se supone que ella está contigo.
You're good.
Eres buena.
Oh, Ross, listen to me. I have sold 100 million copies of my books...
Oh, Ross, escúchame. He vendido 100 millones de copias de mis libros...
...and you know why?
...¿y sabes por qué?
The girl on the cover with her nipples showing?
¿La chica de la portada con los pezones al descubierto?
No, because I know how to write men that women fall in love with.
No, porque sé cómo escribir hombres de los que las mujeres se enamoran.
Believe me, I cannot sell a Paolo.
Créeme, no puedo vender un Paolo.
People will not turn 325 pages for a Paolo.
La gente no va a pasar 325 páginas por un Paolo.
Come on. The guy's a secondary character.
Vamos. El tipo es un personaje secundario.
He's just a... You know, a complication you eventually kill off.
Es solo una... ya sabes, una complicación que eventualmente matas.
When?
¿Cuándo?
He's not a hero.
Él no es un héroe.
You know who our hero is?
¿Sabes quién es nuestro héroe?
The guy on the cover with his nipples showing?
¿El tipo de la portada con los pezones al descubierto?
No, it's you.
No, eres tú.
- Please. - No, really.
- Por favor. - No, en serio.
Come on. You're smart. You're sexy.
Vamos. Eres inteligente. Eres sexy.
- Right. - Oh, come on, kiddo.
- Cierto. - Oh, vamos, pequeña.
You're gonna be fine, believe me.
Vas a estar bien, créeme.
Uh-oh.
Uh, I'll just pee in the street.
Eh, me haré pis en la calle.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[LLAMAN A LA PUERTA]
Is Chandler here?
¿Está Chandler aquí?
- Yeah. - Wait. Come here.
- Sí. - Espera. Ven aquí.
Okay, uh, about last night...
Okay, eh, sobre anoche...
...um, you know...
...um, ya sabes...
...Chandler. You didn't tell...
...Chandler. No le dijiste...
Okay, I'm thinking we don't need to tell Chandler.
Okay, creo que no necesitamos decirle a Chandler.
It was just a kiss. One kiss. No big deal, right?
Solo fue un beso. Un beso. No es gran cosa, ¿verdad?
- Right. No big deal. - Okay.
- Cierto. No es gran cosa. - Okay.
In Bizarro-world.
En el mundo Bizarro.
You broke the code.
Rompiste el código.
- What code? - You don't kiss your friend's mom.
- ¿Qué código? - No besas a la mamá de tu amigo.
Sisters are okay. Maybe a hot-looking aunt.
Las hermanas están bien. Quizás una tía atractiva.
But not a mom. Never a mom.
Pero no una mamá. Nunca una mamá.
[ALL SHOUTING]
[TODOS GRITANDO]
What are you guys doing out here?
¿Qué hacen ustedes aquí afuera?
Uh, well, Joey and I had discussed getting in an early morning racquetball game.
Eh, bueno, Joey y yo habíamos planeado jugar racquetball temprano.
But, um, apparently somebody overslept.
Pero, eh, aparentemente alguien se quedó dormido.
Yeah, well, you don't have your racquet.
Sí, bueno, no tienes tu raqueta.
No. No, I don't, because it's being restrung.
No. No la tengo, porque la están encordando.
Ahem. Somebody was supposed to bring me one.
Ejem. Alguien se suponía que me traería una.
Yeah. Well, you didn't call and leave your grip size.
Sí. Bueno, no llamaste para decirme el tamaño del grip.
Okay, you guys are spending way too much time together.
Okay, ustedes pasan demasiado tiempo juntos.
Okay, I'm scum. I'm scum.
Okay, soy escoria. Soy escoria.
- Ross, how could you let this happen? - I don't know.
- Ross, ¿cómo pudiste dejar que esto pasara? - No lo sé.
Well, it's not like she's a regular mom. You know? She's sexy. She's...
Bueno, no es como si fuera una mamá cualquiera. ¿Sabes? Es sexy. Es...
You don't think my mom's sexy?
¿No crees que mi mamá es sexy?
Well, not in the same way.
Bueno, no de la misma manera.
I'll have you know that Gloria Tribbiani...
Que se enteren que Gloria Tribbiani...
...was a handsome woman in her day, all right?
...era una mujer guapa en sus tiempos, ¿de acuerdo?
You think it's easy giving birth to seven children?
¿Crees que es fácil dar a luz a siete hijos?
Huh?
¿Eh?
Okay, I think we're getting into a weird area here.
Okay, creo que estamos entrando en un terreno raro aquí.
- Aah. - Hey.
- ¡Aah! - Oye.
- Hey. - What are you guys doing out here?
- Oye. - ¿Qué hacen ustedes aquí afuera?
Well, ha, ha, not playing racquetball.
Bueno, ja, ja, no jugando racquetball.
- He forgot to leave his grip size. - He didn't get the goggles.
- Se le olvidó decir el tamaño del grip. - No consiguió las gafas.
Oh. Right.
Oh. Cierto.
Well, sounds like you two have issues.
Bueno, parece que ustedes dos tienen problemas.
Goodbye, baby.
Adiós, nena.
[SPEAKING IN ITALIAN]
[HABLANDO EN ITALIANO]
Do they wait for me to do this?
¿Me esperan para hacer esto?
- So are you gonna tell him? - I'm not gonna tell him.
- Entonces, ¿le vas a decir? - No voy a decirle.
- Why would I tell him? - How about, because if you don't...
- ¿Por qué le diría? - ¿Qué tal si, porque si no lo haces...
...his mother might? - Hmm.
...¿su madre lo hace? - Hmm.
What are you guys doing here?
¿Qué hacen ustedes aquí?
Uh, he's not even wearing a jock strap.
Uh, ni siquiera lleva puesto un suspensorio.
What did I ask?
¿Qué pregunté?
[EKG BEEPING]
[SUENA UN BIP DE ELECTROCARDIOGRAMA]
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
What are you doing here?
¿Qué haces aquí?
Nothing. I just thought I'd stop by, you know, after the, ahem...
Nada. Solo pensé en pasar, ya sabes, después de la, ejem...
That I, you know. Um, so, what are you doing here?
Que yo, ya sabes. Um, entonces, ¿qué haces aquí?
I'm not really here.
Realmente no estoy aquí.
I just thought I'd drop these off on the way. My way.
Solo pensé en dejar esto de camino. De mi camino.
Do you, um, come here a lot...
¿Vienes aquí, um, a menudo...
...without me?
...sin mí?
No, no, no.
So, um, do you think he's doing any better than he was this morning?
Entonces, um, ¿crees que le va mejor de lo que le iba esta mañana?
How would I know? I wasn't here.
¿Cómo lo sabría? Yo no estaba aquí.
Really? Not even to, um, change his pajamas?
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
You're my friend. I had to tell you.
[ERROR API]
I can't believe it.
Paolo kissed my mom?
[ERROR API]
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if you noticed, but he had a lot to drink.
I mean, you know how he gets when he's drunk...
[ERROR API]
I can't do this. I did it.
It was me. I'm sorry. I kissed your mom.
[ERROR API]
What?
¿Qué?
I was really upset about Rachel and Paolo and I think I had too much tequila...
[ERROR API]
...and Nora... Mrs. Mom, your Bing, was...
She was just being nice, you know? But nothing happened.
[ERROR API]
Nothing. Ask Joey. Joey came in...
- You knew about this? - Uh...
[ERROR API]
You know, knowledge is a tricky thing.
I spent the entire day with you. Why didn't you tell me?
[ERROR API]
Hey, hey. You're lucky I caught them when I did...
...or else who knows what would've happened?
[ERROR API]
Thanks, man. Big help.
I can't believe this. What the hell were you thinking?
[ERROR API]
I wasn't. I don't know. I...
Of all my friends, no one knows the crap I go through with my mom more than you.
[ERROR API]
- I know. - I can't believe you did this.
- Me neither. - I'm mad at you for not telling me.
[ERROR API]
- What are you mad at me...? - Let me slam the door.
Chandler, I didn't kiss her. He did.
[ERROR API]
See what happens when you break the code?
- Joey. - Aah! Uh.
[ERROR API]
- Rach. - Hey.
"A Woman Undone. By Rachel Karen Green."
[ERROR API]
Yeah, I thought I'd give it a shot. I'm still on the first chapter.
Now, do you think his "love stick" can be "liberated from its denim prison"?
[ERROR API]
Yeah, I'd say so.
And there's no "J" in "engorged."
[ERROR API]
- Hey, Rach. - Hey.
- Hello. - Hello.
[ERROR API]
- You going to the hospital tonight? - No. You?
No. You?
[ERROR API]
You just asked me.
Okay, maybe it was a trick question.
[ERROR API]
- Um, Rachel, can we do this now? - Okay.
I am so hot.
[ERROR API]
And here's a picture of my mother and father on their wedding day.
Now, you tell me she's not a knockout.
[ERROR API]
I cannot believe we're having this conversation.
Come on, just try to picture her not pregnant. That's all.
[ERROR API]
Central Perk is proud to present Miss Phoebe Buffay.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[LA MULTITUD APLAUDE]
PHOEBE: Thanks.
PHOEBE: Gracias.
Hi. Um, ahem. Okay.
Hola. Eh, ejem. De acuerdo.
I'd like to start with a song that's about a man I recently met...
Me gustaría empezar con una canción que trata sobre un hombre que conocí recientemente...
...who's, um, come to be very important to me.
...que, eh, se ha vuelto muy importante para mí.
Okay.
[SINGING] You don't have to be awake To be my man
[CANTANDO] No tienes que estar despierto Para ser mi hombre
Long as you have brain waves I'll be there to hold your hand
Mientras tengas ondas cerebrales Estaré ahí para tomar tu mano
Though we just met the other day
Aunque nos conocimos el otro día
There's something I have got to say
Hay algo que tengo que decir
Okay, thank you very much. I'm gonna take a short break.
De acuerdo, muchas gracias. Voy a tomar un breve descanso.
RACHEL: Okay, that was Phoebe Buffay, everybody. Whoo!
RAQUEL: De acuerdo, esa fue Phoebe Buffay, todos. ¡Whoo!
- What the hell was that? - Phoebe just started...
- ¿Qué demonios fue eso? - Phoebe acaba de empezar...
I believe I was talking to Joey. All right, there, mother-kisser?
Creo que estaba hablando con Joey. ¿De acuerdo, ahí, hijo de puta?
[LAUGHING]
[RÍEN]
"Mother-kisser."
"Hijo de puta."
I'll shut up.
Me callaré.
Chandler, can I say something? I know you're still mad at me.
Chandler, ¿puedo decir algo? Sé que todavía estás enojado conmigo.
I just wanna say that there were two people there that night, okay?
Solo quiero decir que hubo dos personas allí esa noche, ¿de acuerdo?
- There were two sets of lips. - Yes, well, I expect this from her.
- Hubo dos pares de labios. - Sí, bueno, esto lo esperaba de ella.
Okay? She's always been a Freudian nightmare.
¿De acuerdo? Ella siempre ha sido una pesadilla freudiana.
Okay, but if she always behaves like this, why don't you say something?
Está bien, pero si ella siempre se comporta así, ¿por qué no dices algo?
Because it's complicated. It's complex.
Porque es complicado. Es complejo.
Hey, you kissed my mom.
Oye, besaste a mi mamá.
We're rehearsing a Greek play.
Estamos ensayando una obra griega.
- That's funny. We done now? - No.
- Eso es gracioso. ¿Terminamos? - No.
Okay, you mean you're not gonna talk to her, tell her how you feel?
De acuerdo, ¿quieres decir que no vas a hablar con ella, decirle cómo te sientes?
That would be a no. Just because you played tonsil tennis with my mom...
Eso sería un no. Solo porque jugaste al tenis de lengua con mi mamá...
...doesn't mean you know her, all right? Trust me, you can't talk to her.
...no significa que la conozcas, ¿de acuerdo? Confía en mí, no puedes hablar con ella.
Okay. "You can't"? Or you can't?
De acuerdo. ¿"No puedes"? ¿O no puedes?
Okay, that's my finger. Okay, that's my knee.
De acuerdo, ese es mi dedo. De acuerdo, esa es mi rodilla.
Still doing the play.
Todavía haciendo la obra.
[SHOUTS THEN HUMS]
[GRITA LUEGO TARAREA]
All right, what did you do with him?
Muy bien, ¿qué hiciste con él?
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[SE ESCUCHA LA DESCARGA DEL INODORO]
- You're awake. - Look at you.
- Estás despierto. - Mírate.
How do you feel?
¿Cómo te sientes?
Uh, a little woozy, but basically okay.
Eh, un poco mareado, pero básicamente bien.
Gosh, you look good.
Vaya, te ves bien.
I feel good.
Me siento bien.
Who are you?
¿Quién eres?
- Sorry. - I'm Phoebe Buffay.
- Lo siento. - Soy Phoebe Buffay.
I'm Monica Geller. I've been taking care of you.
Soy Monica Geller. Te he estado cuidando.
We both have.
Ambos lo hemos hecho.
- So the Etch A Sketch is from you guys? - Actually, it's just from me.
- ¿Entonces el Etch A Sketch es de ustedes? - En realidad, es solo mío.
- Yeah, I got you the foot massager. - Know who shaved you? That was me.
- Sí, te traje el masajeador de pies. - ¿Sabes quién te afeitó? Fui yo.
- I read to you. - I sang. Ha.
- Te leí. - Yo canté. Ja.
Well, thanks.
Bueno, gracias.
- Oh, my pleasure. - You're welcome.
- Oh, fue un placer. - De nada.
So I guess I'll see you around.
Supongo que nos vemos por ahí.
What? That's it?
¿Qué? ¿Eso es todo?
"See you around"?
"¿Nos vemos por ahí"?
- Well, what do you want me to say? - Well, I don't know.
- Bueno, ¿qué quieres que diga? - Pues, no sé.
Maybe, uh:
Quizás, eh:
"That was nice.
"Eso estuvo bien.
It meant something to me.
Significó algo para mí.
I'll call you."
Te llamaré."
- All right. I'll call you. - I don't think you mean that.
- De acuerdo. Te llamaré. - No creo que lo digas en serio.
This is so typical.
Esto es tan típico.
You know, we give...
Sabes, damos...
...and we give...
...y damos...
...and we give.
...y damos.
And then we just get nothing back.
Y luego no recibimos nada a cambio.
And then one day, it's just, you know, you wake up and "See you around."
Y entonces un día, es solo, ya sabes, te despiertas y "Adiós."
Let's go, Phoebe.
Vamos, Phoebe.
You know what? We thought you were different.
¿Sabes qué? Pensamos que eras diferente.
But I guess it was just the coma.
Pero supongo que solo fue el coma.
NORA: The car's running downstairs.
NORA: El coche está listo abajo.
I wanted to drop off these copies of my book for your friends.
Quería dejar estas copias de mi libro para tus amigos.
- Anything you want from Lisbon? - No, just knowing you're there is enough.
- ¿Algo que quieras de Lisboa? - No, solo saber que estás ahí es suficiente.
All right. Well, be good. I love you.
Está bien. Bueno, pórtate bien. Te quiero.
You kissed my best Ross.
Besaste a mi mejor amigo, Ross.
Or something to that effect.
O algo por el estilo.
Okay.
Look, it was stupid.
Mira, fue una estupidez.
- Really stupid. - Really stupid.
- Muy estúpido. - Muy estúpido.
And I don't even know how it happened.
Y ni siquiera sé cómo pasó.
I'm sorry, honey. I promise it will never happen again.
Lo siento, cariño. Prometo que no volverá a pasar.
- Are we okay now? - Yeah.
- ¿Estamos bien ahora? - Sí.
No. No.
Ah, the forbidden love of a man and his door.
Ah, el amor prohibido de un hombre y su puerta.
Shh.
He did it. He told her off. And not just about the kiss, about everything.
Lo hizo. La mandó a volar. Y no solo por el beso, por todo.
- You're kidding? - No.
- ¿Me estás bromeando? - No.
He said, "When are you gonna grow up and start being a mom?"
Dijo: "¿Cuándo vas a madurar y empezar a ser una mamá?"
- Wow. - Wait, then she came back with:
- Guau. - Espera, entonces ella respondió:
"The question is, when are you gonna grow up and realize I have a bomb?"
"La pregunta es, ¿cuándo vas a madurar y darte cuenta de que tengo una bomba?"
Okay, wait. Are you sure she didn't say:
Okay, espera. ¿Estás segura de que no dijo:
"When are you gonna grow up and realize I am your mom?"
"¿Cuándo vas a madurar y darte cuenta de que soy tu mamá?"
- That makes more sense. - You think?
- Eso tiene más sentido. - ¿Tú crees?
Yeah.
Sí.
So, what's going on now?
Entonces, ¿qué está pasando ahora?
I don't know. I've been standing here spelling it out for you.
No lo sé. He estado parada aquí explicándotelo.
I don't hear anything. Wait, wait, wait.
No oigo nada. Espera, espera, espera.
What do you see?
¿Qué ves?
It's hard to tell. They're so tiny and upside down.
Es difícil de decir. Son tan pequeños y están al revés.
Wait, wait, wait.
Espera, espera, espera.
They're walking away. They're walking away.
Se están alejando. Se están alejando.
No, they're not. They're coming right at us. Run, run!
No, no lo hacen. Vienen directo hacia nosotros. ¡Corre, corre!
You okay, kiddo?
¿Estás bien, campeón?
- Yeah, I'm okay. - All right. You be good.
- Sí, estoy bien. - Está bien. Pórtate bien.
Drive safe.
Conduce con cuidado.
[CHUCKLES]
[RÍE]
- Mrs. Bing. - Mr. Geller.
Señora Bing. - Señor Geller.
Hey.
Oye.
You mean that?
¿Te refieres a eso?
Yeah, why not?
Sí, ¿por qué no?
- So I told her. - Oh.
- Así que se lo dije. - Oh.
- How did it go? - Awful. Awful.
- ¿Cómo fue? - Terrible. Terrible.
Couldn't have gone worse.
No pudo haber ido peor.
- Well, how do you feel? - Pretty good.
- Bueno, ¿cómo te sientes? - Bastante bien.
I told her.
Se lo dije.
Well, see?
Bueno, ¿ves?
So maybe it wasn't such a bad idea, you know, me kissing your mom, huh?
Así que tal vez no fue tan mala idea, ¿sabes?, que yo besara a tu mamá, ¿eh?
But we don't have to go down that road.
Pero no tenemos que entrar en detalles.
Now, this is just the first chapter...
Ahora, este es solo el primer capítulo...
...and I want your absolute honest opinion. Okay?
...y quiero tu opinión más honesta. ¿De acuerdo?
Oh, and on page two, he's not reaching for her "heaving beasts."
Oh, y en la página dos, él no está alcanzando sus "bestias palpitantes".
What's a "niffle"?
¿Qué es un "niffle"?
You can usually find them on the heaving beasts.
Normalmente puedes encontrarlos en las bestias palpitantes.
All right, all right, so I'm not a great typist.
Está bien, está bien, así que no soy un gran mecanógrafo.
Wait, did you get to the part about his "huge, throbbing pens"?
Espera, ¿llegaste a la parte de sus "enormes y palpitantes penes"?
Tell you, you don't wanna be around when he starts writing with those.
Te digo, no querrás estar cerca cuando empiece a escribir con esos.
- All right, that's it. Give them back. GROUP: No.
- Está bien, eso es todo. Devuélvelos. - No.