- You ready to go? - Let me just finish this.
- ¿Listo para ir? - Déjame terminar esto.
Hey, Ross. Check this out.
Oye, Ross. Mira esto.
Yeah, I can't do that. Heh.
Sí, no puedo hacer eso. Je.
- What are you doing? - Have you seen this?
- ¿Qué haces? - ¿Has visto esto?
It's our new alumni website for college.
Es nuestro nuevo sitio web de exalumnos de la universidad.
You can post messages for people, let everyone know what you're up to.
Puedes publicar mensajes para la gente, avisar a todos de lo que estás haciendo.
Oh, great. A faster way to tell people that I'm unemployed and childless.
Oh, genial. Una forma más rápida de decirle a la gente que estoy desempleado y sin hijos.
It's actually interesting to find out what people are doing.
En realidad es interesante saber lo que hace la gente.
Remember Andrea Rich?
¿Recuerdas a Andrea Rich?
- Tall girl, wouldn't sleep with you? - Uh-huh.
- ¿La alta que no se acostaba contigo? - Ajá.
Well, her Internet company went under, and she lost an ear in a boating accident.
Bueno, su compañía de internet quebró y perdió una oreja en un accidente de navegación.
Bet she'd sleep with you now.
Apuesto a que ahora sí se acostaría contigo.
No, I already e-mailed her.
No, ya le envié un correo.
Let me see what you wrote about yourself.
Déjame ver lo que escribiste sobre ti.
- Oh. - "Doctor of paleontology, two kids."
- Oh. - "Doctor en paleontología, dos hijos."
Wait a second. You split with Carol because you had different interests?
Espera un segundo. ¿Te separaste de Carol porque tenían intereses diferentes?
I think you split with Carol because you had one very similar interest.
Creo que te separaste de Carol porque tenían un interés muy similar.
You know what? I'm gonna finish this later, okay? Let me just grab my coat.
¿Sabes qué? Voy a terminar esto después, ¿vale? Déjame solo agarrar mi abrigo.
Okay.
What, did you think you learned how to do it in the last two minutes?
¿Qué, pensaste que aprendiste a hacerlo en los últimos dos minutos?
Maybe we finish this for him.
Quizás terminemos esto por él.
Also, I cloned a dinosaur in my lab.
Además, cloné un dinosaurio en mi laboratorio.
She is now my girlfriend.
Ella es ahora mi novia.
I don't care what society says, it's the best sex I've ever had.
No me importa lo que diga la sociedad, es el mejor sexo que he tenido.
- And send. - No, no... You can't do that to him.
- Y enviar. - No, no... No puedes hacerle eso.
- All right, let's go. - Dude!
- Muy bien, vámonos. - ¡Amigo!
Uh, I think you made it clear you can't be trusted with the ball inside the house.
Uh, creo que dejaste claro que no se puede confiar en ti con la pelota dentro de la casa.
And send.
Y enviar.
Hey. How was basketball?
Oye. ¿Cómo estuvo el baloncesto?
It was fun. Right up until Chandler got a finger in the eye.
Estuvo divertido. Justo hasta que a Chandler le metieron un dedo en el ojo.
Oh, no. Who did that?
Oh, no. ¿Quién hizo eso?
Chandler. Yeah.
Chandler. Sí.
H93'-
- Rash? - Yeah?
- ¿Rash? - ¿Sí?
What's Huggsy doing in the crib with Emma?
¿Qué hace Huggsy en la cuna con Emma?
She was just crawling around and she found him...
Solo estaba gateando y lo encontró...
...so I just let her sleep with him.
...así que la dejé dormir con él.
- That's all right, isn't it? - Of course. Yeah.
- Está bien, ¿no? - Claro. Sí.
It's a stuffed animal, you know? It's for kids. Not for adults.
Es un peluche, ¿sabes? Es para niños. No para adultos.
I know that.
Lo sé.
Joey, you're sure? I mean, I know how much you love him.
Joey, ¿estás seguro? Quiero decir, sé cuánto lo quieres.
Rachel, let's be clear on this, okay? I do not love Huggsy.
Rachel, seamos claros en esto, ¿vale? Yo no amo a Huggsy.
I like him a normal amount.
Me gusta una cantidad normal.
All right. Well, Emma loves him.
Está bien. Bueno, Emma lo ama.
Yeah. Well, why wouldn't she? He's a wonderful person.
Sí. Bueno, ¿por qué no lo haría? Es una persona maravillosa.
- Hi. - Hey, Phoebe. How you doing?
- Hola. - Hola, Phoebe. ¿Cómo estás?
- You feeling better? - Breaking up sucks.
- ¿Te sientes mejor? - Terminar una relación apesta.
- Oh, I really miss Mike. - Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Oh, extraño mucho a Mike. - Oh, lo siento mucho.
I've tried everything to feel better. I even tried writing a song about it...
He intentado de todo para sentirme mejor. Incluso intenté escribir una canción sobre ello...
...but I can't think of anything that rhymes with:
...pero no se me ocurre nada que rime con:
Hey, Monica, I'm gonna need your help getting through this.
Oye, Monica, voy a necesitar tu ayuda para superar esto.
You're saying you're not gonna need my help?
¿Estás diciendo que no vas a necesitar mi ayuda?
No. When I get to the point where I'm ready...
No. Cuando llegue al punto en que esté lista...
...to hear cruel, mocking jokes about Mike, I'm gonna come to you.
...para escuchar chistes crueles y burlones sobre Mike, iré contigo.
Oh, good, because I've already thought of three. Four! I just thought of a fourth.
Oh, bien, porque ya he pensado en tres. ¡Cuatro! Acabo de pensar en una cuarta.
Okay. I mean, I know I did the right thing.
Está bien. Quiero decir, sé que hice lo correcto.
Mike never wants to get married...
Mike nunca quiere casarse...
...and I shouldn't be in a relationship that has no future.
...y no debería estar en una relación que no tiene futuro.
But pretty soon, I'm gonna miss him so much...
Pero muy pronto, lo extrañaré tanto...
...I'm gonna want to see him again, and you have to stop me.
...que querré verlo de nuevo, y tienes que detenerme.
Okay, you got it.
Está bien, entendido.
Unless... Am I being too crazy about this?
A menos que... ¿Estoy siendo demasiado loca con esto?
All right, so, you know, there's no future.
Muy bien, entonces, ya sabes, no hay futuro.
But that doesn't mean we still can't have fun.
Pero eso no significa que todavía no podamos divertirnos.
- You know what? Forget what I said. - Really?
¿Sabes qué? Olvida lo que dije. ¿En serio?
- All right, if that's what you want. - That was a test, and you just failed.
Está bien, si eso es lo que quieres. Esa fue una prueba, y acabas de fallar.
Damn it! Rookie mistake.
¡Maldición! Error de novato.
I have sex with dinosaurs?
¿Tengo sexo con dinosaurios?
I believe I read that somewhere.
Creo que leí eso en alguna parte.
Not only is it not funny, it's physically impossible. Okay?
No solo no es gracioso, es físicamente imposible. ¿Está bien?
Depending on the species, I'd have to have a 6-foot-long... It's not funny!
Dependiendo de la especie, tendría que tener un... ¡No es gracioso!
I respectfully disagree.
Respetuosamente no estoy de acuerdo.
I can't believe you put that on my alumni page.
No puedo creer que pusiste eso en mi página de exalumnos.
- Who cares? Nobody reads those. - You better hope not...
¿A quién le importa? Nadie las lee. Más te vale que no...
...because I just read what you put on your page.
...porque acabo de leer lo que pusiste en tu página.
- I don't have a page. - Oh, I respectfully disagree!
No tengo página. ¡Oh, respetuosamente no estoy de acuerdo!
Look at you. All sweet and innocent, sleeping like an angel.
Mírate. Toda dulce e inocente, durmiendo como un ángel.
With Emma's chubby little hands wrapped around you.
Con las regordetas manitas de Emma a tu alrededor.
It's okay, Emma. You stay asleep.
Está bien, Emma. Sigue durmiendo.
Step away from the crib! I have a weapon!
¡Aléjate de la cuna! ¡Tengo un arma!
It's okay! It's okay, Rach! It's me! Put down the scrunchie.
¡Está bien! ¡Está bien, Rach! ¡Soy yo! Baja la cola de caballo.
- What are you doing? - Well, I heard Emma stirring...
¿Qué estás haciendo? Bueno, escuché a Emma revolverse...
...so I came in to make sure she could reach Huggsy.
...así que entré para asegurarme de que pudiera alcanzar a Huggsy.
Oh. Oh, thanks. All right, well, now that I'm up, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Oh. Oh, gracias. Está bien, bueno, ahora que estoy despierta, voy al baño.
Okay, there you go, sweetie.
Está bien, ahí tienes, cariño.
This isn't over.
Esto no ha terminado.
Wait a second. Why would Ross tell everyone in your class...
Espera un segundo. ¿Por qué Ross le diría a todos en tu clase...
...that you are "as gay as the day is long"?
...que eres "tan gay como el día es largo"?
Because I told everyone he slept with dinosaurs.
Porque le dije a todos que durmió con dinosaurios.
Well, that's clearly a joke. This could easily be true.
Bueno, eso es claramente una broma. Esto podría ser fácilmente verdad.
Would you get that, please? People have been calling to congratulate me all day.
¿Podrías contestar eso, por favor? La gente ha estado llamando para felicitarme todo el día.
Hello?
¿Hola?
No, he's not here. Yeah, this is his wife.
No, no está aquí. Sí, esta es su esposa.
Yeah. Well, it came as quite a shock to me too.
Sí. Bueno, a mí también me pareció una gran sorpresa.
Well, I guess I should've known. Yeah.
Bueno, supongo que debería haberlo sabido. Sí.
He just kept making me watch Moulin Rouge.
No dejaba de hacerme ver Moulin Rouge.
Hang up-Hang UP-
Cuelga-¡CUELGA!-
And that was a great movie.
Y esa fue una gran película.
I'm so gonna get back at Ross.
Me voy a vengar de Ross.
Oh, yeah, this'll show him. Here we go.
Oh, sí, esto le mostrará. Aquí vamos.
- What are you doing? - Oh, you'll see, my friend!
[ERROR API]
I'm dead?
And so young.
[ERROR API]
Posting that I died? That really isn't funny.
Well, how you died was funny.
[ERROR API]
Oh, please. Hit by a blimp?
It kills over one Americans every year.
[ERROR API]
Unbelievable. My classmates are gonna think I'm dead.
My professors. My parents are gonna get phone calls.
[ERROR API]
You're messing with people's feelings here.
You wanna talk about people's feelings?
[ERROR API]
You should have heard how hurt Professor Stern was...
...when I told him I wouldn't be able to go with him to Key West!
[ERROR API]
You've really crossed a line here. But that's okay.
Because I'm on my way to buy some Photoshop software...
[ERROR API]
...and a stack of gay porn.
That's right. Your coming-out is about to get real graphic!
[ERROR API]
God, I wish Mike were here.
Okay, if Mike were here, what would the two of you be doing?
[ERROR API]
What are you, animals? It's 4:00 in the afternoon.
I gotta call him. Just to talk to him. There's no harm in that.
[ERROR API]
Phoebe, that's how it starts.
"I don't need to eat the cake, I'll just smell the icing.
[ERROR API]
Why not just a little sliver?" Or, "Okay, just a slice or two."
You know, the next thing you know, you're 210 pounds...
[ERROR API]
...and you get wedged in going down the tunnel slide.
Phoebe, honey, I know this is hard.
[ERROR API]
But look, if you talk to him, then you're gonna want to see him.
And if you see him, you're gonna wanna get back together.
[ERROR API]
And I know that's not what you want.
All right, so give me your phone.
[ERROR API]
- Here. - Thank you.
Aquí. - Gracias.
- And now your cell. - Okay.
[ERROR API]
There you go.
Ahí tienes.
- This is your cell phone? - Yes.
[ERROR API]
This is your current cell phone?
Yes. It reminds me of a simpler time.
[ERROR API]
Phoebe? Where's your purse?
“Hey! No! - No!
[ERROR API]
- Give it to me! - You can't have it.
- Give it to me! - No.
[ERROR API]
- I'll go in there. - Oh, yeah.
- Come here! - No!
[ERROR API]
- Give it to me! - You're crazy! God.
Aha!
[ERROR API]
Damn you, Monica Geller hyphen Bing!
Hey, look who's here. It's Joey. And he brought home a friend.
[ERROR API]
Joey, Emma's right here.
You promised not to bring girls home in the middle of the day anymore.
[ERROR API]
No, no, no, it's not a girl. It's...
- ...a brand-new Huggsy! - Oh.
- ¡...un Huggsy nuevecito! - Oh.
Oh, that's so great. Now Emma has two Huggsies.
Oh, qué genial. Ahora Emma tiene dos Huggsies.
No, no. Oh, no. No, Emma has one Huggsy.
No, no. Oh, no. No, Emma tiene un Huggsy.
The new Huggsy. Huh?
El nuevo Huggsy. ¿Eh?
The other Huggsy, I don't know, I guess I'll just take him back.
El otro Huggsy, no sé, supongo que me lo llevo de vuelta.
You know what? When I was a little girl, I had a little pink pony named Cotton.
¿Sabes qué? Cuando era niña, tenía un ponito rosa llamado Cotton.
Oh, I loved her so much. I took her everywhere. I would braid her tail...
La quería tanto. La llevaba a todas partes. Le trenzaba la cola...
Make the transfer!
¡Haz la transferencia!
Should I be concerned that a button fell off the old Huggsy and I can't find it?
¿Debería preocuparme de que se le cayera un botón al viejo Huggsy y no lo encuentro?
Don't worry about it. I swallowed that years ago. Hey.
No te preocupes. Me lo tragué hace años. Oye.
Oh, what? I don't think she likes the new Huggsy.
Oh, ¿qué? No creo que le guste el nuevo Huggsy.
- But he's the same. - I think she wants the old one back.
- Pero si es el mismo. - Creo que quiere el viejo de vuelta.
- Yeah, but he's the same. - Joey, come on.
- Sí, pero es el mismo. - Joey, vamos.
But he's the same.
Pero es el mismo.
You're not the same.
Tú no eres el mismo.
Aha!
¡Ajá!
You know, it's a lot less surprising to do that...
Sabes, es mucho menos sorprendente hacer eso...
...after I've buzzed you into the building.
...después de que te di acceso al edificio.
So, Phoebe, why are there men's shoes by the door?
Entonces, Phoebe, ¿por qué hay zapatos de hombre junto a la puerta?
- Those are my shoes. - Oh.
- Son mis zapatos. - Oh.
Well, when you get over this breakup, we need to go shopping.
Bueno, cuando superes esta ruptura, tenemos que ir de compras.
Look, Monica, I really appreciate you checking in on me.
Mira, Monica, aprecio mucho que te preocupes por mí.
- But I'm actually feeling a lot better. - You are?
- Pero en realidad me siento mucho mejor. - ¿Sí?
Yeah, I just kind of want to be alone right now.
Sí, solo quiero estar sola ahora mismo.
- Who's that? - I ordered Chinese food.
- ¿Quién es? - Pedí comida china.
What are the chances?
¿Qué probabilidades hay?
One billion Chinese people, and they send Mike!
Mil millones de chinos, ¡y mandan a Mike!
- What are you doing here? - Phoebe called me.
- ¿Qué haces aquí? - Me llamó Phoebe.
- Phoebe! - I'm sorry. I broke down.
- ¡Phoebe! - Lo siento. Me derrumbé.
I wanted to see him.
Quería verlo.
Damn it, Phoebe, how did you even call him?
Maldición, Phoebe, ¿cómo lo llamaste?
There's a speakerphone on the base unit.
Hay un altavoz en la unidad base.
Base unit. Think, Monica, think!
Unidad base. ¡Piensa, Monica, piensa!
- Look, if I want to see Phoebe, and she... - This doesn't concern you.
- Mira, si quiero ver a Phoebe, y ella... - Esto no te concierne.
Sorry. I guess I was thrown off by the mention of my name.
Lo siento. Supongo que me desconcertó que mencionaran mi nombre.
Look, guys, you can't do this.
Miren, chicos, no pueden hacer esto.
It's gonna make getting over each other harder.
Va a hacer que superarse sea más difícil.
Not if nothing happens. Why can't we just hang out as friends?
No si no pasa nada. ¿Por qué no podemos simplemente pasar el rato como amigos?
Sure. If you're just gonna hang out as friends, then maybe I'll join you.
Claro. Si solo van a pasar el rato como amigos, entonces tal vez me una.
I'm your friend and Mike's friend.
Soy tu amiga y la amiga de Mike.
Well...
Bueno...
Sit down.
Siéntate.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Make room for your friend.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hazle espacio a tu amigo.
- So how have you been? - I've been pretty good.
- ¿Cómo has estado? - He estado bastante bien.
- You look really beautiful. - Thanks. You look good too.
- Te ves muy hermosa. - Gracias. Tú también te ves bien.
No, no, no. This is dangerous territory. Keep it clean.
No, no, no. Este es territorio peligroso. Mantenlo limpio.
So how's the piano playing going?
¿Cómo va lo de tocar el piano?
Actually, I've been playing a lot of love songs lately.
En realidad, he estado tocando muchas canciones de amor últimamente.
- I've missed you. - I've missed you too.
- Te he extrañado. - Yo también te he extrañado.
You know, on the way over here, I saw this drunk guy throw up.
Sabes, de camino aquí, vi a un tipo borracho vomitar.
And then a pigeon ate it.
Y luego una paloma se lo comió.
Hey. Ross.
Oye. Ross.
Look, I just wanted to apologize.
Mira, solo quería disculparme.
Don't tell me you actually made those gay pictures of me.
No me digas que en realidad hiciste esas fotos mías gay.
Uh-huh, uh-huh. Check this out.
Ajá, ajá. Mira esto.
So that's what I'd look like if I worked out.
Así que así me vería si hiciera ejercicio.
And was being serviced by a policeman.
Y estuviera siendo atendido por un policía.
You're not gonna actually send these out, are you?
No vas a enviar esto de verdad, ¿verdad?
Actually, I don't need to, because your little "Ross is dead" joke didn't work.
En realidad, no necesito hacerlo, porque tu pequeña broma de "Ross está muerto" no funcionó.
Okay? There were no responses.
¿Okay? No hubo respuestas.
Nobody posted anything on the website, nobody called my parents...
Nadie publicó nada en la página web, nadie llamó a mis padres...
...so the joke, my friend, is on you.
...así que la broma, amigo mío, es tuya.
Nobody called, nobody wrote anything, nobody cares that I'm dead.
Nadie llamó, nadie escribió nada, a nadie le importa que esté muerto.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
- Nobody cares that I'm dead? - Oh, come on, you know that's not true.
- ¿A nadie le importa que esté muerto? - Ay, vamos, sabes que eso no es verdad.
What are you talking about? You get 60 responses...
¿De qué estás hablando? Recibes 60 respuestas...
...just for coming out of the closet.
...solo por salir del armario.
I didn't get one response, and I'm dead!
¡No recibí una sola respuesta, y estoy muerto!
Well, the gay community is a lot more vocal than the dead community.
Bueno, la comunidad gay es mucho más vocal que la comunidad de muertos.
I can't believe this. Not even my geology lab partner. And I carried that guy.
No puedo creer esto. Ni siquiera mi compañero de laboratorio de geología. Y yo cargué a ese tipo.
All right. Look, let's think about this, okay?
Está bien. Mira, pensemos en esto, ¿vale?
You think people are gonna disturb your family at this tragic time?
¿Crees que la gente va a molestar a tu familia en este momento trágico?
That people are gonna post condolences on a website?
¿Que la gente va a publicar condolencias en una página web?
This isn't about people not caring that you're dead.
Esto no se trata de que a la gente no le importe que estés muerto.
This is about people not having a decent outlet for their grief.
Esto se trata de que la gente no tenga un canal decente para su dolor.
- You're right. There isn't a decent outlet. - Right.
- Tienes razón. No hay un canal decente. - Exacto.
Come on. I'm sure if you had a funeral or memorial service...
Vamos. Estoy segura de que si tuvieras un funeral o un servicio conmemorativo...
...tons of people would come.
...vendría muchísima gente.
Exactly!
¡Exacto!
Ross, what are you doing?
Ross, ¿qué estás haciendo?
You're having a memorial service for yourself?
¿Estás organizando un servicio conmemorativo para ti?
No, that would be stupid. You're having it for me.
No, eso sería estúpido. Lo estás organizando para mí.
- Ross, don't press send. Don't press... - No, too late. Too late. It's sent.
- Ross, no presiones enviar. No presiones... - No, demasiado tarde. Demasiado tarde. Ya está enviado.
Sorry, so is that picture of you and the policeman.
Lo siento, así que esa foto tuya con el policía.
I'm trying to put Emma down for a nap. Have you seen Huggsy?
Estoy intentando que Emma duerma la siesta. ¿Has visto a Huggsy?
Uh, original or crappy?
¿Uh, original o chapucero?
- Original. - No. Sorry. Haven't seen him.
- ¿Original? - No. Lo siento. No lo he visto.
Then what's that big lump under your covers'?
Entonces, ¿qué es esa gran bulto debajo de tus sábanas?
- It's Monica, okay? - That's not Monica!
- Es Monica, ¿vale? - ¡Esa no es Monica!
All right, fine! It's original Huggsy!
¡Está bien, vale! ¡Es el Huggsy original!
I know Emma wants him, but he's mine and I need him.
Sé que Emma lo quiere, pero es mío y lo necesito.
She's being unreasonable.
Ella está siendo irrazonable.
Joey, there is a reason that Emma loves that stupid penguin so much!
Joey, hay una razón por la que Emma ama tanto a ese estúpido pingüino.
Oh, don't cover its ears!
¡Oh, no le tapes las orejas!
It's because it reminds her of her Uncle Joey.
Es porque le recuerda a su tío Joey.
- It does? - Yeah.
- ¿Sí? - Sí.
And she's comforted by him because she loves her Uncle Joey so much.
Y él la consuela porque ama mucho a su tío Joey.
- Really? She loves me? - Oh, yeah.
- ¿En serio? ¿Me ama? - Oh, sí.
But you know what? If you need Huggsy, don't worry.
Pero, ¿sabes qué? Si necesitas a Huggsy, no te preocupes.
Emma will totally understand. I won't, but whatever.
Emma lo entenderá totalmente. Yo no, pero bueno.
Okay, wait a minute, wait a minute, Rach. I mean, if...
Okay, espera un minuto, espera un minuto, Rach. Quiero decir, si...
If Huggsy means that much to Emma, then...
Si Huggsy significa tanto para Emma, entonces...
Well, she can have him.
Bueno, ella puede tenerlo.
Oh, sweet, I knew Uncle Joey would step up.
Oh, genial, sabía que el tío Joey ayudaría.
- Look, Emma. Look who's back. - No, forget it! Forget it! I can't do it!
- Mira, Emma. Mira quién volvió. - No, ¡olvídalo! ¡Olvídalo! ¡No puedo hacerlo!
Are you...? You're gonna take Huggsy away from a little child?
¿Vas a...? ¿Le vas a quitar a Huggsy a una niña pequeña?
How do you think I got him in the first place?
¿Cómo crees que lo conseguí en primer lugar?
All right, you two. I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Está bien, ustedes dos. Voy a ir al baño.
I don't want anything going on while I'm gone.
No quiero que pase nada mientras no estoy.
Here's a few things you can discuss:
Aquí hay algunas cosas que pueden discutir:
Mucus, fungus, and the idea of me and Ross doing it.
Mocos, hongos y la idea de Ross y yo haciéndolo.
I've missed you so much.
Te he extrañado tanto.
I'm not gonna ask you to get back together. I know we want different things, but...
No te voy a pedir que vuelvan a estar juntos. Sé que queremos cosas diferentes, pero...
- Just to be with you one more night. - I want that too.
- Solo para estar contigo una noche más. - Yo también quiero eso.
- But is that gonna make it too hard? - It can't be any harder than this.
- ¿Pero eso lo hará demasiado difícil? - No puede ser más difícil que esto.
I mean, if I had known the last time I saw you would be the last time, I...
Quiero decir, si hubiera sabido que la última vez que te vi sería la última vez, yo...
I would have stopped to memorize your face, the way you moved.
Me habría detenido a memorizar tu cara, tu forma de moverte.
Everything about you.
Todo sobre ti.
If I had known the last time I kissed you would be the last time...
Si hubiera sabido que la última vez que te besé sería la última vez...
...I never would have stopped.
...nunca me habría detenido.
Kiss him, you fool!
¡Bésalo, tonto!
- What? - Didn't you hear that speech?
- ¿Qué? - ¿No oíste ese discurso?
If you don't kiss him, then I will.
Si no lo besas, entonces lo haré yo.
I missed you so much.
Te extrañé muchísimo.
- I knew you'd be here! - Aw, crap.
- ¡Sabía que estarías aquí! - Ay, mierda.
- Who is this? - It's my friend Manny.
- ¿Quién es? - Es mi amigo Manny.
I asked him to keep me away from you.
Le pedí que me mantuviera alejada de ti.
- Hey, that's what I'm doing for Phoebe. - Well, you're not doing a very good job.
- Oye, eso es lo que estoy haciendo por Phoebe. - Bueno, no lo estás haciendo muy bien.
- Excuse me? - What's with the kissing?
- ¿Disculpa? - ¿Qué pasa con los besos?
Hey, at least I knew where my guy was.
Oye, al menos sabía dónde estaba mi chico.
Yeah, thank God you were here to oversee all the kissing.
Sí, gracias a Dios que estabas aquí para supervisar todos los besos.
- You didn't hear the speech. - I've heard the speech.
- No oíste el discurso. - He oído el discurso.
If he knew it was gonna be the last time...
Si hubiera sabido que iba a ser la última vez...
Hey, it was very moving. You're just heartless!
Oye, fue muy conmovedor. ¡Eres simplemente descorazonada!
- You're weak! - You're weird!
- ¡Eres débil! - ¡Eres rara!
- Your pants are undone. - Oh!
- Tienes los pantalones desabrochados. - ¡Oh!
Where'd they go?
¿A dónde fueron?
- Damn it. - Well, we blew it.
- Maldición. - Bueno, la fastidiamos.
I blame myself.
Me culpo a mí misma.
And I blame you too.
Y yo también te culpo a ti.
It's been an hour, and not one of my classmates has shown up?
Ha pasado una hora, ¿y ninguno de mis compañeros de clase ha aparecido?
I tell you, when I actually die, some people are gonna get seriously haunted.
Te digo, cuando muera de verdad, algunas personas se van a asustar mucho.
There you go. Someone came.
Ahí tienes. Alguien vino.
Okay. Okay. I'm gonna go hide.
Okay. Okay. Me voy a esconder.
This is so exciting. My first mourner!
Esto es tan emocionante. ¡Mi primer doliente!
Hi. Glad you could come.
Hola. Me alegra que hayas podido venir.
- Please come in. - Hi. You're Chandler Bing, right?
- Por favor, pasa. - Hola. Eres Chandler Bing, ¿verdad?
- I'm Tom Gordon. I was in your class. - Oh, yes. Yes, let me take your coat.
- Soy Tom Gordon. Estuve en tu clase. - Oh, sí. Sí, déjame tomar tu abrigo.
Thanks. Uh, I'm so sorry about Ross, it's...
Gracias. Uh, lamento mucho lo de Ross, es...
No, at least he died doing what he loved.
No, al menos murió haciendo lo que amaba.
Watching blimps.
Viendo dirigibles.
- Who is it? - You know some guy, Tom Gordon?
- ¿Quién es? - ¿Conoces a un tipo, Tom Gordon?
I don't remember him.
No lo recuerdo.
But then again, I touched so many lives.
Pero bueno, toqué tantas vidas.
So did you know Ross well?
¿Conocías bien a Ross?
Actually, I barely knew him. I came because I heard Chandler's news.
En realidad, apenas lo conocía. Vine porque escuché las noticias de Chandler.
Do you know if he's seeing anyone?
¿Sabes si está saliendo con alguien?
- Yes, he is. Me. - What? You mean...? Oh.
- Sí, conmigo. - ¿Qué? ¿Quieres decir...? Oh.
Can I ask you a personal question? How do you shave your beard so close'?
¿Puedo hacerte una pregunta personal? ¿Cómo te afeitas tan al ras?
Okay, Tommy! That's enough mourning for you.
¡Ya basta, Tommy! Has llorado suficiente.
Here we go. Bye-bye. All right.
Aquí vamos. Adiós. Muy bien.
- Hey, listen. Call me. - Okay.
- Oye, escucha. Llámame. - De acuerdo.
- I'm dead and no one cares? - I look like a man?
- ¿Estoy muerto y a nadie le importa? - ¿Parece un hombre?
Please, one ridiculous problem at a time.
Por favor, un problema ridículo a la vez.
This isn't ridiculous. Look around, no one's here.
Esto no es ridículo. Mira alrededor, no hay nadie.
You gave them one day's notice. Not everyone checks the website every day.
Les diste un día de aviso. No todos revisan la página web todos los días.
And Monica, it's probably the way you stand!
Y Monica, ¡probablemente sea tu forma de pararte!
I guess you're right. Still, somebody must have seen it.
Supongo que tienes razón. Aun así, alguien debió haberlo visto.
I mean, I went to that school for four years and I didn't have an impact on anyone?
O sea, ¿fui a esa escuela por cuatro años y no impacté a nadie?
Well, that's not true. You had an impact on me.
Bueno, eso no es cierto. Me impactaste.
I mean, it's 15 years later and we're still best friends.
O sea, han pasado 15 años y seguimos siendo los mejores amigos.
Doesn't that count for something?
¿Eso no cuenta para algo?
Oh, great, more party boys for Chandler.
Oh, genial, más fiesteros para Chandler.
I'm sure it's somebody for you. Now go hide.
Seguro que hay alguien para ti. Ahora escóndete.
Hi. I'm here for Ross Geller's memorial service.
Hola. Vengo al servicio conmemorativo de Ross Geller.
- Kori? Kori Weston? - Yeah.
- ¿Kori? ¿Kori Weston? - Sí.
- You look amazing. - And you are?
- Te ves increíble. - ¿Y tú quién eres?
Chandler. Chandler Bing. And I'm not gay. I'm not gay at all.
Chandler. Chandler Bing. Y no soy gay. Para nada soy gay.
You are married, though.
Aunque estás casado.
Don't listen to him. He's in a really bad mood.
No le hagas caso. Está de muy mal humor.
I can't believe that Ross is gone. It is just so sad.
No puedo creer que Ross se haya ido. Es muy triste.
I didn't know Ross and you were so close.
No sabía que tú y Ross fueran tan cercanos.
Oh, we weren't. But we had one class together. He was such a great guy.
Oh, no lo éramos. Pero tuvimos una clase juntos. Era un gran tipo.
And he talked so passionately about science.
Y hablaba con tanta pasión sobre ciencia.
- I always remembered him. - I'm sure that would mean a lot to him.
- Siempre lo recordé. - Seguro que eso significaría mucho para él.
And if heaven has a door...
Y si el cielo tiene una puerta...
...I'm sure he's pressing his ear up against it and listening intently.
...estoy segura de que está pegando su oído contra ella y escuchando atentamente.
I thought so many times about calling him and asking him out.
Pensé muchas veces en llamarlo y pedirle una cita.
I guess I really missed my chance.
Supongo que realmente perdí mi oportunidad.
No, you didn't!
¡No, no fuiste!
I'm still alive!
¡Todavía estoy viva!
Kori, I know this is a big surprise for you.
Kori, sé que esto es una gran sorpresa para ti.
It's a long story. But the things you just said really made my day.
Es una larga historia. Pero lo que acabas de decir realmente alegró mi día.
The fact that you're here means more to me...
El hecho de que estés aquí significa más para mí...
...than if this room were filled with people.
...que si esta sala estuviera llena de gente.
You sick freak! Who does that?
¡Tú, enfermo! ¿Quién hace eso?
I can't believe I had a crush on you.
No puedo creer que me gustaras.
Did you hear that?
¿Oíste eso?
Kori Weston had a crush on me!
¡Kori Weston me gustaba!
No, Mom, I am not dead.
No, mamá, ¡no estoy muerta!
I know it's not something to kid about.
Sé que no es algo para tomarse a broma.
It was just a practical joke between Chandler and me, but it's over, okay?
Era solo una broma entre Chandler y yo, pero ya terminó, ¿de acuerdo?
Actually, no. Even if I had died, you would not be left childless.
En realidad, no. Incluso si hubiera muerto, tú no te habrías quedado sin hijos.
Monica?
¿Monica?