Previously on Friends:
Anteriormente en Friends:
Don't come out here.
[ERROR API]
- I ran into Richard. - Which Richard?
My ex-boyfriend.
[ERROR API]
This is the worst thing that could happen.
You decided to tell him about the Richard thing.
[ERROR API]
Oh, no.
- You can't see him. - You can't tell me what to do.
[ERROR API]
That's funny, I think I just did.
- I have found my identical hand twin. - What's that?
[ERROR API]
A guy with my identical hands. I'm gonna be a millionaire!
You thought I wanted to have sex with you?
[ERROR API]
No.
Last night was embarrassing for you too.
[ERROR API]
I just don't embarrass that easily.
- I think the check-in is that way. - Ah.
[ERROR API]
Hello.
Hola.
Ah, kids love me.
[ERROR API]
Hey! Hi. You guys are here!
Yay! What'd you do? Did you go to a costume party?
[ERROR API]
Let me guess. Um, Pancho Villa.
And you're Bob Saget.
[ERROR API]
Pancho Villa?
What are you talking about, Pheebs? I don't...
[ERROR API]
Oh, my God! You drew on me?
Hey, you wet my pants!
[ERROR API]
Whoa, what kind of party was this?
I've been walking around like this? You have so crossed a line.
[ERROR API]
Rach, wait. The men's room is that way.
- Oh! - What?
[ERROR API]
It's the third time she's won on a machine I was playing.
Oh. I bet she's one of those people.
[ERROR API]
Mole people?
What? No, a lurker.
[ERROR API]
Oh. What's that?
When you're playing a machine and it hasn't paid out...
[ERROR API]
...a lurker waits for you to give up and then...
Kills you?
[ERROR API]
No, they swoop in and steal your jackpot.
- Oh. - Mm-hm.
[ERROR API]
- How do you know about this? - My nana used to do it.
That's how she paid for my dance... Karate lessons.
[ERROR API]
Dance karate?
Yes, it's a deadly...
[ERROR API]
...but beautiful sport.
- It won't come off. - What?
[ERROR API]
It won't come off.
Oh, my God. Rach, are you sure?
[ERROR API]
I took it off, and then I drew it back on.
Hey! You made it!
[ERROR API]
Who's your friend? He's hot.
¿Quién es tu amigo? Está buenísimo.
Thanks, man.
Gracias, amigo.
Listen, I talked to Chandler, and I'm sorry about the movie.
Oye, hablé con Chandler y lamento lo de la película.
Don't be sorry.
No te disculpes.
I don't need it anymore. I found my identical hand twin.
Ya no lo necesito. Encontré a mi gemelo de mano idéntico.
Your what?
¿Tu qué?
My identical hand twin. The person whose hands are like mine.
Mi gemelo de mano idéntico. La persona cuyas manos son como las mías.
This is a gold mine.
Esto es una mina de oro.
What?
¿Qué?
That won't make you any money.
Eso no te dará dinero.
Well, fine.
Bueno, está bien.
None of you will live with me in my hand-shaped mansion.
Ninguno de ustedes vivirá conmigo en mi mansión con forma de mano.
Except, uh, you. You can live in the thumb.
Excepto, eh, tú. Tú puedes vivir en el pulgar.
All right, baby, come on!
¡Vamos, nena, vamos!
Yes! Yes!
¡Sí! ¡Sí!
- I am on fire! - See you later.
- ¡Estoy que ardo! - Hasta luego.
What are you doing?
¿Qué estás haciendo?
What's it look like? Going home.
¿Cómo se ve? Me voy a casa.
Why?
¿Por qué?
Chandler.
Chandler, wait.
Chandler, espera.
Sorry, I was just playing for one second.
Perdón, solo estaba jugando un segundo.
If you don't want me to see Richard again, I won't.
Si no quieres que vuelva a ver a Richard, no lo haré.
He means nothing to me.
No significa nada para mí.
Oh, come on. I was there.
Ay, vamos. Yo estuve ahí.
I know he's the love of your life.
Sé que es el amor de tu vida.
Not anymore.
Ya no.
Really?
¿En serio?
Really.
En serio.
All right?
¿De acuerdo?
Let's forget about going home and celebrate our anniversary.
Olvidemos ir a casa y celebremos nuestro aniversario.
Okay, this is empty.
Vale, esto está vacío.
I wanted to make a dramatic scene, but I hate packing.
Quería hacer una escena dramática, pero odio empacar.
Where's the other guy?
¿Dónde está el otro tipo?
Which guy?
¿Qué tipo?
Tall, dark hair, hand looks exactly like this?
¿Alto, pelo oscuro, mano que se ve exactamente así?
I don't know about the hands, but he went to the restroom.
No sé lo de las manos, pero fue al baño.
Okay.
- How you doing? - Very busy.
- ¿Cómo estás? - Muy ocupado.
Right. Okay.
Bien. De acuerdo.
Yes, hello. I have a question.
Sí, hola. Tengo una pregunta.
Um, I used your pen to draw on my friend's face.
Um, usé tu bolígrafo para dibujar en la cara de mi amiga.
A beard and a mustache.
Una barba y un bigote.
Thank you.
Gracias.
No, she didn't think so.
No, ella no lo creyó.
I know. It's like... Anyway...
Lo sé. Es como... De todos modos...
Makeup didn't cover it. We've tried everything, and nothing's worked.
El maquillaje no lo cubrió. Hemos intentado de todo y nada ha funcionado.
What do we do?
¿Qué hacemos?
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Sí. Ajá.
Yeah. Oh, okay.
Sí. Oh, de acuerdo.
Okay, thank you.
Ok, gracias.
Yeah, it's not coming off.
Sí, no se quita.
What? What else did he say?
¿Qué? ¿Qué más dijo?
Um, he said he thought I was funny.
Mmm, dijo que pensaba que era graciosa.
Okay, look. Let's just go downstairs...
Okay, mira. Bajemos...
...we'll have some fun, and you will forget all about it.
...nos divertiremos un poco y olvidarás todo.
There's no way I am leaving looking like this!
¡De ninguna manera me voy a ir así!
Come on, Rach. It's not that bad.
Vamos, Rach. No está tan mal.
Ross, I am a human doodle!
Ross, ¡soy un garabato humano!
Just because some idiot drew on your face doesn't mean you can't have fun.
Solo porque algún idiota te dibujó en la cara no significa que no puedas divertirte.
Besides, no one will even look at you.
Además, nadie te mirará.
This is Vegas. Hello? There are tons of other freaks here.
Esto es Las Vegas. ¿Hola? Hay un montón de otros raros aquí.
There are tons of freaks here. No other. No.
Hay un montón de raros aquí. Ningún otro. No.
Come on. No one will notice. I swear.
Vamos. Nadie se dará cuenta. Lo juro.
There was some staring and pointing.
Hubo algunas miradas y señalamientos.
I need a drink.
Necesito una copa.
They really overcharge you for that stuff.
Realmente te cobran de más por esas cosas.
But who cares, because it's all on me.
Pero, ¿a quién le importa? Porque todo corre por mi cuenta.
That is one big drink.
Esa es una copa grande.
Macadamia nut?
¿Nuez de macadamia?
Um, wow! That's some pricey nut.
Mmm, ¡wow! Esa es una nuez cara.
Really like those macadamia nuts, huh?
Te gustan mucho esas nueces de macadamia, ¿eh?
Nope.
No.
Get out of here, you lurker!
¡Fuera de aquí, acechador!
Go on, get!
¡Vete!
- Hey, Pheebs. - You made up.
- Hola, Pheebs. - Se reconciliaron.
I couldn't be mad at him for too long.
No pude estar enojada con él por mucho tiempo.
She couldn't live without the "Chand love."
Ella no podía vivir sin el "amor de Chandler".
Aw.
Ay.
Get a room.
Consigan un cuarto.
- We have one. - I know. Use it.
- Tenemos uno. - Lo sé. Úsenlo.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, sí.
That's right. Take good care of those babies.
Así es. Cuida bien a esos bebés.
- Excuse me? - It's me. Joey.
- ¿Disculpa? - Soy yo. Joey.
Do I know you?
¿Te conozco?
Joey?
¿Joey?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, sí.
Yeah, the hand guy.
Sí, el del las manos.
So, what are we gonna do about this hand twin thing?
Entonces, ¿qué vamos a hacer con esto de los gemelos de manos?
Nothing.
Nada.
Look, you and I have been given a gift.
Mira, tú y yo hemos recibido un don.
We have to do something with it. Like hand modeling. Or magic.
Tenemos que hacer algo con él. Como modelaje de manos. O magia.
And you know NASA's gonna want to talk to us.
Y sabes que la NASA querrá hablar con nosotros.
- I have to get back to work. - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Tengo que volver al trabajo. - Quieto, quieto, quieto.
We can have our own show.
Podemos tener nuestro propio programa.
We can clap our hands together. People will love it!
Podemos aplaudir juntos. ¡A la gente le encantará!
Huh?
¿Eh?
And I wrote a song for us.
Y escribí una canción para nosotros.
This hand is your hand
Esta mano es tu mano
This hand is my hand
Esta mano es mi mano
Oh, wait, that's your hand
Oh, espera, esa es tu mano
No, wait, it's my hand
No, espera, es mi mano
- That's okay. - But you haven't even heard the chorus!
- Está bien. - ¡Pero ni siquiera has oído el coro!
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
I look like my great-aunt, Muriel.
Me parezco a mi tía abuela, Muriel.
All right, you know what?
Está bien, ¿sabes qué?
We don't have to go downstairs.
No tenemos que bajar.
We can bring Vegas up to us.
Podemos traer Vegas hasta nosotros.
All right, come on.
Está bien, vamos.
We'll play some blackjack. Here we go.
Jugaremos al blackjack. Aquí vamos.
- Thirteen. - Hit me.
- Trece. - Dame otra.
Ooh, 23.
Which is what we play to at this casino!
¡Que es a lo que jugamos en este casino!
You win $10!
¡Ganas $10!
- I bet 20. - Right.
- Apuesto 20. - Correcto.
A new pair of shoes for the Chan-Chan man!
¡Un par de zapatos nuevos para el Chan-Chan man!
Yes!
¡Sí!
I've never seen a roll like this!
¡Nunca había visto una tirada como esta!
That's right, baby!
¡Así es, nena!
What do I want now?
¿Qué quiero ahora?
Eight? Uh, six.
¿Ocho? Uh, seis.
Pick a number! That is your only job.
¡Elige un número! Ese es tu único trabajo.
- Eight. - Thank you.
- Ocho. - Gracias.
If you get this, we buy everybody a steak dinner.
Si sacas esto, invitamos a todos a cenar un filete.
- Eight it is. - Yes!
- Ocho está decidido. - ¡Sí!
We're not buying steak dinners, are we?
No vamos a comprar cenas de filete, ¿verdad?
- No. - Okay, good.
- No. - Okay, bien.
- What do I want now? - Try a hard eight.
- ¿Qué quiero ahora? - Prueba un ocho difícil.
- What? - Two fours.
- ¿Qué? - Dos cuatros.
Eight!
¡Ocho!
Don't you let her go. You're a lucky guy.
No la dejes ir. Eres un tipo con suerte.
Thank you, Mr. Drunken Gambler.
Gracias, señor Borracho Jugador.
You get this, and, uh, we get the biggest suite in the place.
Si sacas esto, y, eh, conseguimos la suite más grande del lugar.
We get the biggest suite in the place.
Conseguimos la suite más grande del lugar.
The biggest suite in the place!
¡La suite más grande del lugar!
Come on!
¡Vamos!
I love you! I can't remember why we fought.
¡Te amo! No recuerdo por qué peleamos.
Because I had lunch with Rich...
Porque almorcé con Rich...
Me neither!
¡Yo tampoco!
- What now? - Uh, another hard eight.
- ¿Ahora qué? - Uh, otro ocho difícil.
Hard eight? Let's call it easy eight!
¿Ocho difícil? ¡Llamémoslo ocho fácil!
I'll tell you what. You roll another hard eight...
Te digo una cosa. Si sacas otro ocho difícil...
...and we get married here, tonight.
...y nos casamos aquí, esta noche.
Shut up!
¡Cállate!
It just got interesting!
¡Esto se acaba de poner interesante!
What did you say?
¿Qué dijiste?
You roll another eight, we get married tonight.
Si sacas otro ocho, nos casamos esta noche.
- You serious? - Yes. I love you.
- ¿Hablas en serio? - Sí. Te amo.
I've never loved anybody as much as I love you.
Nunca he amado a nadie tanto como te amo a ti.
So if an eight comes up, we take it as a sign and we do it.
Así que si sale un ocho, lo tomamos como una señal y lo hacemos.
What do you say?
¿Qué dices?
- Okay. - Okay.
- Vale. - Vale.
Hard eight.
Ocho, el difícil.
That's a four. And where's the other one?
Esa es un cuatro. ¿Y dónde está la otra?
- Under the table. - Nobody move!
- Debajo de la mesa. - ¡Nadie se mueva!
You look that way, I look this way.
Tú miras para allá, yo miro para acá.
Here it is, here it is.
Aquí está, aquí está.
That could be 4 or 5.
Eso podrían ser 4 o 5.
It's your call.
Tú decides.
It's a four.
Es un cuatro.
I think so too.
Yo también creo.
Oh, well, lost again.
Oh, bueno, perdí otra vez.
That's it. You and me. Outside!
¡Se acabó! Tú y yo. ¡Afuera!
I wouldn't want you to lose a chunk of that pretty blond hair!
¡No quisiera que perdieras un mechón de ese pelo rubio tan bonito!
Oh!
¡Oh!
Be cool.
Cálmate.
Okay, your lurking days are over.
Okay, tus días de acechar terminaron.
- What? - Everyone you lurk, I'll lurk first.
- ¿Qué? - Cada vez que aceches, yo acecharé primero.
You move on, I'll be one step ahead of you...
Tú sigues adelante, yo estaré un paso delante de ti...
...every single time.
...cada vez.
And then I'll be on your ass every hour of every day...
Y entonces te pisaré los talones cada hora de cada día...
...till Monday...
...hasta el lunes...
...because that's when I go home.
...porque ese es el día que me voy a casa.
- When do you leave? - Also Monday.
- ¿Cuándo te vas? - También el lunes.
What time? Maybe we can share a cab.
¿A qué hora? Quizás podamos compartir un taxi.
Hit me.
Dale.
We need more cards.
Necesitamos más cartas.
Yeah, and we also need more, um, drinks. Hold on a second.
Sí, y también necesitamos más, eh, bebidas. Espera un segundo.
Hello, Vegas?
¿Hola, Vegas?
We would like more alcohol.
Quisiéramos más alcohol.
You know what else? We would like some more beers.
¿Sabes qué más? Quisiéramos más cervezas.
Oh, I forgot to dial.
Oh, olvidé marcar.
That must be our alcohol and beers.
Debe ser nuestro alcohol y cervezas.
- Hey. - It's Joey! I love Joey!
- ¡Oye! - ¡Es Joey! ¡Amo a Joey!
Oh, I love Joey!
¡Oh, amo a Joey!
Joey lives with a duck.
Joey vive con un pato.
Look, I need some help, okay?
Mira, necesito ayuda, ¿sí?
Someone has to convince my hand twin to cooperate.
Alguien tiene que convencer a mi gemelo de mano para que coopere.
I'll do it. Whatever you need me to do, I'm your man.
Lo haré yo. Lo que necesites que haga, soy tu hombre.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Are you okay?
¿Estás bien?
Yeah. Fine. Thanks.
Sí. Bien. Gracias.
Hey, Rach?
Oye, Rach?
How you doing?
¿Cómo estás?
I'm doing good, baby. How you doing?
Estoy bien, nena. ¿Cómo estás tú?
Don't let her drink anymore.
No dejes que beba más.
Here's that macadamia nut.
Aquí tienes esa nuez de macadamia.
- No, something else. - Oops.
- No, otra cosa. - Ups.
So, what do you wanna do now?
Entonces, ¿qué quieres hacer ahora?
I wanna get out of the room.
Quiero salir de la habitación.
I really miss downstairs.
Realmente extraño la planta baja.
Okay, you know what? There is only one way I am leaving this hotel room.
Okay, ¿sabes qué? Solo hay una forma en que saldré de esta habitación de hotel.
Well, hello!
¡Bueno, hola!
I'm Ross.
Soy Ross.
- Good luck to you. - Sir, you've got a little something...
- Buena suerte. - Señor, tiene algo...
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hola. - Hola.
I won! I won! I finally won!
¡Gané! ¡Gané! ¡Finalmente gané!
I won! That was my quarter!
¡Gané! ¡Esa era mi moneda!
Take a hike, toots.
Vete a dar un paseo, bonita.
Excuse me, sir.
Disculpe, señor.
This lady played my quarter. This is my money.
Esta señora jugó mi moneda. Es mi dinero.
Is that true, miss?
¿Es eso cierto, señorita?
- Sells drugs to kids. - What?
- Vende drogas a niños. - ¿Qué?
She sells drugs to kids.
Ella vende drogas a niños.
It was my quarter.
Era mi moneda.
Was it her quarter?
¿Era su moneda?
How about we talk about this over dinner?
¿Qué tal si hablamos de esto durante la cena?
- Okay, lady, you're out of here. - No, you can't arrest me!
- Okay, señora, está fuera de aquí. - ¡No, no puede arrestarme!
I won't go back to that hellhole!
¡No volveré a ese infierno!
I'm just taking you outside.
Solo te estoy sacando.
Oh, okay.
Oh, está bien.
I need something old, something new, something borrowed and something blue.
Necesito algo viejo, algo nuevo, algo prestado y algo azul.
Here's something blue and new.
Aquí tienes algo azul y nuevo.
You are so efficient. I love you.
Eres tan eficiente. Te amo.
- Let's go. - No, wait!
- Vamos. - ¡No, espera!
We need something old.
Necesitamos algo viejo.
I have a condom in my wallet that I've had since I was 12.
Tengo un condón en mi billetera que tengo desde que tenía 12 años.
That'll work.
Eso servirá.
I don't think so.
No lo creo.
Now something borrowed.
Ahora algo prestado.
- Here, just take this. - That's stealing.
- Toma, solo toma esto. - Eso es robar.
We'll bring it back. Put it under your dress.
Lo devolveremos. Ponlo debajo de tu vestido.
Aw.
Ay.
Okay. One thing at a time.
Okay. Una cosa a la vez.
- Are you gonna play? - No, I don't really have any money.
- ¿Vas a jugar? - No, en realidad no tengo dinero.
Not yet, anyway.
Todavía no, de todos modos.
Can't sit here if you don't play.
No puedes sentarte aquí si no juegas.
Hello. My name is Regina Phalange.
Hola. Mi nombre es Regina Phalange.
I'm a businesswoman in town on business.
Soy una empresaria en la ciudad por negocios.
Would you like to see my card?
¿Le gustaría ver mi tarjeta?
What did I do with my Filofax?
¿Qué hice con mi Filofax?
I must've left it in Conference Room B.
Debo haberlo dejado en la Sala de Conferencias B.
- Fourteen. - Hit me.
- Catorce. - Dame.
Oh, my God. May I just say that you gentlemen have the exact same hands?
Oh, Dios mío. ¿Puedo decir que ustedes, caballeros, tienen exactamente las mismas manos?
They're identical.
Son idénticas.
I've never seen that in the business world.
Nunca he visto eso en el mundo de los negocios.
Stop it.
Para.
Miss Phalange, may I ask you a question as an impartial person at this table?
Señorita Phalange, ¿puedo hacerle una pregunta como persona imparcial en esta mesa?
Please stop it.
Por favor, detente.
Wouldn't you pay good money to see identical hands...
¿No pagarías buen dinero por ver manos idénticas...
...showcased in some type of an entertainment venue?
...exhibidas en algún tipo de lugar de entretenimiento?
If you leave now, I will chop off my hand and give it to you!
¡Si te vas ahora, me cortaré la mano y te la daré!
Didn't I just throw you out?
¿No te acabo de echar?
No, you threw out Phoebe.
No, echaste a Phoebe.
I'm Regina Phalange. Phalange.
Soy Regina Phalange. Phalange.
Come on, lady.
Vamos, señora.
Please take him too.
Por favor, lléveselo también.
Me? Oh, come on, man.
¿Yo? Ay, vamos, hombre.
Come on, buddy.
Vamos, amigo.
Don't let him do this. Come on!
¡No dejes que haga esto! ¡Vamos!
I'm your hand twin!
¡Soy tu gemelo de mano!
Hello. One marriage, please.
Hola. Un matrimonio, por favor.
We want to get married.
Queremos casarnos.
There's a service in progress. Have a seat.
Hay un servicio en curso. Siéntense.
All right.
De acuerdo.
What are you doing?
¿Qué estás haciendo?
The "Wedding March." Does that freak you out?
"La Marcha Nupcial". ¿Eso te asusta?
No, it's the graduation song.
No, es la canción de graduación.
Okay.
This is it. We're gonna get married.
Esto es todo. Nos vamos a casar.
You sure you wanna do this?
¿Seguro que quieres hacer esto?
Hello, Mrs. Ross!
¡Hola, Sra. Ross!
Well, hello, Mr. Rachel!
¡Pues hola, Sr. Rachel!
Wait. Okay.
Espera. Vale.