- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Wow, you look nice. What's the occasion?
Guau, te ves bien. ¿Cuál es la ocasión?
Monica and I are celebrating our 10-month anniversary.
Mónica y yo celebramos nuestro décimo aniversario.
- Got reservations at Jean-George. - Wow.
- Tengo reservación en Jean-George. - Guau.
- How'd you get in? - Oh.
- ¿Cómo entraste? - Oh.
Made a few calls, pulled some strings...
Hice unas llamadas, moví algunos hilos...
...and they'll seat us if we both have chicken and don't get dessert.
...y nos darán mesa si ambos comemos pollo y no pedimos postre.
- Hi, Chandler. - Hey, Caitlin.
- Hola, Chandler. - Hola, Caitlin.
Somebody got a haircut.
Alguien se cortó el pelo.
Ugh. I hate it. I look like an 8-year-old boy.
Ugh. Lo odio. Parezco un niño de 8 años.
If that was true, gym class would've been more interesting.
Si eso fuera cierto, la clase de gimnasia habría sido más interesante.
- It's, uh, $27 even. - Oh, okay. Here you go.
- Son, eh, $27 exactos. - Oh, está bien. Aquí tienes.
Where's the chicken?
¿Dónde está el pollo?
Oh, it's in the back. The duck pissed him off.
Oh, está atrás. El pato lo enfureció.
He said that eggs came first.
Dijo que los huevos fueron primero.
- Ha, ha, thanks. I'll see you later. - Okay. Bye.
- Ja, ja, gracias. Te veo luego. - De acuerdo. Adiós.
What the hell was that?
¿Qué demonios fue eso?
- What? - The flirting.
- ¿Qué? - Lo de coquetear.
Aren't you supposed to be going out with, hmm, let's see, my sister?
¿No se supone que ibas a salir con, mmm, a ver, mi hermana?
I was not flirting.
No estaba coqueteando.
It was totally flirting! "Somebody got a haircut..."
¡Fue totalmente coquetear! "Alguien se cortó el pelo..."
First of all, the impression? Uncanny.
Primero, la imitación. Insuperable.
Second, that wasn't flirting. That was just casual conversation between two people.
Segundo, eso no fue coquetear. Fue solo una conversación casual entre dos personas.
Oh! Yeah, right.
¡Oh! Sí, claro.
You wanna see flirting? I'll show you flirting.
¿Quieres ver coquetear? Te mostraré cómo se coquetea.
I'm good. I'm okay.
Estoy bien. Estoy bien.
I am so proud of Joey.
Estoy tan orgulloso de Joey.
- He's gonna be on Law and Order! - I know.
- ¡Va a estar en Law and Order! - Lo sé.
But don't you think it should be called Order and Law?
¿Pero no crees que debería llamarse Orden y Ley?
No, because they arrest the guy and then try him.
No, porque arrestan al tipo y luego lo juzgan.
Yeah. Don't get me started on that.
Sí. Ni me hagas empezar con eso.
- I was not flirting. - And on your anniversary. For shame!
- No estaba coqueteando. - Y en tu aniversario. ¡Qué vergüenza!
What's going on?
¿Qué está pasando?
Chandler was hitting on the hot delivery girl.
Chandler estaba intentando ligar con la chica de las entregas.
I was not. And oh, God! Shh!
No lo estaba. ¡Y, Dios mío! Shh.
I'm sorry, but you were. And besides, if anyone should be hitting on her...
Lo siento, pero sí lo estabas. Y además, si alguien debería intentar ligar con ella...
...it's the guy who's single...
...es el tipo que está soltero...
...the guy who can do something about it.
...el tipo que puede hacer algo al respecto.
Sounds like someone wants to be Mr. Pizza Delivery Girl.
Suena a que alguien quiere ser el Sr. Chica de las Entregas de Pizza.
Well...
Bueno...
Is that what this is about? You like Caitlin?
¿De esto se trata? ¿Te gusta Caitlin?
Ha, ha, Ross, we broke up two years ago. You've been married since then.
Ja, ja, Ross, terminamos hace dos años. Tú te has casado desde entonces.
I think it's okay that we see other people.
Creo que está bien que veamos a otras personas.
- I was watching her at the pizza place. - Mm-hm.
- La estaba viendo en la pizzería. - Mm-hm.
And she was just so sexy and funny and has the cutest little...
Y era tan sexy y divertida y tiene un pequeño y adorable...
We don't need her measurements. Ha, ha.
No necesitamos sus medidas. Ja, ja.
Pepperoni, pepperoni, pepperoni.
I know she's pretty and you love her, but is she stupid?
Sé que es guapa y la amas, pero ¿es tonta?
She forgot my vegetarian.
Se olvidó de mi vegetariana.
This is perfect. She'll have to come back here with your pizza.
Esto es perfecto. Tendrá que volver aquí con tu pizza.
And when she does, I will turn on the charm "au" Ross.
Y cuando lo haga, usaré mi encanto "al" estilo Ross.
Oh, I am so glad you don't eat meat. Ha, ha.
Oh, me alegra tanto que no comas carne. Ja, ja.
- See? Vegetarianism benefits everyone. - Mm.
- ¿Ves? El vegetarianismo beneficia a todos. - Mm.
Hey, everybody, look who's here! You remember my grandmother.
¡Oigan todos, miren quién llegó! ¿Recuerdan a mi abuela.
- Big night! - Yeah, it's so cool.
- ¡Gran noche! - Sí, es genial.
Joey on Law and Order. You must be very proud.
Joey en "La Ley y el Orden". Debes estar muy orgullosa.
Chandler, she doesn't understand a word of English.
Chandler, ella no entiende ni una palabra de inglés.
Ha, ha, I thought you were Joey's other grandmother.
Ja, ja, pensé que eras la otra abuela de Joey.
I've done it again.
Lo he vuelto a hacer.
Nonnie's my biggest fan.
Nonnie es mi mayor fan.
She's the only one in the family who's always believed in me.
Es la única en la familia que siempre ha creído en mí.
Big star.
Gran estrella.
My big fat Joey star.
Mi gran estrella Joey.
Yeah. Yeah.
Sí. Sí.
Yeah, I weighed, like, 27 pounds when I was born.
Sí, pesé como 27 libras cuando nací.
Hey.
Oye.
- Happy anniversary. - Happy anniversary, 10 months.
- Feliz aniversario. - Feliz aniversario, 10 meses.
- Oh! Mm. - Mm.
- ¡Oh! Mm. - Mm.
Um, in the shower I was thinking about our first night in London.
Mmm, en la ducha estaba pensando en nuestra primera noche en Londres.
Oh, uh, Joey's grandmother's right there.
Oh, eh, la abuela de Joey está ahí.
- The one who speaks English? - The one who doesn't.
- ¿La que habla inglés? - La que no habla.
That was some hot love you gave me. Ha-ha-ha.
Eso fue un amor muy apasionado el que me diste. Ja-ja-ja.
- I'll get ready. - Wear those earrings I got you.
- Me prepararé. - Ponte esos aretes que te regalé.
Oh, that's a great idea. I was saving them for something special.
Oh, es una gran idea. Los estaba guardando para algo especial.
Mm.
- You've got to go home. - But I like it here.
- Tienes que irte a casa. - Pero me gusta estar aquí.
Go home and get the earrings you borrowed. He wants me to wear them.
Ve a casa y trae los aretes que tomaste prestados. Él quiere que me los ponga.
I think they're in my purse. Go get dressed and I'll look for them.
Creo que están en mi bolso. Ve a arreglarte y los buscaré.
Okay.
Ahem, Rach. Hi.
Ejem, Rach. Hola.
I need those earrings you borrowed.
Necesito esos aretes que tomaste prestados.
Oh. Um...
Oh. Mmm...
- Okay. - Okay.
- Vale. - Vale.
- Yeah, I'll be right back. - Okay.
- Sí, vuelvo enseguida. - De acuerdo.
Wow, Pheebs, you speak Italian?
Wow, Pheebs, ¿hablas italiano?
I guess so.
Supongo.
- Here you go. - Thanks. Wait, where's the other one?
- Aquí tienes. - Gracias. Espera, ¿dónde está el otro?
Oh, what, you want both of them? Ha, ha.
Oh, ¿qué, quieres los dos? Ja, ja.
Rachel Karen Green, where's the other earring?
Rachel Karen Green, ¿dónde está el otro arete?
Okay, okay. Look, just don't freak out, but I kind of lost it.
Está bien, está bien. Mira, solo no te alteres, pero como que lo perdí.
Oh, I know it's in the apartment, but I definitely lost it.
Oh, sé que está en el apartamento, pero definitivamente lo perdí.
What'll I tell Monica? She wants to wear them tonight.
¿Qué le diré a Monica? Quiere usarlos esta noche.
- Tell her to wear her own earrings. - These are her earrings.
- Dile que use sus propios aretes. - Son sus aretes.
No. No.
You lent me Monica's earrings? I'm not allowed to borrow her stuff.
¿Me prestaste los aretes de Monica? No tengo permitido tomar sus cosas.
- Why not? - Because I lose her stuff!
- ¿Por qué no? - ¡Porque pierdo sus cosas!
He, uh, left a little after 2.
Él, eh, se fue un poco después de las 2.
You see that blind guy right there? I'm gonna bash his head in later.
¿Ves a ese ciego de ahí? Le voy a dar un golpe en la cabeza más tarde.
Oh, uh, my big scene's coming up. Uh, the big scene coming up.
Oh, eh, mi gran escena se acerca. Eh, la gran escena se acerca.
If you said, "Big lima bean bubbling up," would she know the difference?
Si dijeras, "Gran frijol burbujeante", ¿ella sabría la diferencia?
Rach, what are you doing?
[ERROR API]
Oh, I just can't watch. It's too scary.
- Huh. - It's a diaper commercial.
[ERROR API]
Oh, yeah, well, you know me. Babies, responsibilities...
- Pizza delivery. - I'll get it! I will get that!
[ERROR API]
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
- One vegetarian pizza. It's 12.50. - Ah.
[ERROR API]
Uh, by the way, if it makes you feel any better, uh...
...I happen to like 8-year-old boys.
[ERROR API]
What?
¿Qué?
Oh, I mean... No, no, no. The, uh...
[ERROR API]
Your hair. Before. Your hair.
You said you thought your hair looked like an 8-year-old boy's...
[ERROR API]
...and I'm just saying I like it.
The hair.
[ERROR API]
Oh. Thanks.
You understand, I don't actually like 8-year-old boys.
[ERROR API]
All I'm looking for is the money.
Here you go. Now, stop bringing us pizzas, you.
[ERROR API]
- I'm gonna try. Ha, ha. - Okay.
You're welcome.
De nada.
You couldn't let me have her, could you?
[ERROR API]
- What? - This is a girl I really like...
...and you had to swoop in there! - What's going on?
[ERROR API]
Chandler was flirting with the hot delivery girl.
Thank you for that.
[ERROR API]
I was not flirting.
No estaba coqueteando.
It's okay. I don't care. Ha, ha. It's fine.
[ERROR API]
- Really? - Really?
It's no big deal. I do it all the time.
[ERROR API]
So, uh... Ahem. You flirt with guys all the time?
Sure. It doesn't mean anything. Just like I know it doesn't mean anything with you.
[ERROR API]
But there's a big difference. You're a lot hotter.
True story.
[ERROR API]
Ha, ha. This actually bothers you?
Yes, and I think it'd bother a lot of people.
[ERROR API]
When you were going out with Ross, did it bother you when he flirted with other women?
Uh, no. No, it bothered me when he slept with other women.
[ERROR API]
And thank you for that.
But I never had anything to worry about.
[ERROR API]
Ross was never very good at the flirting thing.
What...? What...? Ha, ha.
[ERROR API]
What are you talking about? It worked with you.
Oh. No, you're right.
[ERROR API]
We met, you flirted and then, bam, nine years later, you had me.
All right. All right.
[ERROR API]
You know what I'm gonna do? I am gonna order another pizza.
And when Caitlin gets here...
[ERROR API]
...I will show you how well I flirt.
- I will get her phone number. - Oh, well...
[ERROR API]
And not the one on the menu.
Y no el que está en el menú.
- I found it. - Oh, thank God! Where was it?
- Lo encontré. - ¡Ay, Dios mío! ¿Dónde estaba?
On your dresser.
En tu tocador.
- Okay, that is the one we already have. - Oh.
- Está bien, ese es el que ya tenemos. - Oh.
Okay, here's my big scene. My big scene's here.
Okay, aquí está mi gran escena. Mi gran escena está aquí.
- What do you bet nobody heard anything? - No bet.
- ¿A cuánto apuestas a que nadie oyó nada? - No apuesto.
Anybody home?
¿Hay alguien en casa?
- Oh, my God. - What?
- ¡Dios mío! - ¿Qué?
Okay, everybody just keep smiling. It'll kill my grandmother if she finds out. Ha, ha.
Okay, todos sigan sonriendo. Matará a mi abuela si se entera. Ja, ja.
- Oh, what is it? - Uh, they cut me out of the show.
- Oh, ¿qué es? - Uh, me sacaron del programa.
What?
¿Qué?
- Are you sure? - Maybe your scene's coming up.
- ¿Estás seguro? - Quizás tu escena viene ahora.
Not likely. Because you see that body bag right there?
Poco probable. Porque, ¿ves esa bolsa para cadáveres de ahí?
- Yeah. - I'm in it.
- Sí. - Estoy en ella.
This is terrible. What'll you do?
Esto es terrible. ¿Qué harás?
I don't know. But this little old lady lives for my career.
No lo sé. Pero esta viejita vive para mi carrera.
When they dumped me off Days of Our Lives, she almost died.
Cuando me sacaron de Days of Our Lives, casi se muere.
That's not good.
Eso no es bueno.
You're not smiling. Not that face! Smile, everybody smile! Ha, ha.
No sonríes. ¡Esa cara no! ¡Sonríe, todos sonrían! Ja, ja.
Why don't you just tell her what happened? It's not your fault.
¿Por qué no le dices lo que pasó? No es tu culpa.
If we keep talking this way, aren't we gonna freak her out soon?
Si seguimos hablando así, ¿no la vamos a asustar pronto?
Oh, uh, soon. I'm gonna be on soon.
Oh, uh, pronto. Estaré pronto.
There I am!
¡Ahí estoy!
No.
Sam Waterston!
¡Sam Waterston!
Oh, no, no. That's me. That's me!
Oh, no, no. Ese soy yo. ¡Ese soy yo!
No. Sam Waterston.
Crime Misdemeanor, Capricorn One.
She doesn't know "hello," but she knows Capricorn One.
Ella no sabe decir "hola", pero conoce Capricorn One.
- Phoebe. - Hmm?
- Phoebe. - ¿Mmm?
I need those earrings. We're leaving when the show's over.
Necesito esos aretes. Nos vamos cuando termine el programa.
But I already gave them back to you.
Pero si ya te los devolví.
No, you didn't.
No, no lo hiciste.
All right, I already didn't gave them back to you. That's what I said.
Está bien, ya no te los devolví. Eso es lo que dije.
Ahem. Where's that other earring?
Ejem. ¿Dónde está el otro arete?
It's not here, Pheebs. It's not here. Oh!
No está aquí, Pheebs. No está aquí. ¡Oh!
I went to Chandler's last night.
Fui a casa de Chandler anoche.
Make sure you check Chandler's jewelry box.
Asegúrate de revisar la caja de joyas de Chandler.
Wait a minute, Chandler has a jewelry box?
Espera un minuto, ¿Chandler tiene una caja de joyas?
Okay, we have 10 minutes. Do you want me to get into that now?
Okay, tenemos 10 minutos. ¿Quieres que hablemos de eso ahora?
Hey, Pheebs.
Oye, Pheebs.
How's that, uh...
¿Cómo va esa, eh...
...vegetarian pizza working out for you, huh?
...pizza vegetariana contigo, ¿eh?
You and those, uh, vegetables have a real, uh...
Tú y esas, eh, verduras tienen algo, eh...
...thing going on, huh?
...algo especial, ¿eh?
Why are you being weird?
¿Por qué actúas raro?
Do you like it?
¿Te gusta?
No. That would be, "Why are you being cute?"
No. Sería, "¿Por qué eres linda?"
Okay. I'm working on my flirting.
Okay. Estoy practicando mi coqueteo.
Oh! I did not get that.
¡Oh! No entendí eso.
So, uh, Monica, do you like Law and Order?
Entonces, eh, Mónica, ¿te gusta "La ley y el orden"?
- Yeah, it's good. - Oh.
- Sí, está bien. - Oh.
I found out all this stuff about you. You like Law and Order...
Descubrí un montón de cosas sobre ti. Te gusta "La ley y el orden"...
...and you've flirted with every guy in the tri-state area.
...y has coqueteado con todos los chicos del área metropolitana.
Shh. Shh.
Okay, let me get this straight.
Okay, déjame entender bien.
It's okay for you to flirt, but not for me?
¿Está bien que tú coquetees, pero yo no?
Oh, I'm so glad we cleared that up.
Oh, me alegra tanto que hayamos aclarado eso.
Look, I'm sorry, but some things are different for men and women.
Mira, lo siento, pero algunas cosas son diferentes para hombres y mujeres.
Go on, teach me about men and women.
Adelante, enséñame sobre hombres y mujeres.
Okay. I've already taught you so much already, but whatever.
Okay. Ya te he enseñado mucho, pero bueno.
When you flirt with a guy, you think, "No big deal."
Cuando coqueteas con un chico, piensas: "No es nada."
But the guy thinks, "Finally! Somebody who wants to sleep with me."
Pero el chico piensa: "¡Por fin! Alguien que quiere acostarse conmigo."
- No way! - It's true.
- ¡No puede ser! - Es verdad.
- Well, that's pathetic. - Again, true.
- Bueno, eso es patético. - De nuevo, verdad.
- This goes for all guys? - All guys that are awake.
- ¿Esto aplica a todos los chicos? - A todos los chicos que están despiertos.
Then we go to sleep.
Entonces nos vamos a dormir.
All guys from the other end of the world wake up and behave the exact same way.
Todos los chicos del otro lado del mundo se despiertan y se comportan exactamente igual.
All right. It's another commercial and I still haven't told her.
Bien. Es otra pausa comercial y todavía no se lo he dicho.
Joey, this is the last commercial.
Joey, esta es la última pausa comercial.
- You got, like, 10 minutes left. - I know!
- Te quedan como 10 minutos. - ¡Lo sé!
What am I gonna do? Oh!
¿Qué voy a hacer? ¡Oh!
You are not gonna run out and leave her here.
No vas a salir corriendo y dejarla aquí.
Yeah, all right. Oh!
Sí, está bien. ¡Oh!
Joey?
¿Joey?
Uh, Joey's gonna be right back. Right back?
Eh, Joey volverá enseguida. ¿Enseguida?
Meanwhile, let's talk about you.
Mientras tanto, hablemos de ti.
So, you're old and small.
Entonces, eres vieja y pequeña.
- Hey. - Did you find it?
- ¡Oye! - ¿La encontraste?
The earring, no. But I found my sunglasses.
El pendiente, no. Pero encontré mis gafas de sol.
I've been looking for these since last summer.
Las he estado buscando desde el verano pasado.
Those are my sunglasses. You borrowed them from me.
Esas son mis gafas de sol. Me las pediste prestadas.
Okay. Calm down. Here they are.
Okay. Calma. Aquí están.
Phoebe.
- What do we do? - I don't know. I don't know!
- ¿Qué hacemos? - No sé. ¡No sé!
We'll just have to tell Monica, that's all.
Tendremos que decírselo a Mónica, eso es todo.
Oh, God! She's gonna kill me.
¡Oh, Dios! Me va a matar.
- Oh. - I could tell her it was all my fault.
- Oh. - Podría decirle que todo fue culpa mía.
Oh, that'd be great.
Oh, eso sería genial.
Mon, could I talk to you?
Mon, ¿puedo hablar contigo?
- Yeah. What is it? - Um...
- Sí. ¿Qué pasa? - Um...
I lost one of your earrings.
Perdí uno de tus pendientes.
I'm sorry. I am so, so sorry.
Lo siento. Lo siento muchísimo.
Wow.
Guau.
All right, well, I mean, what can you do? If you lost it, you lost it.
Está bien, bueno, quiero decir, ¿qué puedes hacer? Si lo perdiste, lo perdiste.
I'll replace it, I promise. I feel so terrible.
Lo reemplazaré, lo prometo. Me siento muy mal.
That's fine. You didn't do it on purpose.
Está bien. No lo hiciste a propósito.
- No. - Oh.
Look at you. Come here.
Mírate. Ven aquí.
Aw.
Ay.
- You feel better? Ha, ha. - Yeah. You're the best.
- ¿Te sientes mejor? Ja, ja. - Sí. Eres la mejor.
Okay, wait a minute.
Okay, espera un minuto.
Wait a minute, I can't do this.
Espera un minuto, no puedo hacer esto.
Listen, honey, it's not Phoebe's fault.
Escucha, cariño, no es culpa de Phoebe.
She lent me the earrings.
Ella me prestó los aretes.
I lost it. I'm so sorry, honey. I feel terrible too.
Lo perdí. Lo siento mucho, cariño. Yo también me siento fatal.
That is exactly why I do not lend you stuff!
¡Por eso mismo no te presto cosas!
First it's my jewelry. If it's not that, it's my sweater.
Primero es mi joyería. Si no es eso, es mi suéter.
And if it's not my sweater, it's my sunglasses.
Y si no es mi suéter, son mis gafas de sol.
- Your sunglasses? - Yes.
- ¿Tus gafas de sol? - Sí.
Oh, right.
Oh, claro.
- Pizza. - Mine, mine, mine!
- Pizza. - ¡Mía, mía, mía!
Okay, here goes.
Ok, allá voy.
Prepare yourselves for some class-A flirting.
Prepárense para un flirteo de primera clase.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, espera.
Okay.
If you really like this girl, I don't think flirting is the right way...
Si realmente te gusta esta chica, no creo que coquetear sea la forma correcta...
Ah! Ah! Ah!
¡Ah! ¡Ah! ¡Ah!
You'll see.
Ya verás.
Okay.
Oh, what's her name?
Oh, ¿cómo se llama?
Caitlin!
¡Caitlin!
Caitlin.
Hey.
Oye.
Oh, we can't keep eating like this. Ha, ha.
Oh, no podemos seguir comiendo así. Ja, ja.
Heh. It's, uh, $12.50.
Je. Son, eh, $12.50.
Okay, um...
Está bien, eh...
So...
Así que...
Do you make the pizzas in one of those, uh, wood-burning ovens?
¿Haces las pizzas en uno de esos hornos de leña?
No, actually, I think they're gas.
No, en realidad, creo que son de gas.
Gas? Wow, ha, ha.
¿De gas? Vaya, ja, ja.
Intense.
Intenso.
If this is the way all the Gellers flirt, we don't have a problem.
Si así es como todos los Geller coquetean, no tenemos problema.
Hey, uh...
Oye, eh...
You know that smell gas has?
¿Sabes qué olor tiene el gas?
Yeah.
Sí.
They put that in.
Se lo ponen.
What?
¿Qué?
The gas is odorless.
El gas es inodoro.
But they add the smell so you know when there's a leak.
Pero le añaden el olor para que sepas cuándo hay una fuga.
Well, okay.
Bueno, está bien.
A lot of other gas smells.
Muchos otros olores a gas.
Oh, the humanity.
Oh, la humanidad.
Methane smells...
El metano huele...
You know what? Um, actually, I really should go.
¿Sabes qué? Um, en realidad, debería irme.
- Oh, but I haven't paid you yet. - That's okay.
- Oh, pero aún no te he pagado. - No te preocupes.
You guys have ordered so many that this one's on me.
Han pedido tantas que esta corre por mi cuenta.
Last I heard...
Hasta donde yo sé...
...the cops had over 600 reported missing women still.
...la policía todavía tenía más de 600 mujeres desaparecidas reportadas.
Six hundred.
Seiscientas.
Was I talking to her about gas?
¿Estaba hablando con ella de gas?
More so than anything else.
Más que nada.
I found it interesting.
Me pareció interesante.
I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
Hey, hey. Don't worry about it.
Oye, oye. No te preocupes por eso.
In nine years, she and I will be right there! Ha, ha.
¡En nueve años, ella y yo estaremos justo ahí! Ja, ja.
Okay. Well, I'm gonna clear out some of these boxes.
Okay. Bueno, voy a despejar algunas de estas cajas.
- Ross? - Yeah?
- ¿Ross? - ¿Sí?
What else do they add smell to?
¿A qué más le añaden olor?
Caitlin! Caitlin! Hi.
¡Caitlin! ¡Caitlin! Hola.
Hi, I'm Rachel. Oh.
Hola, soy Rachel. Oh.
From upstairs, people with all the pizza.
De arriba, la gente con toda la pizza.
Oh, was there a problem?
Oh, ¿hubo algún problema?
No, they're fine. Great pizza.
No, están bien. Gran pizza.
But, actually, um, my friend Ross...
Pero, en realidad, eh, mi amigo Ross...
...he just gets really nervous when he's flirting.
...se pone muy nervioso cuando está coqueteando.
Oh, my God! That was flirting?
¡Dios mío! ¿Eso era coquetear?
- Yeah. - Wow.
- Sí. - Vaya.
I know, I know.
Lo sé, lo sé.
I'm telling you, once you get past that part...
Te digo, una vez que superas esa parte...
...where it just feels like you wanna die...
...donde sientes que te quieres morir...
...he's a really good person.
...es una muy buena persona.
- The guy with the gas? - Yeah.
- ¿El chico del gas? - Sí.
I'm telling you, he's really sweet and really funny...
Te digo, es muy dulce y muy divertido...
...and he's just, oh, got a good heart.
...y es, oh, tiene un buen corazón.
- And besides, I think he really likes you. - Really?
- Y además, creo que le gustas mucho. - ¿En serio?
Well, we have seven people and 10 pizzas. What do you think?
Bueno, tenemos siete personas y 10 pizzas. ¿Qué opinas?
I thought Joey was there.
Pensé que Joey estaba allí.
You've got till Monday. Then I move to dismiss.
Tienes hasta el lunes. Luego desestimo.
Hey, Ross?
Oye, Ross.
Um, I just ran into Caitlin in the hallway.
Eh, acabo de encontrarme con Caitlin en el pasillo.
Uh, you must be getting better at this flirting stuff than I thought. Ha, ha.
Ajá, debes estar mejorando en esto de coquetear de lo que pensaba. Ja, ja.
- What? - I don't get it...
- ¿Qué? - No entiendo...
...but she wanted me to give you her phone number.
...pero ella quería que te diera su número de teléfono.
Oh.
And she just gave you this?
¿Y ella te dio esto?
Yeah.
Sí.
Rach, thanks. But I don't need you doing me any favors.
Rach, gracias. Pero no necesito que me hagas favores.
I didn't. I didn't. She thought you were cute.
No lo hice. No lo hice. Ella pensó que eras lindo.
Well, that I can believe.
Bueno, eso sí me lo creo.
Yeah.
Sí.
Hey, is the show still on?
Oye, ¿todavía está el programa?
Almost over, man.
Casi termina, amigo.
Hey, Nonnie.
Hola, Nonnie.
Oh! Is that the Pope?
¡Oh! ¿Es el Papa?
Hey.
Oye.
Why am I looking?
¿Por qué estoy mirando?
Oh, Nonnie, here I am! This is my big scene.
Oh, Nonnie, ¡aquí estoy! Esta es mi gran escena.
All right, back off!
¡Muy bien, quítense!
I got a gun!
¡Tengo un arma!
I'm not afraid to use it.
No tengo miedo de usarlo.
Oh, Joey.
Ay, Joey.
That's right, Nonnie.
Así es, Nonnie.
You couldn't have at least changed your shirt?
¿Ni siquiera pudiste cambiarte de camisa?
Now, I want a suitcase filled with $100,000...
Ahora, quiero una maleta llena de $100,000...
Shh! Shoo, shoo!
¡Shh! ¡Fuera, fuera!
Filled with $100,000 in small bills.
Llena de $100,000 en billetes pequeños.
And if I don't get... Shoo!
Y si no lo consigo... ¡Fuera!
And if I don't get it...
Y si no lo consigo...
...I'm gonna shoot this duck!
...¡voy a dispararle a este pato!
Oh, no!
¡Oh, no!
I'm coming out!
¡Salgo!
And she's supposed to buy this?
¿Y se supone que ella va a comprar esto?
Ground control to Major Tom
Control de tierra a Mayor Tom
Commencing countdown
Iniciando cuenta regresiva
Engines
Motores
On
Encendidos
That's, uh, scenes from next week's show. Next week.
Esas son, eh, escenas del programa de la próxima semana. La próxima semana.
I am definitely gonna watch that.
Definitivamente voy a ver eso.
What about these? Do these look the same?
¿Qué hay de estos? ¿Se ven iguales?
- Definitely. - Not as each other.
- Definitivamente. - No entre sí.
Oh, then, no.
Oh, entonces, no.
- Hey, you ready? - Hi. Yeah.
- Oye, ¿listo? - Hola. Sí.
- You look amazing. - Aw.
- Te ves increíble. - Aw.
I'm the luckiest man in the world.
Soy el hombre más afortunado del mundo.
- Oh, you're about to get a little luckier. - Mm-hm.
- Oh, estás a punto de tener un poco más de suerte. - Mm-hm.
- Let me see the earrings. - Oh, right, the earrings.
- Déjame ver los aretes. - Oh, claro, los aretes.
They look great.
Se ven geniales.
Does your boyfriend have the best taste or what?
¿Tu novio tiene el mejor gusto o qué?
My boyfriend really does have great taste.
Mi novio realmente tiene muy buen gusto.
- Thanks for picking out the earrings. - Mm-hm.
- Gracias por elegir los aretes. - Mm-hm.