Friends, family, we're gathered to celebrate here today...
Amigos, familia, estamos reunidos para celebrar hoy aquí...
...the joyous union of Ross and Emily.
...la feliz unión de Ross y Emily.
Now Ross, repeat after me.
Ahora Ross, repite después de mí.
I, Ross.
Yo, Ross.
Take thee, Emily.
Te tomo, Emily.
Take thee, Rachel.
Te tomo, Rachel.
Emily.
Heh. Emily.
Je. Emily.
Uh, shall I go on?
Eh, ¿sigo?
He said "Rachel," right?
Dijo "Rachel", ¿verdad?
Do you think I should go up there?
¿Crees que debería subir ahí?
Yes. Yes. Do go on.
Sí. Sí. Por favor, sigue.
I think we'd better start again.
Creo que será mejor que empecemos de nuevo.
Ross, repeat after me.
Ross, repite después de mí.
I, Ross.
Yo, Ross.
Take thee, Emily.
Te tomo, Emily.
Ha, ha. Like there'd be anybody else.
Ja, ja. Como si hubiera alguien más.
As my lawfully wedded wife, in sickness and in health...
Como mi esposa legítimamente casada, en la salud y en la enfermedad...
...till death parts us.
...hasta que la muerte nos separe.
As my lawfully wedded wife, in sickness and in health...
Como mi esposa legítimamente casada, en la salud y en la enfermedad...
...until death parts us.
...hasta que la muerte nos separe.
Really, I do. Emily.
De verdad que sí. Emily.
Do you have the rings?
¿Tienen los anillos?
Emily, place this ring on Ross' finger...
Emily, ponle este anillo al dedo de Ross...
...as a symbol of your bond everlasting.
...como símbolo de su vínculo eterno.
Ross, place this ring...
Ross, pon este anillo...
...on Emily's hand as a symbol...
...en la mano de Emily como símbolo...
...of the love that encircles you forever.
...del amor que los une para siempre.
Happy to.
Encantado.
They have made their declarations...
Han hecho sus declaraciones...
...and it gives me great pleasure to declare them husband and wife.
...y me da mucho placer declararlos marido y mujer.
You may kiss the bride.
Pueden besar a la novia.
This is worse than when he married the lesbian.
Esto es peor que cuando se casó con la lesbiana.
Just keep smiling.
Solo sigue sonriendo.
Okay...
Está bien...
Well, that went well. Yeah.
Bueno, eso salió bien. Sí.
It could've been worse. He could've shot her.
Pudo haber sido peor. Podría haberle disparado.
Ha, ha. That was pretty funny, wasn't it?
Ja, ja. Eso fue bastante gracioso, ¿no?
You spoiled everything. It's like a nightmare.
Arruinaste todo. Es como una pesadilla.
All my friends and family are out there. How can I face them?
Todos mis amigos y familia están ahí fuera. ¿Cómo puedo mirarlos?
How could you do this to me?
¿Cómo pudiste hacerme esto?
Hey, no matter what happens with Ross and Emily...
Oye, sin importar lo que pase con Ross y Emily...
...we still get cake, right?
...todavía tendremos pastel, ¿verdad?
That's all right. No, no. You take your time, sweetie.
Está bien. No, no. Tómate tu tiempo, cariño.
I'll be out here. Ha, ha.
Estaré aquí fuera. Ja, ja.
She's just fixing her makeup.
Solo se está arreglando el maquillaje.
I hate you.
Te odio.
And I love you.
Y yo te amo.
Boy, a bad time to say the wrong name, huh, Ross?
Vaya, qué mal momento para decir el nombre equivocado, ¿eh, Ross?
That's true. Thanks, Dad.
Es verdad. Gracias, papá.
People should be dancing, huh?
La gente debería estar bailando, ¿eh?
Hey, this is a party. Come on.
Oye, esto es una fiesta. Vamos.
Joey. Dance.
Joey. Baila.
Yes, Waltham Interiors.
Sí, Waltham Interiors.
Hello, this is Ross Geller's personal physician, Dr. Phalange.
Hola, soy el médico personal de Ross Geller, el Dr. Phalange.
Who?
¿Quién?
Yeah, I discovered that Ross forgot to take his brain medicine.
Sí, descubrí que Ross olvidó tomar su medicina para el cerebro.
Um, now, without it, uh, in the brain of Ross...
Mmm, ahora, sin ella, eh, en el cerebro de Ross...
...uh, women's names are interchangeable.
...eh, los nombres de las mujeres son intercambiables.
Through no fault of his own.
Sin que sea culpa suya.
Oh, my God. Phoebe.
Ay, Dios mío. Phoebe.
No, not Phoebe. Dr. Phalange.
No, no Phoebe. Dr. Phalange.
Oh, no. You have it too.
Oh, no. Tú también lo tienes.
Hello?
¿Hola?
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Wow, I hope you don't take this the wrong way...
Vaya, espero que no te lo tomes a mal...
...but I know we had plans to meet up tonight and...
...pero sé que teníamos planes de vernos esta noche y...
Ugh. I'm just kind of worried about what it might do to our friendship.
Uf. Estoy un poco preocupada por lo que pueda hacerle a nuestra amistad.
I know.
Lo sé.
- Ugh. How could we have let this happen? - Seven times.
- Uf. ¿Cómo pudimos dejar que esto pasara? - Siete veces.
You know, look. We were away.
Sabes, mira. Estábamos fuera.
- In a foreign, romantic country. - Right.
- En un país extranjero y romántico. - Cierto.
I blame London.
Culpo a Londres.
Bad London.
Malo Londres.
So look, um...
Así que mira, mmm...
...while we're still in London, I mean, we can keep doing it, right?
...mientras sigamos en Londres, quiero decir, podemos seguir haciéndolo, ¿verdad?
Well, I don't see that we have a choice.
Bueno, no veo que tengamos otra opción.
But when we're back home, we don't do it.
Pero cuando volvamos a casa, no lo hacemos.
Only here.
Solo aquí.
You know, I saw a wine cellar downstairs.
Sabes, vi una bodega de vinos abajo.
- I'll meet you there in two minutes. - Okay.
- Te veo allí en dos minutos. - Vale.
- Mon? Mon, I got to ask you something. - Now?
- ¿Mon? Mon, tengo que preguntarte algo. - ¿Ahora?
Ross said my name up there. I mean, come on.
Ross dijo mi nombre ahí arriba. Quiero decir, vamos.
I can't just pretend that didn't happen.
No puedo simplemente fingir que eso no pasó.
I don't know.
No sé.
- Monica, what should I do? - Just do the right thing.
- Monica, ¿qué debo hacer? - Haz lo correcto.
What?
¿Qué?
Tow the line. Thread the needle. Think outside the box.
Sigue la corriente. Pasa la aguja. Piensa fuera de la caja.
Monica, wait, listen. I'm gonna talk to Ross about what he thinks it meant.
Monica, espera, escucha. Voy a hablar con Ross sobre lo que él cree que significó.
Wait. Rachel, no.
Espera. Rachel, no.
He's married.
Él está casado.
Married.
Casado.
If you don't realize that, I can't help you.
Si no te das cuenta de eso, no puedo ayudarte.
Okay. You're right.
Está bien. Tienes razón.
You're right. You can't help me.
Tienes razón. No puedes ayudarme.
Jack, is it all our fault? Were we bad parents?
Jack, ¿es todo culpa nuestra? ¿Fuimos malos padres?
Yes.
Sí.
Oh yeah? Well, who serves steak when there's no place to sit?
¿Ah, sí? Bueno, ¿quién sirve filete cuando no hay dónde sentarse?
I mean, how are you supposed to eat this?
Quiero decir, ¿cómo se supone que vas a comer esto?
Hey, what's up?
Hola, ¿qué tal?
Where were you? We were supposed to meet.
¿Dónde estabas? Se suponía que nos íbamos a encontrar.
- Forget it. That's off. - Why?
- Olvídalo. Ya no. - ¿Por qué?
The next tour of the wine cellar...
El próximo tour de la bodega...
...will commence in two minutes.
...comenzará en dos minutos.
Joey, what are you doing?
Joey, ¿qué estás haciendo?
You promised Phoebe no meat till she has the babies.
Le prometiste a Phoebe nada de carne hasta que tenga a los bebés.
Well, I figured we're in another country, so it doesn't count.
Bueno, pensé que como estamos en otro país, no cuenta.
- That's true. - The man's got a point.
- Es verdad. - El hombre tiene un punto.
Oh, hi.
Oh, hola.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
I'm sorry things aren't working out so well.
Lamento que las cosas no estén saliendo tan bien.
Oh, no. Ha, ha. It could be better. It's gonna be okay, right?
Oh, no. Ja, ja. Podría ser mejor. Va a estar bien, ¿verdad?
Oh, yeah. Of course. I mean, she's gonna get over this, you know?
Oh, sí. Claro. O sea, ella va a superar esto, ¿sabes?
I mean, so you said my name.
O sea, dijiste mi nombre.
You know, you just said it because you saw me there.
Sabes, solo lo dijiste porque me viste allí.
If you'd seen a circus freak, you would've said:
Si hubieras visto a un fenómeno de circo, habrías dicho:
I take thee Circus Freak.
Te tomo, Fenómeno de Circo.
It didn't mean anything. It's just a mistake.
No significó nada. Fue solo un error.
It didn't mean anything.
No significó nada.
- Right? - No, no.
- ¿Verdad? - No, no.
Of course it didn't mean anything.
Claro que no significó nada.
I mean, I can understand why Emily would think it meant something...
O sea, puedo entender por qué Emily pensaría que significó algo...
...you know, because it was you.
...sabes, porque eras tú.
But it absolutely didn't. It didn't! It didn't!
¡Pero absolutamente no lo hizo! ¡No lo hizo! ¡No lo hizo!
Ross, hey, the band's ready outside for your first dance with Emily.
Ross, hola, la banda está lista afuera para tu primer baile con Emily.
Oh. Oh, the band's ready.
Oh. Oh, la banda está lista.
Well, we got to do what the band says.
Bueno, tenemos que hacer lo que dice la banda.
I don't care about the stupid band!
¡No me importa la estúpida banda!
You spit on me, man.
Me escupiste, amigo.
I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
- Emily is taking kind of a long time, huh? - Heh.
- Emily se está tardando un poco, ¿eh? - Heh.
When I locked myself in the bathroom at my wedding...
Cuando me encerré en el baño en mi boda...
...it was because I was trying to pop the window out of the frame.
...fue porque estaba intentando sacar la ventana del marco.
- Right. - Get the hell out of there. You know?
- ¿Cierto? - Sal de ahí. ¿Sabes?
Emily.
I'm coming in.
Ya voy.
Oh, look at that. Same thing.
Oh, mira eso. Lo mismo.
In the middle of everything...
En medio de todo...
...if I scream the word "yippee," just ignore me.
...si grito la palabra "yippee", ignórame.
- Huh! Oh, my God. Rachel. - Oh, hello, Rachel.
- ¡Huh! Oh, Dios mío. Rachel. - Oh, hola, Rachel.
Ross said my name.
Ross dijo mi nombre.
Okay? My name.
¿Okay? Mi nombre.
Ross said my name up there.
Ross dijo mi nombre allá arriba.
That obviously means that he still loves me.
Eso obviamente significa que todavía me ama.
Okay, don't believe me. I know I'm right.
Okay, no me creas. Sé que tengo razón.
All right. Do you guys want to go and get a drink?
Muy bien. ¿Quieren ir a tomar algo?
Yes, we do.
Sí, tenemos que hacerlo.
But we have to change first.
Pero tenemos que cambiarnos primero.
Yes, I want to change.
Sí, quiero cambiarme.
- Why don't you go get a table? - We'll be down in five minutes.
- ¿Por qué no vas a buscar una mesa? - Bajamos en cinco minutos.
- Fifteen minutes. - Ha, ha.
- Quince minutos. - Ja, ja.
Hello.
Hola.
Oh, Pheebs. It's Phoebe.
Oh, Pheebs. Es Phoebe.
- Oh, hey, hey. - Oh, great.
- Oh, hola, hola. - Oh, genial.
Hi.
Hola.
So, what happened?
Entonces, ¿qué pasó?
Well, Ross said my name.
Bueno, Ross dijo mi nombre.
Yeah, I know, but I don't think that means anything.
Sí, lo sé, pero no creo que eso signifique nada.
Okay, Pheebs, let's look at this objectively.
Está bien, Pheebs, veamos esto objetivamente.
All right, ninth grade, right?
Bien, noveno grado, ¿verdad?
The obsession starts.
Empieza la obsesión.
All right? Summer after ninth grade...
¿De acuerdo? El verano después de noveno grado...
...he sees me in a two-piece for the first time.
...me ve en bikini por primera vez.
His obsession begins to grow, right?
Su obsesión empieza a crecer, ¿verdad?
Hey, listen, why don't we go change in my room?
Oye, escucha, ¿por qué no vamos a cambiarnos a mi habitación?
My clothes are... Oh.
Mi ropa está... Oh.
- Wow, you look... - No time for that.
- Vaya, te ves... - No hay tiempo para eso.
Okay.
Hey, dude. Let me in. I got a girl out here.
Oye, amigo. Déjame entrar. Tengo una chica afuera.
Well, I've got a girl in here.
Bueno, yo tengo una chica aquí adentro.
No, you don't. I just saw you go in there with Monica.
No, no la tienes. Acabo de verte entrar ahí con Monica.
Well, we're hanging out in here.
Bueno, estamos aquí pasando el rato.
Which one of us is gonna be having sex in there? Me or you?
¿Cuál de los dos va a tener sexo ahí dentro? ¿Yo o tú?
Well, I suppose I would have to say you.
Bueno, supongo que tendría que decir que tú.
- What if we're watching a movie in here? - Which we are.
- ¿Y si estamos viendo una película aquí? - Que es lo que estamos haciendo.
And we've already paid for it. It's My Giant.
Y ya pagamos por ella. Es 'Mi Gigante'.
My Giant? I love that movie.
'Mi Gigante'? Me encanta esa película.
You really think this is okay?
¿De verdad crees que esto está bien?
Well, Ross and Emily aren't gonna use it.
Bueno, Ross y Emily no la van a usar.
Oh, it's so beautiful.
Oh, es tan hermoso.
Oh.
You know, I don't feel right about this.
Sabes, no me siento bien con esto.
Oh, Monica...
This is the honeymoon suite.
Esta es la suite nupcial.
The room expects sex.
La habitación espera sexo.
The room would be disappointed if it didn't get sex.
La habitación se decepcionaría si no tuviera sexo.
All the other honeymoon suites would think it was a loser.
Todas las otras suites nupciales pensarían que es un fracaso.
Okay.
- Emily? - Nope. Not under here.
- ¿Emily? - No. No está aquí abajo.
- You didn't find her? - No, I've looked everywhere.
- ¿No la encontraste? - No, la busqué por todas partes.
Well, you couldn't have, or else you would've found her.
Bueno, no pudiste, o la habrías encontrado.
- I think you should keep looking. - Yeah. For about, uh, 30 minutes?
- Creo que deberías seguir buscando. - Sí. ¿Por como, eh, 30 minutos?
Or 45?
¿O 45?
Wow, in 45 minutes, you could find her twice.
Vaya, en 45 minutos, podrías encontrarla dos veces.
No. For all I know, she's trying to find me...
No. Por lo que sé, ella está intentando encontrarme...
...but couldn't because I kept moving around.
...pero no pudo porque yo no paraba de moverme.
No, from now on, I'm staying in one place.
No, de ahora en adelante, me quedaré en un solo lugar.
Right here.
Justo aquí.
- It's getting late. - Yeah, We're going to go.
- Se está haciendo tarde. - Sí, nos vamos.
Actually...
En realidad...
...do you guys mind staying here for a while?
...¿les importa quedarse aquí un rato?
Ugh. You know, we got to get up early and catch that plane to New York.
Uf. Sabes, tenemos que levantarnos temprano y tomar ese avión a Nueva York.
Yeah, it's a very large plane.
Sí, es un avión muy grande.
That's cool.
Qué bueno.
But we'll stay here with you.
Pero nos quedaremos aquí contigo.
Thanks, guys. Ha, ha.
Gracias, chicos. Ja, ja.
I really appreciate this, you know, but you don't need to rub my butt.
Realmente aprecio esto, sabes, pero no necesitas frotarme el trasero.
We have to leave for New York in an hour.
Tenemos que irnos a Nueva York en una hora.
I know. I've been looking at those doors.
Lo sé. He estado mirando esas puertas.
They look pretty soundproof, don't you think?
Parecen bastante insonorizadas, ¿no crees?
We can't do that. That's insane.
No podemos hacer eso. Es una locura.
I mean, A, he could wake up. And B, you know...
Quiero decir, A, podría despertarse. Y B, sabes...
...let's go for it.
...vamos a hacerlo.
Emily? Emily.
¿Emily? ¿Emily.
- Emily! - Nope.
- ¡Emily! - No.
- Forget about Emily. She's not with us. - We've come for her things.
- Olvídate de Emily. Ella no está con nosotros. - Hemos venido por sus cosas.
Where is she?
¿Dónde está?
She's in hiding. She's utterly humiliated. She doesn't want to see you ever again.
Está escondida. Está completamente humillada. No quiere volver a verte nunca más.
We're very sad that it didn't work out between you and Emily, monkey.
Lamentamos mucho que no funcionara entre tú y Emily, mono.
But I think you're absolutely delicious.
Pero creo que eres absolutamente delicioso.
Excuse me, I'm standing right here.
Disculpa, estoy aquí mismo.
Oh, yes.
Oh, sí.
There you are.
Ahí estás.
Hey. Hey, you guys. Hurry up. Get some. There's a whole cart outside.
Oigan. Oigan, chicos. Apúrense. Tomen algo. Hay un carrito afuera.
- Goodbye, Geller. - Now, hold on. Hold on.
- Adiós, Geller. - Ahora, esperen. Esperen.
Look, look. Your daughter and I...
Miren, miren. Su hija y yo...
...are supposed to leave tonight for our honeymoon.
...se supone que nos vamos esta noche de luna de miel.
Now, you tell her that I'm gonna be at that airport...
Ahora, dile que estaré en ese aeropuerto...
...and I hope that she'll be there too.
...y espero que ella también esté allí.
Yeah, I said Rachel's name, but it didn't mean anything.
Sí, dije el nombre de Rachel, pero no significó nada.
She's just a friend. That's all. Now, look, just tell Emily I love her...
Es solo una amiga. Eso es todo. Ahora, mira, solo dile a Emily que la amo...
...and that I can't imagine spending my life with anyone else.
...y que no puedo imaginar pasar mi vida con nadie más.
Please, promise me that you'll tell her that.
Por favor, prométeme que se lo dirás.
All right, I'll tell her.
Está bien, se lo diré.
Come on, bugger face.
Vamos, cara de bicho.
Call me.
Llámame.
You spend half your life in the bathroom.
Pasas la mitad de tu vida en el baño.
Why do you never go out the bloody window?
¿Por qué nunca sales por la maldita ventana?
Well, maybe it's best we never got to do it again.
Bueno, tal vez sea mejor que no volvamos a hacerlo.
Yeah, it kind of makes that one night special.
Sí, de alguna manera hace que esa noche sea especial.
You know, technically, we still are over international waters.
Sabes, técnicamente, todavía estamos en aguas internacionales.
I'm going to the bathroom. Maybe I'll see you there in a bit?
Voy al baño. ¿Quizás te vea allí en un rato?
Okay.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Oye, ¿puedo preguntarte algo?
Uh, no.
Eh, no.
Felicity and I, we were watching My Giant. And I was thinking...
Felicity y yo estábamos viendo My Giant. Y estaba pensando...
...I'm never gonna be as good an actor as that giant.
...nunca seré tan buen actor como ese gigante.
Do you think I'm just wasting my life with this acting thing?
¿Crees que estoy perdiendo mi vida con esto de la actuación?
No.
I mean, the giant's like five years younger than me.
[ERROR API]
You know, you think I'll ever get there?
Yes.
Sí.
- Thanks, man. - Okay, man.
[ERROR API]
But what about how much taller he is than me?
I mean, there's no way I can make myself taller now.
[ERROR API]
And who knows what science will come up with in the future...
...but, Chandler, what if I die an unsuccessful, regular-size man?
[ERROR API]
Hey, Monica. Wow, you've been in the bathroom for, like, a half-hour.
I know.
Lo sé.
Had the beef tips, huh?
[ERROR API]
Hey.
Oye.
You ate meat!
[ERROR API]
You had sex!
- No, we didn't. - I know you didn't.
[ERROR API]
I was talking about Monica.
Phoebe, I did not have sex.
[ERROR API]
Oh, this pregnancy is throwing me all off.
- I'm gonna say hi to the chick and duck. - Oh, me too.
[ERROR API]
Why would you need to say hi? You've been feeding them for four days.
Oh, right. Maybe I'll just go home.
[ERROR API]
Well, we certainly are alone.
Good thing we have that "not New York" rule.
[ERROR API]
Right.
Cierto.
Um, listen, since we're on that subject...
[ERROR API]
...um, I just wanted to tell you that, um...
Well, I was going through a really hard time in London...
[ERROR API]
...what with my brother getting married and that guy thinking I was Ross' mother.
Right.
Cierto.
Well, anyway, I just...
[ERROR API]
That night meant a lot to me. And I guess I'm trying to say thanks.
Oh.
You know, that night meant a lot to me too.
[ERROR API]
And it wasn't because I was in a bad place or anything.
It just meant a lot to me because you're really hot.
[ERROR API]
- Is that okay? - Ha, ha. That's okay.
And I'm cute too?
[ERROR API]
- And you're cute too. - Thank you.
- All right, I got to go unpack. - Okay.
[ERROR API]
Bye.
Adiós.
I'm still on London time. Does that count?
[ERROR API]
- Oh, that counts. - Oh, good.
Rach.
- Rach. - Hi.
[ERROR API]
What are you doing here?
¿Qué haces aquí?
Well, I've been on standby for a flight home for hours.
[ERROR API]
- Oh. - Oh. So no sign of Emily, huh?
Not yet.
[ERROR API]
So, um...
Entonces, eh...
What time are you supposed to leave?
[ERROR API]
This is the last call for Flight 1066 to Athens.
Este es el último llamado para el Vuelo 1066 a Atenas.
The last call.
El último llamado.
Pretty soon, I guess.
Supongo que pronto.
I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
I just... I don't understand. I mean, how could she do this?
Yo... no entiendo. O sea, ¿cómo pudo hacerme esto?
What, am I like a complete idiot...
¿Qué, soy un completo idiota...
...for thinking she'd actually show up?
...por pensar que realmente aparecería?
No.
You're not an idiot, Ross.
No eres un idiota, Ross.
You're a guy very much in love.
Eres un hombre muy enamorado.
Same difference.
Es lo mismo.
All passengers for Flight 1066 to Athens should now be on board.
Todos los pasajeros del Vuelo 1066 a Atenas deben estar a bordo ahora.
I get it!
¡Entiendo!
Well, that's that.
Bueno, eso es todo.
No, you know what?
No, ¿sabes qué?
I think you should go.
Creo que deberías irte.
- What? - Yeah, I do think you should go...
- ¿Qué? - Sí, creo que deberías ir...
...by yourself. Get some distance.
...sola. Toma distancia.
Clear your head. I think it would be really good.
Despeja tu mente. Creo que sería muy bueno.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, no sé.
Oh, come on, Ross. I think it would be really good for you.
Ay, vamos, Ross. Creo que sería muy bueno para ti.
I could. I could do that.
Podría. Podría hacer eso.
Yeah.
Sí.
I can't even believe her.
Ni siquiera puedo creerle.
You know what? I am going to go.
¿Sabes qué? Voy a ir.
- Good. - Why not?
- Bien. - ¿Por qué no?
- Right? - Right. Right.
- ¿Verdad? - Sí. Sí. Sí.
- Thanks. - Okay, I'll see you back at home.
- Gracias. - Okay, te veo en casa.
If I ever get a flight out of here.
Si es que logro salir de aquí.
Hey, well...
Oye, bueno...
- No. - What? Wait, what?
- No. - ¿Qué? Espera, ¿qué?
Why don't you come?
¿Por qué no vienes?
I mean, I have two tickets. Why not?
Tengo dos boletos. ¿Por qué no?
Well, I don't know, Ross. Really?
Bueno, no sé, Ross. ¿En serio?
Yeah, yeah. It'd be great. I mean, you can...
Sí, sí. Sería genial. O sea, puedes...
You can lay on the beach...
Puedes tirarte en la playa...
...and I can cry over my failed marriage.
...y yo puedo llorar por mi matrimonio fallido.
- You see how I make jokes? - Uh-huh.
- ¿Ves cómo hago chistes? - Ajá.
Really. I mean...
En serio. O sea...
God, I could use a friend.
Dios, podría usar un amigo.
Oh, wow. Okay, maybe.
Oh, wow. Okay, tal vez.
Um...
Yes, I can do that.
Sí, puedo hacer eso.
- Cool. - All right, cool.
- Genial. - De acuerdo, genial.
Okay, we're going to Greece. Yeah, okay.
Okay, nos vamos a Grecia. Sí, okay.
Aah, aah. I forgot my jacket.
Aah, aah. Olvidé mi chaqueta.
- Well, you tell them to wait. - Okay.
- Bueno, diles que esperen. - Okay.
- Wait. Wait. - Okay.
- Espera. Espera. - Okay.
Emily.
Oh, no, no, no.
No! No!
¡No! ¡No!
Emily!
¡Emily!
Ah, yes. I will have a glass of the Merlot...
Ah, sí. Me daré una copa del Merlot...
...and he will have a white-wine spritzer.
...y él se tomará un spritzer de vino blanco.
Whoo!
¡Whoo!
Huh.
Vaya.
Hey, look at that. The airport's moving.
Oye, mira eso. El aeropuerto se está moviendo.
Hey, are we moving?
Oye, ¿nos estamos moviendo?
Are we moving? Why are we moving?
¿Nos movemos? ¿Por qué nos movemos?
They... Um...
Ellos... Mmm...
Yeah, does the captain know that we're moving?
Sí, ¿sabe el capitán que nos estamos moviendo?
Oh, my gosh.
Ay, Dios mío.