- Pick a card. - Okay.
[ERROR API]
All right. Now memorize it.
- You got it? - Oh, yes.
[ERROR API]
Okay. Is that your card?
- Yes. - Ha, ha.
[ERROR API]
- Hey, guys. - Hi there.
Guess what. Ben is gonna be in a TV commercial.
[ERROR API]
- What are you talking about? - Well, it's not for sure.
But, uh, we met this guy in the park who thought Ben was really cute.
[ERROR API]
You know, which he is. Um, anyhoo, he gave us his card...
...and told us to bring him down for this commercial he's auditioning.
[ERROR API]
Whoa.
The guy's like the biggest commercial casting director in town.
[ERROR API]
Ben takes one lousy walk in the park and gets an audition?
I mean, way to go, Ben!
[ERROR API]
Man, I've been in that park a million times. No one's ever offered me an audition.
I know, it's crazy. We were just pushing Ben on the swings...
[ERROR API]
I'm always on the swings.
What am I doing wrong?
[ERROR API]
That.
- Okay, gotta go. Wish me luck. - Good luck.
[ERROR API]
Hey, Rach, now that you working at Ralph Lauren, can you get me some shirts?
Uh, well, you know what? I don't know if I'd feel comfortable stealing...
[ERROR API]
...on my very first day.
Unwilling to steal from work.
[ERROR API]
Interesting.
Interesante.
Besides, if anybody is gonna get free stuff, it's me.
[ERROR API]
Okay, guys, way to wish me luck.
- Go get them. - Bye.
[ERROR API]
Okay, let's discuss Rachel's birthday.
I say we throw a surprise party this weekend.
[ERROR API]
Whoa, whoa. But her birthday's not for another month.
Okay, but if we throw her a party on her birthday, then it's not a surprise.
[ERROR API]
I think that's a great idea. We can have a dinner party and invite her close friends.
Ross. We're having a surprise party for Rachel.
[ERROR API]
- Okay. - Done.
Okay, great. So do you wanna do it together?
[ERROR API]
I would love to do it together.
They're gonna do it together.
[ERROR API]
Dude, that's my girlfriend.
So I gotta shut it down now?
[ERROR API]
All right, I gotta take off. I'm picking up Ben...
...and then we're off to the big audition.
[ERROR API]
It's gonna be weird seeing some actor pretending to be Ben's dad.
- Yeah. - Weirder than his two moms making out?
[ERROR API]
Whoa, whoa. Dad? There's a dad in the commercial?
Yeah. The dad and Ben eat soup and pretend to enjoy it.
[ERROR API]
Well, maybe I'll go with you and see if I can audition as the dad.
I mean, who better to play Ben's father than his godfather?
[ERROR API]
- You're not his godfather. - What?
Are you kidding?
¿Estás bromeando?
Of course I am.
Claro que sí.
- Okay, let's go, godfather. - All right. Ha, ha.
- Dale, vamos, padrino. - De acuerdo. Ja, ja.
Hey, I'm in. They're gonna let me audition.
Oye, me apunto. Me van a dejar audicionar.
Really? That's great.
¿En serio? Qué bien.
I know, I know. One of the casting ladies has actually seen me in a play.
Ya sé, ya sé. Una de las chicas de casting me ha visto en una obra.
So I steered clear of her.
Así que la evité.
- That kid looks familiar. - Oh, yeah.
- Ese niño me suena. - Ah, sí.
Yeah, he's done tons of commercials.
Sí, ha hecho un montón de anuncios.
I've seen him in Sugar Smacks, PlayStation...
Lo he visto en Sugar Smacks, PlayStation...
...and that one for the phone company.
...y en ese de la compañía telefónica.
In fact, he was so good in that one...
De hecho, lo hizo tan bien en ese...
...he actually convinced me to switch phone companies.
...que me convenció para cambiar de compañía telefónica.
Chandler was mad.
Chandler se enfadó.
Yeah, well, he's not gonna get this one. All right? Ben is way cuter than that kid.
Sí, bueno, no va a conseguir este. ¿Vale? Ben es mucho más mono que ese niño.
I mean, look at him.
O sea, míralo.
That's great.
Eso es genial.
Listen, wouldn't it be great if I got to play Ben's dad?
Oye, ¿no sería genial si yo pudiera hacer de papá de Ben?
Joey, you look nothing like Ben.
Joey, no te pareces en nada a Ben.
I look more like him than you do.
Me parezco más a él que tú.
Well, I really don't know you well enough for you to do that.
Bueno, la verdad es que no te conozco lo suficiente como para que hagas eso.
So it's down to these two. Nancy, I know you like this one...
Así que se reduce a estos dos. Nancy, sé que te gusta este...
...and I think I agree. Rachel, what do you think?
...y creo que estoy de acuerdo. Rachel, ¿tú qué opinas?
Well, um, that one is pretty...
Bueno, mmm, ese es bastante...
...but I just love this fabric. Sorry.
...pero me encanta esta tela. Lo siento.
Oh, don't be. That's part of your job here, to give your opinions.
Oh, no te preocupes. Es parte de tu trabajo aquí, dar tu opinión.
And then I take credit for them. I'm kidding. Ha, ha.
Y luego yo me llevo el mérito. Es broma. Ja, ja.
She is kidding. But don't ever disagree with her again.
Es broma. Pero no vuelvas a discrepar con ella.
- Okay, now I'm kidding. - Oh, ha, ha.
- Vale, ahora es broma. - Oh, ja, ja.
Oh, what a fun office.
Oh, qué oficina tan divertida.
I don't know which one. But I do know I need a cigarette.
No sé cuál. Pero sí sé que necesito un cigarrillo.
So, what do you say we take a break, go outside...
Entonces, ¿qué dices si hacemos una pausa, salimos afuera...
...and figure this out when we come back.
...y lo resolvemos cuando volvamos?
- Rachel? - Yeah.
- ¿Rachel? - Sí.
- You smoke? - No.
- ¿Fumas? - No.
My dad's a doctor. And he would always tell me just horror stories...
Mi papá es doctor. Y siempre me contaba historias de terror...
About ghosts and goblins...
...sobre fantasmas y duendes...
...who totally supported the princess' right to smoke.
...que apoyaban totalmente el derecho de la princesa a fumar.
And then they came back from smoking...
Y luego volvían de fumar...
...and they'd made all of the decisions without me.
...y habían tomado todas las decisiones sin mí.
- That doesn't seem fair. - I know.
- Eso no parece justo. - Ya lo sé.
It's like I'm being punished for not having this disgusting, poisonous habit.
Es como si me estuvieran castigando por no tener este hábito asqueroso y venenoso.
Yeah, it is the best.
Sí, es lo mejor.
I mean, what if this keeps happening?
O sea, ¿y si esto sigue pasando?
They'll be outside smoking, making all the decisions...
Estarán afuera fumando, tomando todas las decisiones...
...and I'll just be up in my office breathing in my stupid clean air.
...y yo estaré aquí en mi oficina respirando mi estúpido aire puro.
You know? And when Kim wants to promote one of us...
¿Sabes? Y cuando Kim quiera promocionar a alguien...
...who do you think she's gonna pick? Me or Smokey Smokerson?
...¿a quién crees que va a elegir? ¿A mí o a Fumador Fumador?
Rachel, you can go down there, you don't have to smoke.
Rachel, puedes bajar, no tienes que fumar.
Just say you wanna get some fresh air.
Solo di que quieres tomar un poco de aire fresco.
Yeah, I could do that.
Sí, podría hacer eso.
Yeah, or you could just do the easy thing and smoke.
Sí, o podrías hacer lo fácil y fumar.
- Hey. Do you wanna go get coffee? - Hey.
- Hola. ¿Quieres ir por un café? - Hola.
- Oh, I would love to. - Oh, good.
- Oh, me encantaría. - Oh, qué bien.
- I'm gonna go too, babe. - Oh, good.
- Yo también me voy, cariño. - Oh, qué bien.
- Yay. - Yay.
- ¡Yay! - ¡Yay!
Oh, I changed my mind.
Oh, cambié de opinión.
Okay, let's talk about the party. I have so many ideas.
Okay, hablemos de la fiesta. Tengo muchísimas ideas.
- Ooh, me too. - Oh!
- Ooh, yo también. - ¡Oh!
- Yeah! - Oh, look at that.
- ¡Sí! - Oh, mira eso.
- All right. This is a little sketch of the cake. - Uh-huh. Wow.
- Muy bien. Este es un pequeño boceto del pastel. - Ajá. Vaya.
See? Um, some sample menus.
¿Ves? Um, algunos menús de muestra.
Um, you know, I thought we'd start with a Tuscan-style finger food.
Um, sabes, pensé que empezaríamos con bocadillos estilo toscano.
Okay. And for music, here's an alphabetized list of all of my CDs.
Okay. Y para la música, aquí está una lista alfabética de todos mis CDs.
I've highlighted the ones that'll go really good with the food.
He resaltado los que irían muy bien con la comida.
- What happened to the dinner party? - We're not doing that.
- ¿Qué pasó con la cena? - No la haremos.
- Okay? So... - Wow. All right.
- ¿Okay? Entonces... - Vaya. Muy bien.
Looks like you took care of everything. Thanks a lot, cohost.
Parece que te encargaste de todo. Muchas gracias, coanfitrión.
Wait. I didn't take care of everything.
Espera. No me encargué de todo.
There's plenty of things for you to do.
Hay muchas cosas que puedes hacer.
Uh-huh? Like what?
¿Ajá? ¿Cómo cuáles?
Cups.
Vasos.
Cups. You're giving me cups?
¿Vasos? ¿Me das vasos?
And ice.
Y hielo.
Cups and ice? Oh, I get to be in charge of cups and ice?
¿Vasos y hielo? Oh, ¿me encargaré de los vasos y el hielo?
All right.
De acuerdo.
Fine. Okay, I will be in charge of cups and ice.
Bien. Okay, me encargaré de los vasos y el hielo.
- Wait, I can get ice at the restaurant... - I got it.
- Espera, puedo conseguir hielo en el restaurante... - Yo lo tengo.
- Hi. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
- How did the audition go? - Not so good.
- ¿Cómo fue la audición? - No muy bien.
Wait a minute. Are you doing Joey's:
Espera un minuto. ¿Estás haciendo la de Joey:
"The audition didn't go so well. Yeah, it did!"
"La audición no salió muy bien. ¡Sí, salió!"
Yeah, I am!
¡Sí, lo estoy!
- Yeah, Ben got a second audition. - Oh, great.
- Sí, Ben consiguió una segunda audición. - Oh, genial.
Yeah, I had to teach Ross my bit because I actually didn't get a callback.
Sí, tuve que enseñarle mi parte a Ross porque en realidad no me llamaron.
You got a callback too, didn't you?
Tú también recibiste una llamada, ¿verdad?
Yeah, I did!
¡Sí, lo hice!
Hey, Rachel. What are you doing out here?
Oye, Rachel. ¿Qué haces aquí afuera?
You know, it got kind of lonely up there, so I just thought I would come out here...
Sabes, se puso un poco solitario allá arriba, así que pensé que saldría...
...and get some fresh air.
...a tomar un poco de aire fresco.
We were talking about the fall collection.
Estábamos hablando de la colección de otoño.
- Oh, great. - So anyway, we really...
- Oh, genial. - Así que, de todos modos, realmente...
- I'm sorry. We're smoking all over you. - That's okay.
- Lo siento. Estamos fumando encima de ti. - Está bien.
No, no, no. We'll move. You stay there.
No, no, no. Nos movemos. Tú quédate ahí.
I sent the designs to Ralph. He was excited about it.
Le envié los diseños a Ralph. Estaba emocionado al respecto.
That's great. You are the best.
Eso es genial. Eres la mejor.
Excuse me. Can I bum one of those?
Disculpa. ¿Me das uno de esos?
Actually, this one's...
En realidad, este es...
Okay, okay, okay. What's so funny over here?
Okay, okay, okay. ¿Qué es tan gracioso aquí?
I thought you didn't smoke.
Pensé que no fumabas.
You know, I thought you guys meant marijuana cigarettes.
Sabes, pensé que se referían a cigarrillos de marihuana.
You know what I mean? Like, doobies?
¿Sabes a qué me refiero? ¿Como porros?
Actually, I thought to myself, "Those guys are crazy."
En realidad, pensé para mí: "Esos tipos están locos".
But no, actually, I smoke the regular ones all the time.
Pero no, en realidad, yo fumo los normales todo el tiempo.
We get high.
Nos ponemos high.
Me too.
Yo también.
- I'm kidding. - Oh!
- ¡Te estoy bromeando! - ¡Oh!
Me too.
Yo también.
Oh, God. This is so nerve-racking. How do you do this?
Dios mío. Esto es tan estresante. ¿Cómo haces esto?
Well, fortunately, I don't get many callbacks so...
Bueno, afortunadamente, no recibo muchas llamadas de vuelta, así que...
Is it a good sign that they asked us to hang around after?
¿Es una buena señal que nos pidieran quedarnos después?
Who knows?
¿Quién sabe?
Okay. We have narrowed it down to Raymond, Ben, Kyle and Joey.
Okay. Hemos reducido la lista a Raymond, Ben, Kyle y Joey.
The rest of you, thank you very much.
El resto de ustedes, muchas gracias.
Yes! I knew it!
¡Sí! ¡Lo sabía!
Ah. Bye-bye.
Ah. Adiós.
So long.
Hasta luego.
Later.
This is great. I might actually get to play Ben's dad.
Esto es genial. Podría llegar a interpretar al papá de Ben.
Actually, that can't happen.
En realidad, eso no puede pasar.
Because you all have such different looks...
Como todos tienen apariencias tan diferentes...
...we're putting you with Raymond and Kyle with Ben.
...los pondremos con Raymond y a Kyle con Ben.
So it'll either be you two or you two.
Así que seremos ustedes dos o ustedes dos.
Oh, man.
Oh, Dios.
- This is gonna be kind of weird. - Yeah, it is.
- Esto va a ser un poco raro. - Sí, lo es.
Yeah. It's gonna be weird.
Sí. Va a ser raro.
No. We're like best friends. That's why it's weird.
No. Somos como mejores amigos. Por eso es raro.
Oh, oh.
I thought we were just talking.
Pensé que solo estábamos hablando.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Is it okay if I leave this stuff here till Rachel's birthday party?
¿Está bien si dejo estas cosas aquí hasta la fiesta de cumpleaños de Rachel?
- Uh, sure. What's in them? - Um, cups.
- Uh, claro. ¿Qué hay dentro? - Um, vasos.
Oh, good, because we got Rachel 800 gallons of water.
Oh, bien, porque le compramos a Rachel 800 galones de agua.
Seriously, that's a lot of cups.
En serio, esa es mucha cantidad de vasos.
Yeah, well, I'm in charge of cups and ice.
Sí, bueno, yo estoy a cargo de los vasos y el hielo.
And Monica's gonna rue the day that she put me in charge of cups and ice.
Y Monica va a lamentar el día que me puso a cargo de los vasos y el hielo.
You know, I rued the day once. Didn't get a whole lot else done.
Sabes, yo lamenté el día una vez. No hice mucho más.
Okay, time to bring up the rest of the cups.
Okay, hora de traer el resto de los vasos.
- Hey, Joey. - Hey, Pheebs.
- Hola, Joey. - Hola, Pheebs.
- Hey. - Ross, good, I'm glad you're here.
- Hola. - Ross, bien, me alegro de que estés aquí.
- I want to talk to you about something. - Oh. What's up?
- Quiero hablar contigo de algo. - Oh. ¿Qué pasa?
Well, I've been thinking about this whole commercial thing.
Bueno, he estado pensando en todo esto de los comerciales.
You know me against Ben.
Tú contra Ben.
The two of us competing. Well, that can't lead to anything good.
Nosotros dos compitiendo. Bueno, eso no puede llevar a nada bueno.
I think I'm just gonna step aside.
Creo que simplemente me haré a un lado.
I'm gonna tell them that I won't audition.
Les diré que no haré la audición.
Wow. Uh...
Vaya. Eh...
Joey, that's great. Thanks, man.
Joey, eso es genial. Gracias, amigo.
That's it?
¿Eso es todo?
You're gonna let me do this? This is my career we're talking about here.
¿Me vas a dejar hacer esto? Estamos hablando de mi carrera aquí.
But you just...
Pero tú solo...
I just said that so you wouldn't let Ben do it.
Solo dije eso para que no dejaras que Ben lo hiciera.
Look, Ross, if anyone should step aside, it should be Ben.
Mira, Ross, si alguien debe hacerse a un lado, debería ser Ben.
- What? - Chandler, tell him.
- ¿Qué? - Chandler, dile.
Well, let me get the door first.
Bueno, déjame abrir la puerta primero.
Oh, hi, no one.
Oh, hola, nadie.
Why should Ben step aside?
¿Por qué Ben debería hacerse a un lado?
It was his audition in the first place. You just tagged along.
Era su audición en primer lugar. Tú solo te uniste.
You're like the tag-along dad.
Eres como el papá que se les une.
At least I care about his feelings.
Al menos me importan sus sentimientos.
What?
¿Qué?
Do you know how hard this is gonna be on him when he doesn't get it?
¿Sabes lo difícil que va a ser para él cuando no lo consiga?
And why wouldn't he get it?
¿Y por qué no lo conseguiría?
Oh, come on.
Ay, vamos.
Have you seen what my kid can do? Huh?
¿Has visto lo que mi hijo puede hacer? ¿Eh?
I mean, he dials phones, he eats tortilla chips.
O sea, marca teléfonos, come totopos.
He plays soccer with the cartoon tiger.
Juega fútbol con el tigre de caricatura.
Are you saying your kid eats soup better than my kid?
¿Estás diciendo que tu hijo come sopa mejor que mi hijo?
You just give him a spoon, baby.
Tú solo le das una cuchara, bebé.
- Oh, yeah? I guess we'll see. - Yeah.
¿Ah, sí? Supongo que ya veremos. - Sí.
Because this commercial belongs to me and Mitch.
Porque este comercial me pertenece a mí y a Mitch.
- Your kid's name is Raymond. - Yeah? So is yours.
- El nombre de tu hijo es Raymond. - ¿Sí? El tuyo también.
- How did work go? - Oh, it was great. It was great.
- ¿Cómo te fue en el trabajo? - Oh, genial. Fue genial.
I went down there just like you said. And we talked business.
Fui hasta allá como dijiste. Y hablamos de negocios.
And Kim totally took my opinions.
Y Kim tomó totalmente mis opiniones.
You stink.
Hueles mal.
- Thanks. - No, I'm serious.
- Gracias. - No, lo digo en serio.
That's because I went down there and they were smoking.
Eso es porque fui hasta allá y estaban fumando.
This is actually the smell of success.
Este es en realidad el olor del éxito.
But there's something different, though.
Pero hay algo diferente, sin embargo.
Oh, my God. You smoked.
Dios mío. Fumaste.
- I did not. - Yes, you did.
- No lo hice. - Sí, lo hiciste.
You look happy and sick. You smoked.
Te ves feliz y enferma. Fumaste.
All right, fine. But I had to. I had to do it for my career.
Está bien, de acuerdo. Pero tuve que hacerlo. Tuve que hacerlo por mi carrera.
I wish I had to smoke for my career.
Ojalá yo tuviera que fumar por mi carrera.
That's so gross.
Eso es tan asqueroso.
Well, no, it's not that bad, you know?
Bueno, no, no es tan malo, ¿sabes?
I mean, yeah, my tongue feels a little fuzzy and my fingers sort of smell.
O sea, sí, mi lengua se siente un poco rara y mis dedos huelen un poco.
I actually feel like I could throw up.
En realidad siento que podría vomitar.
But you gotta push past this, okay? Because it's about to get so good.
Pero tienes que superar esto, ¿de acuerdo? Porque está a punto de ponerse muy bueno.
Chandler.
You smell so smoky, I gotta get up.
Hueles tan ahumado que tengo que levantarme.
I'm not kidding.
No bromeo.
I think you smell great.
Creo que hueles genial.
So we're decided. No on plaid, yes on pink.
Entonces estamos decididos. No a cuadros, sí a rosa.
Absolutely.
Absolutamente.
I'm so on board.
Estoy totalmente de acuerdo.
- Rachel, didn't you just light that? - Yeah.
- Rachel, ¿no acabas de encender eso? - Sí.
But you know what?
¿Pero sabes qué?
I'm just really, really trying to cut back, you know.
Solo estoy tratando mucho, mucho de reducir, ¿sabes?
Good luck, Rach.
Suerte, Rach.
I've actually been thinking about quitting.
De hecho, he estado pensando en renunciar.
Oh, well, sure. Every Sunday night, I tell myself I'm quitting.
Oh, bueno, claro. Todos los domingos por la noche, me digo a mí misma que voy a renunciar.
Every Monday morning, it's like:
Todos los lunes por la mañana, es como:
Tell me about it.
Ni me digas.
Well, let's quit. We'll just quit. Let's all quit.
Bueno, renunciemos. Simplemente renunciemos. Renunciemos todos.
It does sound appealing.
Suena tentador.
- I never could do it. - But you could. You can. Absolutely.
- Yo nunca pude hacerlo. - Pero tú sí. Puedes. Absolutamente.
We can help each other out. We could get those patches.
Podemos ayudarnos mutuamente. Podríamos conseguir esos parches.
We could be like the Patch Sisters.
Podríamos ser como las Hermanas del Parche.
You know, we really should quit. Okay, let's quit.
Sabes, de verdad deberíamos renunciar. Okay, renunciemos.
Yes. Great. Give me those cigs. Come on.
Sí. Genial. Dame esos cigarrillos. Vamos.
Give it. Give it. Out. Done. Quit. Whoo!
Dámelo. Dámelo. Fuera. Hecho. Renuncié. ¡Whoo!
- My late husband gave me that lighter. - Ha, ha.
- Mi difunto esposo me dio ese encendedor. - Ja, ja.
I'm not kidding.
No bromeo.
Okay, then. Okay.
Está bien, entonces. Está bien.
Mm, soup.
Mmm, sopa.
Joey, Ross is gonna be here any second.
Joey, Ross va a llegar en cualquier segundo.
Would you mind watching Ben while I use the ladies' room?
¿Te importaría cuidar a Ben mientras uso el baño de mujeres?
- Yeah, no problem. - Thanks.
- Sí, no hay problema. - Gracias.
Mm.
Hi, Ben.
Hola, Ben.
So you want to be an actor, huh? Well, I gotta tell you, it's no picnic.
Así que quieres ser actor, ¿eh? Bueno, tengo que decirte, no es un paseo por el parque.
There's tons of rejection. No stability.
Hay toneladas de rechazo. Nada de estabilidad.
I mean, one day, you're Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Quiero decir, un día eres el Dr. Drake Ramoray.
The next day, you're eating ketchup right out of the bottle.
Al día siguiente, estás comiendo kétchup directo de la botella.
Joey.
Ross.
Ben.
I mean, Ben. Ben.
Quiero decir, Ben. Ben.
Okay, Raymond, Joey, you're up.
Okay, Raymond, Joey, les toca.
- Hi. - Okay.
- Hola. - Vale.
All right, well, let's try one. Whenever you guys are ready.
Muy bien, bueno, intentemos una. Cuando ustedes estén listos.
- Uh-oh. - Is there a problem?
- Uh-oh. - ¿Hay algún problema?
Well, this is noodle soup. And I've been working with tomato.
Bueno, esto es sopa de fideos. Y yo he estado trabajando con tomate.
But that's okay. No problem. No problem.
Pero está bien. No hay problema. No hay problema.
Mm, noodle soup.
Mmm, sopa de fideos.
You know, that's fine. But the line is, "Mm, soup."
Sabes, eso está bien. Pero la frase es: "Mmm, sopa."
- Oh. What'd I say? - Mm, noodle soup.
- Oh. ¿Qué dije? - Mmm, sopa de fideos.
How's that different?
¿Cómo es diferente?
Oh. Right. Yeah.
Oh. Cierto. Sí.
All right. Let's try one.
Muy bien. Intentemos una.
Mm, noodle soup.
Mmm, sopa de fideos.
Okay. Let's do it again.
Okay. Hagámoslo de nuevo.
Okay.
Mm, soup.
Mmm, sopa.
I mean, noodle soup. I mean, soup.
Quiero decir, sopa de fideos. Quiero decir, sopa.
Come on!
¡Vamos!
You know what? We need to move on.
¿Sabes qué? Necesitamos seguir adelante.
Oh, no, I could do it one more time.
Oh, no, yo podría hacerlo una vez más.
See, look.
Mira, fíjate.
Mm, noodle soup.
Mmm, sopa de fideos.
Damn it.
Maldición.
Hey. Hey.
Oye. Oye.
Uh-oh. Busted.
Uy. Te pillaron.
Come on, you guys. What are you doing?
Vamos, chicos. ¿Qué hacen?
I thought we were the Patch Sisters.
Pensé que éramos las Hermanas Patch.
Yeah, that didn't work out.
Sí, eso no funcionó.
Rachel, we tried to quit. But it was too hard.
Rachel, intentamos renunciar. Pero fue muy difícil.
Well, if you started smoking again, you could have at least told me.
Bueno, si hubieras vuelto a fumar, al menos podrías habérmelo dicho.
Come on, give me one of those. What are we talking about?
Vamos, dame uno de esos. ¿De qué estamos hablando?
No, you're doing great. Don't give up.
No, lo estás haciendo genial. No te rindas.
That's why we didn't tell you, and we are not gonna drag you down.
Por eso no te lo dijimos, y no te vamos a arrastrar hacia abajo.
Oh, wait. No, no. Drag me down. Drag me down.
Oh, espera. No, no. Arrástrame hacia abajo. Arrástrame hacia abajo.
Forget it, Rachel. We're both so proud of how well you're doing.
Olvídalo, Rachel. Ambas estamos muy orgullosas de lo bien que te va.
I'm not gonna let you blow it. In fact, if I catch you, you're fired.
No voy a dejar que lo arruines. De hecho, si te pillo, estás despedida.
So go on, get out of here. Go on. I don't want you breathing this stuff. Go on.
Así que adelante, sal de aquí. Anda. No quiero que respires esto. Anda.
So okay. So you'll come with me on the Paris trip?
Entonces, ¿vale? ¿Vendrás conmigo al viaje a París?
Oh, man.
Oh, Dios.
Hey, check it out. Cup hat, cup banner...
Oye, mira esto. Sombrero de taza, pancarta de taza...
...cup chandelier and the thing that started it all. The cup.
...candelabro de tazas y la cosa que lo empezó todo. La taza.
- Great job with the cups, Pheebs. - Ha, ha.
Gran trabajo con las tazas, Pheebs. - Ja, ja.
Why don't you just go out with her?
¿Por qué no sales con ella?
Did you notice the ice? Look.
¿Notaste el hielo? Mira.
We have it all. We have crushed, cubed and dry. Watch.
Lo tenemos todo. Tenemos picado, en cubos y seco. Mira.
Ah.
Mystical.
Místico.
No one's eating my Tuscan finger food. They're filling up on Phoebe's snow cones.
Nadie está comiendo mi comida italiana. Se están llenando con los conos de nieve de Phoebe.
There are snow cones?
¿Hay conos de nieve?
Snow cones. Yuck.
Conos de nieve. Puaj.
- Go, go. - Thank you. Thank you.
Vamos, vamos. - Gracias. Gracias.
- Look, look. - Surprise.
Mira, mira. - Sorpresa.
What? My birthday is not for another month.
¿Qué? Mi cumpleaños no es hasta dentro de un mes.
That's the surprise.
Esa es la sorpresa.
Oh, my God, you guys. This is so great. It's so unexpected.
Dios mío, chicos. Esto es genial. Es tan inesperado.
I mean, Chandler's birthday's even before mine.
Quiero decir, el cumpleaños de Chandler es incluso antes que el mío.
Surprise.
Sorpresa.
Wow. This is so great. Look at all these...
Guau. Esto es genial. Mira todas estas...
...cups. This is so weird.
...tazas. Esto es muy raro.
I was in charge of cups.
Yo estaba a cargo de las tazas.
Oh, okay. Not so weird.
Oh, vale. No tan raro.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hola. - Hola.
Listen, man. I'm sorry the audition didn't go well.
Escucha, amigo. Lamento que la audición no haya ido bien.
Yeah, right.
Sí, claro.
No, really. I am, Joey. I feel bad.
No, de verdad. Lo siento, Joey. Me siento mal.
Well, look, Ross. You don't have to, okay?
Bueno, mira, Ross. No tienes por qué, ¿vale?
It's not your fault I suck.
No es mi culpa que apeste.
What kind of an actor can't even say, "Mm, noodle soup"?
¿Qué clase de actor no puede ni decir "Mm, sopa de fideos"?
Hey, you know what? Maybe you didn't mess up your audition because you suck.
Oye, ¿sabes qué? Quizás no arruinaste tu audición porque apestas.
Maybe you messed up because you care more about your godson.
Quizás la arruinaste porque te importa más tu ahijado.
- What do you mean? - I think, subconsciously...
- ¿A qué te refieres? - Creo que, subconscientemente...
Whoa, you lost me.
Vaya, me perdí.
I think, on some level, you sabotaged...
Creo que, a algún nivel, saboteaste...
...your own audition so Ben would get the part.
...tu propia audición para que Ben consiguiera el papel.
Well, your way sounds a lot better than mine.
Bueno, tu manera suena mucho mejor que la mía.
Yeah.
Sí.
- Yeah. It's not that I'm a bad actor. - No.
- Sí. No es que sea un mal actor. - No.
No, it's just that, uh, I care so damn much about little Ben...
No, es solo que, eh, me importa tanto este pequeño Ben...
...that, uh, it was more important for me to see him succeed.
...que, eh, era más importante para mí verlo triunfar.
- There you go. Thank you. - Thank you.
- Ahí tienes. Gracias. - Gracias.
- So did he get it? - No.
- ¿Y se lo dieron? - No.
Ah, what are you gonna do?
Ah, ¿qué se le va a hacer?
Oh, hi. Excuse me. Is Rachel Green here? I'm supposed to meet her for lunch.
Oh, hola. Disculpe. ¿Está Rachel Green aquí? Debo reunirme con ella para almorzar.
Oh, she doesn't come down anymore. You can find her up on 10.
Oh, ya no baja. Puedes encontrarla en el piso 10.
Okay, great.
Okay, genial.
So we talked about the presentation at lunch.
Así que hablamos de la presentación en el almuerzo.
He wondered if one person would be enough for me to take on the trip.
Se preguntó si una persona sería suficiente para que me acompañara en el viaje.
And I said, "Yeah, absolutely."
Y dije: "Sí, absolutamente."
I'll catch you guys later.
Los veo luego, chicos.