Okay, these were expensive, and he's gonna grow out of them...
Okay, estos fueron caros, y se le van a quedar pequeños...
...in 20 minutes, but I couldn't resist!
...en 20 minutos, ¡pero no pude resistirme!
Aww!
¡Ay!
Look at these.
Miren estos.
Hey, Ben.
Hola, Ben.
"Just do it"! Unh!
"¡Solo hazlo"! ¡Uf!
Oh, my God! Oh!
¡Oh, Dios mío! ¡Oh!
Was that too much pressure for him?
¿Fue demasiada presión para él?
- Oh, is he hungry already? Aw. - I guess so.
- Oh, ¿ya tiene hambre? Aw. - Supongo que sí.
You know, it's...
Sabes, es...
Something funny about sneakers. I'll be right back.
Algo gracioso sobre los tenis. Vuelvo enseguida.
Oh, uh, I gotta get one too.
Oh, eh, tengo que comprar uno también.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Oigan, ¿qué están haciendo?
We're just hanging out by the spoons.
Solo estamos aquí cerca de las cucharas.
Ladle?
¿Un cucharón?
Will you guys grow up?
¿Van a madurar de una vez?
This is the most natural, beautiful thing in the world.
Esta es la cosa más natural y hermosa del mundo.
Yeah, we know. But there's a baby sucking on it.
Sí, lo sabemos. Pero hay un bebé chupándola.
This is my son having lunch, okay? It'll happen a lot, so get used to it.
Este es mi hijo almorzando, ¿okay? Va a pasar mucho, así que acostúmbrate.
If you have a problem, if you're uncomfortable, just ask questions.
Si tienes un problema, si te sientes incómodo, solo haz preguntas.
Carol's fine with it. Come on.
Carol está bien con eso. Vamos.
- Carol? - Carol.
- ¿Carol? - Carol.
I was wondering if Joey could ask you a question about breast-feeding?
Me preguntaba si Joey podría hacerte una pregunta sobre la lactancia?
- Sure. - Uh...
- Claro. - Uh...
Does it hurt?
¿Duele?
It did at first, but not anymore.
Al principio sí, pero ya no.
Chandler?
¿Chandler?
So, uh, how often can you do it?
Entonces, eh, ¿con qué frecuencia puedes hacerlo?
As much as he needs.
Tanto como él necesite.
Oh, okay, I got one, I got one. Uh...
Oh, okay, tengo una, tengo una. Uh...
If he blows into one, does the other one get bigger?
Si sopla en una, ¿la otra se hace más grande?
- Rachel, do you have muffins left? - Yeah, I forget which ones.
- Rachel, ¿te quedan muffins? - Sí, no recuerdo cuáles.
Oh, you're busy, I'll get it.
Oh, estás ocupada, yo lo agarro.
- Anyone else want one? - No, thanks.
- ¿Alguien más quiere uno? - No, gracias.
No, I'm all set.
No, estoy bien.
Oh, you're losing your apron. Let me get it.
Oh, se te está cayendo el delantal. Déjame agarrarlo.
- Oh. - There you go.
- Oh. - Aquí tienes.
Thank you.
Gracias.
Ugh, what a bitch.
Ugh, qué cabrona.
Listen, guys, I have a friend at Bloomingdale's who's quitting...
Escuchen, tengo una amiga en Bloomingdale's que se va a ir...
...and he wants to abuse his discount.
...y quiere aprovechar su descuento.
So anyone want to come take advantage of it?
¿Así que alguien quiere venir a aprovecharlo?
I can't. I have to take my grandmother to the vet.
No puedo. Tengo que llevar a mi abuela al veterinario.
- Okay. Um, I'll go with you. Great.
- Okay. Um, iré contigo. Genial.
Hi, honey. - Hey, sweetums.
Hola, cariño. - Hola, dulzura.
- And hello to the rest. Hi.
- Y hola al resto. Hola.
What are you doing?
¿Qué estás haciendo?
You can't go shopping with her. What about Rachel?
No puedes ir de compras con ella. ¿Qué hay de Rachel?
- It's gonna be a problem, isn't it? - Come on.
- Va a ser un problema, ¿verdad? - Vamos.
You're going to Bloomingdale's with Julie.
Vas a ir a Bloomingdale's con Julie.
It's like cheating on Rachel in her house of worship.
[ERROR API]
- But I... - Monica, she will kill you.
She will kill you like a dog in the street!
[ERROR API]
So, uh, Jules tells me you guys are going shopping tomorrow.
Yeah, um, it's actually not that big a deal. In fact...
[ERROR API]
It's a big deal to me. This is great. I really appreciate this.
You're welcome.
De nada.
Bijan for men?
[ERROR API]
- Hey, Annabel. - Hey, Joey.
- Did you hear about the new guy? - Who?
[ERROR API]
Nobody knows his name. Me and the girls call him "The Hombre Man. "
Hombre?
[ERROR API]
What's he doing in my section?
I guess he doesn't know.
[ERROR API]
Well, he's gonna.
I'll see you a little later, okay?
[ERROR API]
Hey, how you doing?
Morning.
Buenos días.
Listen, uh, heh. I know you're new...
[ERROR API]
...but, uh, it's kind of understood that everything...
...from young men's to the escalator is, uh, my territory.
[ERROR API]
- Your territory, huh? - Yeah.
- Bijan for men? - No, thanks.
[ERROR API]
Hombre?
Yeah, all right.
Sí, está bien.
You were saying?
[ERROR API]
Phoebe, listen. You were with me, and we were shopping all day.
- What? - We were shopping and we had lunch.
[ERROR API]
All right. What did I have?
- You had a salad. - No wonder I don't feel full.
[ERROR API]
Hi, guys. What's up?
I went shopping with Monica all day and I had a salad.
[ERROR API]
Good, Pheebs. What'd you buy?
Um...
We went shopping for, um...
[ERROR API]
For, um...
For fur.
[ERROR API]
- You went shopping for fur? - Yeah.
And then I realized that I'm against that and, um...
[ERROR API]
So then we bought some, um...
Um, boobs.
[ERROR API]
You bought boobs?
Bras!
[ERROR API]
We bought bras!
We bought bras.
[ERROR API]
Bijan for men?
Bijan for...
[ERROR API]
Hey, Annabel. Uh...
Listen, I was wondering if after work we could grab a cup of coffee?
[ERROR API]
Actually, I sort of have plans.
Oh.
You ready, Annabel?
¿Lista, Annabel?
You bet.
Claro que sí.
- Maybe some other time. - Yeah.
- Quizás en otra ocasión. - Sí.
It's not the first time I lost a girl to a cowboy spraying cologne.
No es la primera vez que pierdo una chica por un cowboy que se rocía colonia.
Bijan for men?
¿Bijan for men?
Bijan for men!
¡Bijan for men!
Okay, and this is Funny Clown.
Okay, y este es Payaso Divertido.
Funny Clown is only for after his naps, not before or he won't sleep.
Payaso Divertido es solo para después de sus siestas, no antes o no dormirá.
We've been through this before. We have a good time.
Ya hemos pasado por esto. Nos lo pasamos bien.
We laugh, we play. It's like we're father and son.
Nos reímos, jugamos. Es como si fuéramos padre e hijo.
Honey, relax. Ross is great with him.
Cariño, relájate. Ross se las arregla muy bien con él.
Don't look so surprised. I'm a lovely person.
No te sorprendas tanto. Soy una persona encantadora.
Oh, this is so cute.
Oh, esto es tan tierno.
Ah, I got that for him!
¡Ah, se lo compré yo!
"My Mommies Love Me. "
"Mis mamás me quieren."
That's clever.
Eso es ingenioso.
Hello?
¿Hola?
Oh, hi, Jul...
Oh, hola, Jul...
Hi, Jew!
¡Hola, Judio!
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
Uh-huh. Okay, um, sure.
Ajá. Okay, eh, claro.
That'd be great. See you then. Bye.
Sería genial. Nos vemos entonces. Adiós.
Did you just say, "Hi, Jew"?
¿Acabas de decir "Hola, Judio"?
Yes. Um, yes, I did.
Sí. Eh, sí, lo hice.
That was my friend Eddie Moskowitz.
Ese era mi amigo Eddie Moskowitz.
Yeah, he likes it. Reaffirms his faith.
Sí, le gusta. Reafirma su fe.
Ben, dinner!
¡Ben, a cenar!
Thanks, Aunt Pheebs.
Gracias, tía Pheebs.
You didn't microwave that, did you? It's breast milk, you're not supposed to.
No lo calentaste en el microondas, ¿verdad? Es leche materna, no se supone que debas hacerlo.
Duh, I think I know how to heat breast milk. Heh.
Obvio, creo que sé cómo calentar leche materna. Je.
Okay.
What did you just do?
¿Qué acabas de hacer?
I licked my arm, what?
Me lamí el brazo, ¿qué?
It's breast milk!
¡Es leche materna!
So?
¿Y bien?
Phoebe, that is juice squeezed from a person.
Phoebe, eso es jugo exprimido de una persona.
- What is the big deal? No, no...
- ¿Cuál es el gran problema? No, no...
What did you just do?
¿Qué acabas de hacer?
Can people stop drinking the breast milk?
¿Puede la gente dejar de beber la leche materna?
- You won't even taste it? - No.
- ¿Ni siquiera lo probarás? - No.
Not even if you just pretend it's milk?
¿Ni siquiera si pretendes que es leche?
Not even if Carol's breast had a picture of a missing child on it.
Ni siquiera si el pecho de Carol tuviera la foto de un niño desaparecido.
- Hey. - Hi.
- Hola. - Hola.
- Where is everybody? - Took Ben to the park.
- ¿Dónde está todo el mundo? - Llevamos a Ben al parque.
- Where have you been? - Just out.
- ¿Dónde has estado? - Solo afuera.
Had some lunch. Just me. A little quality time with me.
Tomé algo de almuerzo. Solo yo. Un poco de tiempo de calidad conmigo.
- Hey, thanks for your jacket. - Oh, no problem.
- Oye, gracias por tu chaqueta. - Oh, de nada.
- You can borrow it, by the way. - Heh.
- Puedes tomarla prestada, por cierto. - Je.
- Oh, here are your keys, honey. - Thank you.
- Oh, aquí tienes tus llaves, cariño. - Gracias.
- Mon? - Mm-hmm?
- ¿Lunes? - Mm-hmm?
If, uh, you were at lunch alone, how come it cost you $53?
Si, eh, estabas almorzando sola, ¿cómo es que te costó $53?
You know what probably happened?
¿Sabes qué probablemente pasó?
- Someone must have stolen my credit card. - Ah.
- Alguien debió robar mi tarjeta de crédito. - Ah.
And put the receipt back in your pocket?
¿Y volver a poner el recibo en tu bolsillo?
Huh. That is an excellent, excellent question.
Hmm. Esa es una excelente, excelente pregunta.
That is excellent.
Eso es excelente.
What's with you? Who did you have lunch with?
¿Qué te pasa? ¿Con quién almorzaste?
- Judy. - Who?
- Judy. - ¿Quién?
- Julie. Jody? - What?
- Julie. ¿Jody? - ¿Qué?
- You were with Julie? - Mm. Look.
- ¿Estuviste con Julie? - Mm. Mira.
When it started, I was just trying to be nice to her...
Cuando empezó, solo intentaba ser amable con ella...
...because she was my brother's girlfriend.
...porque era la novia de mi hermano.
And then one thing led to another...
Y luego una cosa llevó a la otra...
...and before I knew it, we were...
...y antes de que me diera cuenta, estábamos...
...shopping. - Aah.
...de compras. - Aah.
Oh, my God.
Dios mío.
Wait, we only did it once.
Espera, solo lo hicimos una vez.
It didn't mean anything to me.
No significó nada para mí.
- Yeah, right. Sure. - Really!
- Sí, claro. Seguro. - ¡De verdad!
Rachel, I was thinking of you the whole time.
Rachel, estuve pensando en ti todo el tiempo.
Look, I'm sorry, all right? I never meant for you to find out.
Mira, lo siento, ¿de acuerdo? Nunca quise que te enteraras.
Oh, please! Please! You wanted to get caught!
¡Oh, por favor! ¡Por favor! ¡Querías que te atraparan!
That is not true!
¡Eso no es verdad!
So you just happened to leave it in here?
¿Así que simplemente te pasó dejarlo aquí?
Did it ever occur to you that I might just be that stupid?
¿Se te ocurrió que podría ser tan estúpida?
Okay, Monica, I just have to know one thing.
Está bien, Monica, solo necesito saber una cosa.
Did you go with her to Bloomingdale's?
¿Fuiste con ella a Bloomingdale's?
Okay. Okay.
Okay, I just really, um... I just need to not be with you right now.
Está bien, yo solo realmente, eh... solo necesito no estar contigo ahora mismo.
Hi, who's this?
Hola, ¿quién es?
Hi, Joanne. Is Rachel working? It's Monica.
Hola, Joanne. ¿Está Rachel trabajando? Soy Monica.
Yes, I know I did a horrible thing.
Sí, sé que hice algo horrible.
Joanne, it's not as simple as all that, okay?
Joanne, no es tan simple como eso, ¿de acuerdo?
No, I don't care what Steve thinks. Hi, Steve.
No, no me importa lo que piense Steve. Hola, Steve.
- Hey! Hi!
- ¡Hey! ¡Hola!
How did we do?
¿Cómo lo hicimos?
Oh, I tasted Ben's milk and Ross freaked out.
Oh, probé la leche de Ben y Ross se alteró.
I... I did not freak out.
Yo... yo no me alteré.
- Why'd you freak out? - Because it's breast milk.
- ¿Por qué te alteraste? - Porque es leche materna.
It's gross!
¡Es asqueroso!
My breast milk is gross?
¿Mi leche materna es asqueroso?
This should be fun.
Esto debería ser divertido.
No, Carol. There's nothing wrong with it.
No, Carol. No tiene nada de malo.
I just don't think breast milk is for adults.
Solo no creo que la leche materna sea para adultos.
Of course, the packaging does appeal to grownups and kids.
Claro, el empaque sí atrae a adultos y niños.
Ross, you're being silly. I've tried it. It's no big deal.
Ross, estás siendo tonto. Yo la he probado. No es gran cosa.
- Come on, just taste it. - Ha-ha-ha.
- Vamos, solo pruébala. - Ja-ja-ja.
That would be no.
Eso sería un no.
- Come on. - Try it.
- Vamos. - Pruébala.
- It's natural. - It doesn't taste bad.
- Es natural. - No sabe mal.
Yeah, it tastes kind of sweet. Sort of like, uh...
Sí, sabe como dulce. Algo como, eh...
- Like what? - Cantaloupe juice.
- ¿Como qué? - Jugo de melón.
Exactly.
Exacto.
You've tasted it.
Ya lo probaste.
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
Oh, you've tasted it.
Oh, ya lo probaste.
You can keep saying it, but it won't stop being true.
Puedes seguir diciéndolo, pero no dejará de ser verdad.
Give me the bottle.
Dame la botella.
Get me the towel.
Tráeme la toalla.
Howdy.
¿Qué tal?
Give me a box ofjuice.
Deme una caja de jugo.
Well, they switched me over to Hombre.
Bueno, me cambiaron a Hombre.
Maybe it's because of the way you're dressed.
Tal vez sea por cómo vas vestido.
Or maybe this guy's doing so good they want to put more people on it.
O tal vez a este tipo le va tan bien que quieren poner a más gente en ello.
This guy goes through two bottles a day now.
Este tipo se toma dos botellas al día ahora.
What do you care?
¿A ti qué te importa?
You're an actor. This is your day job. Isn't supposed to mean anything.
Eres actor. Este es tu trabajo de día. No se supone que signifique nada.
I know, but I was the best.
Lo sé, pero era el mejor.
You know? I liked being the best.
¿Sabes? Me gustaba ser el mejor.
Maybe I should get out of the game.
Tal vez debería dejarlo.
They need guys up in housewares to serve cheese.
Necesitan gente en el departamento de hogar para servir queso.
Say you do that.
Digamos que haces eso.
Sooner or later, somebody will come along that slices a better cheddar.
Tarde o temprano, alguien vendrá que corte un mejor cheddar.
And then where you gonna run?
¿Y entonces a dónde vas a huir?
- I guess you're right. - Damn right I'm right.
- Supongo que tienes razón. - Claro que tengo razón.
Show this guy what you're made of. Stand your ground.
Demuéstrale a este tipo de lo que estás hecho. Mantente firme.
Show him that you're the baddest Hombre west of the lingerie!
¡Demuéstrale que eres el Hombre más rudo al oeste de lencería!
- I'm gonna do it! - All right!
- ¡Lo haré! - ¡Muy bien!
Now, go see Miss Kitty and she'll fix you up with a nice hooker.
Ahora, ve a ver a Miss Kitty y ella te conseguirá una buena prostituta.
I don't know what to say.
No sé qué decir.
That works good because I'm not listening.
Eso funciona bien porque no estoy escuchando.
I feel terrible. I really do.
Me siento terrible. De verdad.
Oh, I'm sorry. Did my back hurt your knife?
Oh, lo siento. ¿Mi espalda te lastimó el cuchillo?
Rachel!
¡Rachel!
Say that I'm friends with her. We spend time together.
Di que soy su amiga. Pasamos tiempo juntas.
- Is that so terrible? - Yes.
- ¿Es tan terrible? - Sí.
- It's that terrible? - Yes, Monica! You don't get it.
- ¿Es tan terrible? - ¡Sí, Monica! No lo entiendes.
It's bad enough she stole the guy...
Ya es bastante malo que le robó al tipo...
...who may be the person I'm supposed to be with.
...con quien se supone que debo estar.
But now...
Pero ahora...
...she's actually...
...ella en realidad está...
But now she's actually stealing you!
¡Pero ahora te está robando a ti!
Me?
¿Yo?
What are you talking about?
¿De qué estás hablando?
Nobody could steal me from you.
Nadie podría robarme de ti.
Because I'm friends with her doesn't make me any less friends with you.
Porque sea amiga de ella no significa que sea menos tu amiga.
Honey.
Cariño.
I mean, you're my...
Quiero decir, tú eres mi...
And we're...
Y estamos...
- Oh, I love you! - I love you too!
- ¡Oh, te amo! - ¡Yo también te amo!
You guys, um, I know that this really doesn't have anything to do with me.
Chicos, eh, sé que esto realmente no tiene nada que ver conmigo.
But, um, I love you guys too!
Pero, eh, ¡yo también los amo, chicos!
Ugh, I really needed that.
Uf, realmente necesitaba eso.
Look, I know you're in a place right now...
Mira, sé que estás en un momento...
...where you really need to hate Julie's guts.
...en el que realmente necesitas odiar a Julie.
But she didn't do anything wrong.
Pero ella no hizo nada malo.
She's just a girl who met a guy, and now they go out.
Ella es solo una chica que conoció a un chico, y ahora salen.
I think that if you gave her a chance, you'd like her.
Creo que si le dieras una oportunidad, te caería bien.
Will you give that a chance?
¿Le darás una oportunidad?
For me?
¿Por mí?
I'd do anything for you, you know that.
Haría cualquier cosa por ti, lo sabes.
I'd do anything for you!
¡Haría cualquier cosa por ti!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
¡Espera, espera, espera, espera!
Morning.
Buenos días.
Heh. I said, morning.
Je. Dije, buenos días.
I heard you.
Te oí.
All right, everybody. I'm opening the doors.
Muy bien, todos. Estoy abriendo las puertas.
You boys ready?
¿Están listos, chicos?
Ready.
Listos.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Sí, estoy listo.
You idiot! You stupid cowboy!
¡Idiota! ¡Estúpido vaquero!
You've blinded me! I'm suing!
¡Me has cegado! ¡Te voy a demandar!
Oh, my God! Todd! What the hell did you do?
¡Dios mío! ¡Todd! ¿Qué demonios hiciste?
I'm sorry. I'm such a doofus!
Lo siento. ¡Soy un tonto!
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Lo siento mucho. Lo siento mucho.
My God, what happened?
Dios mío, ¿qué pasó?
Eh, these new kids, they never last.
Eh, estos chicos nuevos, nunca duran.
Sooner or later they all...
Tarde o temprano todos...
...stop lasting.
...dejan de durar.
Listen, uh, what do you say I buy you that cup of coffee now?
Escucha, eh, ¿qué dices si te invito esa taza de café ahora?
Sure.
Claro.
- So. - So.
- Entonces. - Entonces.
I just thought the two of us should hang out a bit.
Solo pensé que nosotros dos deberíamos pasar un rato.
I mean, you know, we've never really talked.
Quiero decir, ya sabes, nunca hemos hablado realmente.
I guess you'd know that, being one of the two of us. Ha, ha, right?
Supongo que lo sabrías, siendo uno de nosotros dos. Ja, ja, ¿verdad?
- I know. - Mm.
- Lo sé. - Mm.
I probably shouldn't even tell you this...
Probablemente ni siquiera debería decirte esto...
...but I'm pretty much totally intimidated by you.
...pero me intimidas bastante.
Really? Me?
¿En serio? ¿Yo?
Oh, my God, are you kidding?
¡Dios mío, ¿estás bromeando?!
Ross is so crazy about you...
Ross está muy loco por ti...
...and I really wanted you to like me, and I...
...y realmente quería que te cayera bien, y yo...
It's probably me just being totally paranoid...
Probablemente soy yo, solo estoy totalmente paranoica...
...but I kind of got the feeling that maybe you don't.
...pero tengo la sensación de que tal vez no.
Well...
Bueno...
...you're not totally paranoid.
...no estás totalmente paranoica.
- Oy. - Um.
- Oy. - Eh.
Okay. Um...
Está bien. Um...
- God. Um... - Heh.
- Dios. Eh... - Je.
When you and, uh, Ross first started going out...
Cuando tú y, eh, Ross empezaron a salir...
...it was really hard for me, um...
...fue muy difícil para mí, eh...
...for many reasons of which I'm not gonna bore you with now, but, um...
...por muchas razones de las que no te voy a aburrir ahora, pero, eh...
I see how happy he is and how good you guys are together.
Veo lo feliz que está y lo bien que se complementan.
And, um, Monica's always saying how nice you are...
Y, eh, Monica siempre dice lo simpática que eres...
...and God, I hate it when she's right.
...y, Dios, odio cuando tiene razón.
- Thanks. - Yeah.
- Gracias. - Sí.
Listen. Would you like to go to a movie sometime or something?
Escucha. ¿Te gustaría ir al cine alguna vez o algo así?
- Yeah, that'd be great. I'd love it. - Yeah?
- Sí, sería genial. Me encantaría. - ¿Sí?
- I'd love it too. Okay. - Okay.
- A mí también me encantaría. Vale. - Vale.
- Oh, shoot, I gotta go. - Okay.
- Oh, caray, me tengo que ir. - Vale.
- So I'll talk to you later. - All right, Julie.
- Entonces hablamos luego. - De acuerdo, Julie.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Adiós. - Adiós.
What a manipulative bitch.
Qué manipuladora.
It's not bad.
No está mal.